This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
As usual...
ACT.1
Ultimate Tofu Guy Drift
1,300,000 yen ($13,000)
for a 1991 model.
As I thought, the S13
is expensive.
It's the Eight-Six after all.
It's more realistic.
The car has to be FR,
right, Takumi?
Takumi?
Hey, are you listening?!
I am, Itsuki.
So, how much is
that Eight-Six thing?
Well, there's one
for 300,000 ($3000).
It needs the tag though.
And how much do you
have saved so far?
A little over 50,000 ($500).
Long way to go...
Where can I find a good job
for quick money?
Even if I work full time this summer
at the station we're at...
...I can only earn 120,000 ($1200)
at most.
I wonder if I can find
a better paying job...
You guys have jobs?
Mogi?
What, is it so surprising
for me to talk to you?
Not really.
120,000 for full time
during the summer?
How long do you
work a day?
From the morning until the night!
You work that hard, and you
only earn 120,000 a month?
That's a ballpark figure.
Pay's really low for
high school students.
I didn't know.
I've never had a job.
Work hard, okay?
Let's go out together when
finals are over, okay?
Yeah!
She just said "go out together",
didn't she?
Yeah.
With Mogi...?
Cool, cool!
Takumi, why didn't
you tell me?
You should've told me
that you knew her.
It's been almost a year since
I last talked to her.
We were in the same club...
...so we used to talk often,
until last summer.
What're you talking about?
It doesn't matter anymore.
Mogi Natsuki, huh?
What a nice turn in the story!
My eyes can't help following her.
She's so cute...
Takumi!
Hey, Takumi!
You look out of it!
We've gotta hurry!
We have a grammar test!
H...hey!
Say, why don't we buy
an Eight-Six together?
If we combine our pay,
we can pay the loan.
I don't want to.
Why do you want a car so badly?
Your family has one, don't they?
It's no good!
My dad's car is automatic
and front wheel drive.
And the engine is diesel.
It sucks.
It's not even a car.
If it runs on four tires, it's a car.
You don't know anything...
If it's not enjoyable on the mountain
passes, I don't call it a car.
What do you do on the
mountain passes?
It's so obvious.
Tackle the corners!
The corners?
Is it fun doing that?
Of course!
You're a man, and you don't want to tackle
the corners on the mountain passes?!
I'm tired of that kind of thing.
What do you mean?
We just got our licenses
last month.
You're pretty.
You look best in your uniform.
Do I?
Thank you, Papa.
Papa, my schoolmate has a job.
Even if he works throughout the summer,
he'll only earn 120,000 or so.
Well, that's about right.
I guess it's hard to earn money.
I receive 300,000 ($3000) a month
by only seeing you three times.
Is it alright to get that much?
It's alright, because you're worth it.
Is it?  I don't know.
Thank you very much.
Hey, Takumi, think about
the Eight-Six, okay?
Forget about the Eight-Six.
You guys have good taste...
...looking at an Eight-Six.
Right, right, right?
You think so, too, Iketani?
Yeah, the Eight-Six is a good car.
See?!
Well, to tell the truth, I don't know
anything about the Eight-Six.
Who makes it?
Are you serious, Takumi?
Wanna drink some high octane?!
It's pitiful for someone working at a gas station
not to know about the Eight-Six!
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
When you guys were in 3rd or 4th grade,
the 92 was already available.
There's an old car we use
for work, at my place...
Don't compare it with that!
Even if it's old, the Eight-Six is different!
If I bought an Eight-Six,
could I join your team?
I've been dreaming of joining
the Akina Speedstars!
Sure.
By the way, it's Saturday, so people
will be gathering on Mt. Akina tonight.
You wanna come along?
Can we?
But... we don't have a car.
I'll give you a ride.
In your S13?
I will, I will!
I'll definitely go!
You're going, right, Takumi?  We don't
get a chance like this very often!
Yahoo, I'll join the Speedstars!
I didn't say I was going.
We're leaving!
Alright, and I'll pick you up
at the bus station at 8:00pm!
Okay!
You're really into it.  Which mountain
pass are you going to?
Manager, Mt. Akina is the only place
to drive around here.
Our team is proud of being
the fastest on Mt. Akina.
There are many guys who proclaim
themselves the fastest on Mt. Akina.
When I was actively driving...
...there was a guy everyone knew
was the fastest on Mt. Akina.
And he's still driving on Mt. Akina.
Even now?
I know most of the people driving on Mt. Akina,
but I don't know anyone that old.
He doesn't drive at the
same time you do.
He's an old guy, who
runs a tofu shop.
He delivers tofu to the hotel
by Akina Lake around 4:00am.
His speed on the downhill
is well worth watching.
He has to drive in rain and snow,
because it's his job.
If it's Akina, he knows everything,
even the stains on the asphalt.
I bet the fastest on Mt. Akina is
the Eight-Six from a tofu shop.
The Eight-Six from
a tofu shop?!
Are you going out, Takumi?
Yeah, I'm supposed to
meet with Itsuki.
I don't mind you
staying out late...
...but I'll beat you until you
wake up in the morning.
I know.  You don't have to tell me.
Well, I'm leaving.
Shut up, Takumi!
You'll disturb Iketani!
Even if you say so,
what's scary is scary!
It can't be helped.
Everyone's scared when
riding with a Road Racer.
Next, it's a hairpin
curve in 2nd gear.
Shut up, Takumi!
Alright, I'll push a
little harder tonight.
Okay, let's go full tilt.
Are you alright, Takumi?
I didn't expect you
to be so scared...
...so I pushed hard without
worrying about you.
You're such a wimp!
You're so uncool!
You must be one of those people
who screams on a roller coaster!
I've never thought a
roller coaster was scary!
It's not like that...
Itsuki, you wouldn't
understand this fear...
...even if I explained it to you.
I've never seen them before...
Are they heading for
Mt. Akina at this time?
Something might be
happening at the peak.
Never seen them before.
Redsuns...?
Are they the Redsuns,
the fastest on Akagi?
We're the members of the
Akagi Redsuns team.
I hate to ask this so
abruptly, but...
...if you know any team or driver who's
the fastest on this mountain, let us know.
Is he serious?
It should be us.
We're the Akina Speedstars team...
...and we consider ourselves the fastest here.
That makes it easy.
Would you like to hold a "gathering" with
the Akagi Redsuns on this mountain?
Wow, it's gonna be a cool scene!
What do you say?
It's boring, always driving
against people you know.
It's exciting to drive
with other teams.
You can make new friends,
and exchange information.
It'll help improve both
of our skill levels.
We'll drive along for a while,
then pick one from each team...
...and race uphill and
downhill at the end.
We're not concerned about winning or losing,
just friendship between teams.
How does it sound?
If that's what it is, we don't have
any reason to decline.
Nope.
How does next Saturday
at 10:00pm sound?
Okay, fine.
Then we'll drive as much
as we can today.
This is awesome,
so awesome, Takumi!
We don't have to hold back!
Let's get going!
Okay!
Iketani...
Let me see how the Takahashi brothers,
the fastest on Akagi, drive.
Takahashi brothers...?
Do you mean they're the super famous
Takahashi brothers...
...the ones who were covered
in the magazine?
rotary:  reference to the Wankel engine used by Mazda
Yeah, people call them the Takahashi
brothers of the rotary engine.
Iketani, what about us?
Sorry, but I drive alone
when I drive seriously.
Wait here,
I'll pick you up later.
I feel left out!
Why are we the only ones
who don't have a car?
Hey, Itsuki...
...is it so fun to be a Road Racer?
Why do they get so excited
about such a thing?
I'm the one who has to wonder!
Hearing the sounds of cars
being pushed to the limit...
...don't you get excited, Takumi?
Excited...?
Yes, Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Oh, it's you, Yuichi.
What's with the call
in the middle of the night?
"It's you" you said?
It's been a while, and you sound so cold.
I passed you coming back
from your delivery.
I flashed my lights,
but you ignored me.
No, that wasn't me.
It had to be, because the car was your Eight-Six.
Well, actually...
It was probably my car,
but I wasn't driving.
My son, Takumi, is delivering
tofu to the hotel now.
S...say what?!
S...since when?
Five years ago.
"Five years ago...?"
(Note:  Japan's legal driving age is 18.)
When he was only 7th grade?!
Dammit, I can't keep up!
They're fast.
I'm pushing myself to the limit, and I can't
catch any of the Redsuns.
What do you think, Brother?
They're pathetic.
Even our second stringers
could beat them.
We don't have to send
our best next week.
I'll pass on it.
If you won't, then I'll pass, too.
No, you should drive.
Leave a course record that the
local guys can never beat.
Otherwise, the name of the Akagi
Redsuns won't become legend.
For starters, we'll rewrite every
course record in this prefecture.
Soon, we'll do the same in Saitama,
Kanagawa, Tokyo, and Chiba.
We'll be legendary Road Racers, leaving the fastest
records in the Kanto area, then retire.
That's the Akagi Redsuns'
"Fastest in Kanto Project."
Incredible.  They're
fundamentally different.
It's so shocking to be outrun
by outsiders on our home ground.
They've spent a lot of money on their
suspension, and they've got power, too.
It's impossible to compete
with the Redsuns.
But the local people can't run away!
Right.  Since we said
"yes," we have to!
But you can't beat them with just guts.
Well, that's...  But...
It's getting late, so let's find a place
to talk about this tomorrow.
Road Racers hate defeat.
So when it comes to racing,
we tend to become overly stubborn.
Nothing could be worse than being defeated
by outsiders on our home ground.
It's like the code of the Road Racer.
Hey, where's Ryosuke?
He went home a long time ago.
We're the only ones still here.
It'll be dawn soon.
Let's go home.
They can't keep up with me
if I drive seriously?
They aren't so good.
There's somebody.
It's not from our team.
Is it an MR2 or a 180?
Fine.  You won't be in my mirror
after two more corners!
An Eight-Six?!
No fucking way!
My FD can't outrun an
obsolete Eight-Six?!
Am I having a bad dream or what?
Shit!
I'm number two in the Akagi Redsuns!
He doesn't know what's ahead?
After this slow right-hander,
there's a tight left corner.
If he doesn't slow down, he'll end up
at the bottom of the ravine.
As I thought.
He's going too fast.
He doesn't have enough room
to recover and slow down.
W...what the hell...?
Inertia drift?!
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
In the japanese Street Racing scene, cars
are referred to by their model names
Eight-Six (AE86): 1983 Toyota Trueno
In Europe Corolla GT - with fixed headlights,
in the US Corolla GT-S  (prod. ceased in 1987)
FD (FD3S): 1991 Mazda RX-7
S13 (S13): 1991 Nissan Silvia
(prod. ceased in 1993)
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
180 (S13): 1991 Nissan 180SX
(prod. ceased in 1998)
In Europe under the name 200SX
In the US under the name 240SX
MR2 (SW20): 1991 Toyota MR2
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
Keisuke thought Takumi's
Eight-Six (Hachi-Roku)
was an MR2 or 180 bacause
those are also cars with the
flip-up headlight design.
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
Papa: Older men sometimes
pay young girls to be with
them.
The girl usually refers
to the man as “Papa”.
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
Drift fans and Eight-Six owners,
sorry for the long wait!
Initial D has finally started!
How'd you like Takumi's Eight-Six chasing
around that super high performance...
...350HP FD, 1.6 liter, non-turbo,
using his super drift technique?
It was totally awesome, wasn't it?
Initial D is full of distinctive essences that
those who know cars well can truly enjoy!
Watch a hot race in
the next episode, too!
Next Time: ACT.2
Declaration of Revenge!  Howling Turbo
Don't miss it!