This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
W...what the hell?
I don't believe this.
Did I just see the ghost of a
Road Racer who died here?
His first counter-steer was a motion to
get the right angle for the left curve.
It was the perfect drift of a driver who
knows everything about Akina.
Keisuke, did you see that Eight-Six?
Yeah.
My pride is torn up.
My FD, with its mountain setup, was beaten
by a 10 year old Eight-Six junker.
What the hell is that Eight-Six?
Declaration of Revenge!  Howling Turbo
ACT.2
Yes, Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Hey, Takumi!  Takumi!
How much longer are you gonna sleep?
Get up!  You've got a phone call!
It's Itsuki, isn't it?
I don't know, hurry and
pick up the phone!
Hello, it's me.
Takumi, over here!
Were you surprised?
I was.
I thought it was Itsuki.
I thought it was about time
to restore our friendship.
Restore, you said?
But we weren't in a fight or anything.
You guys were talking about
cars at school yesterday.
Can you drive, Takumi?
Yeah, I just got a license.
Then let's go driving somewhere
during summer break.
You drive and I'll fix lunch.
Fine with me...
...but I only have a dorky one for work.
I don't mind. It at least has a
cassette deck, doesn't it?
I don't care what the car is.
I don't mind at all.
You don't?
It'll be fun.
I'm getting excited!
Why don't we drive a long way?
That's right!
The ocean would be nice.
Let's swim together, since it's summer.
No doubt, it's the Eight-Six.
I bet the fastest on Akina is
the tofu shop's Eight-Six.
Is this... the fastest machine
on the downhill?
It looks like it's an
ordinary Eight-Six.
An early Apex model,
except for the fog lights.
A car like this can't be faster
than the latest machines.
Something must be wrong
with me, searching for it.
Iketani...
Takumi?
What're you doing here?
Hey, is this your house?
Yeah.
What were you doing
in front of my house?
I had something to do, and...
I was just passing by.
Anyway, Takumi, you really don't
know anything about cars.
You said you didn't know about
the Eight-Six yesterday...
...but the car at your house
is an Eight-Six.
Wait a minute.
It's not an Eight-Six.
It says Trueno on the back.
You see, a Trueno is an Eight-Six.
The Levins and Truenos with the chassis
type AE86 are called Eight-Six.
Huh?
An Eight-Six at Takumi's house?!
Are you serious, Iketani?
Yeah, I'm serious.
Damn you, Takumi!
Why'd you keep it a secret?!
It couldn't be helped,
because I didn't know.
If it's a Trueno, why
don't you say Trueno?
You said "Eight-Six."
Ordinary people don't call them that.
Why you...
By the way, I have
something to discuss.
Can you borrow the Eight-Six
next Saturday?
Why?
It's obvious!
We'll go watch the gathering
of the Speedstars and Redsuns!
Since that incident yesterday,
I'm really into the Road Racer world!
Don't you want to see how the Takahashi
brothers, the fastest on Akagi, drive?
Not really...
Say what?!
How can you say that?!
Are you really my friend?!
I beg you to drive your
Eight-Six on Saturday.
Hey, guys, what're you doing?
You have a customer.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Welcome!
Installing brand new tires?
You've really spoiled yourself.
I've got to cut my time by
installing high grip tires.
I'll also change the brake pads.
Brakes are important on the downhill.
Are you going to run, Iketani?
I'll run on the downhill.
I'll tackle the downhill of Akina like hell.
Don't push yourself too hard.
One mistake'll kill you on the downhill.
I know.
I know, but I have to push it...
...for the locals' pride.
That Eight-Six didn't
show up today.
He isn't a Road Racer
from this area?
No.  He knew everything
about Mt. Akina.
I want to see it again,
and get revenge...
...or I won't be able
to calm down!
Come out, ghost of Akina!
I don't care about the Speedstars.
I'm here to face you!
That's just like the drift king,
Tsuchiya Keiichi!  I can't sit still!
He must be controlling it
using only acceleration.
Takumi, I wish we could soon
perform a drift like that!
Yeah.
Look at that drift!
It's awesome!
Yeah.
Takumi...
You only say "yeah, yeah!"
Do you really know what drift is?!
Yeah, I know what drift is.
Well then, explain what it is.
In the curve...
Don't say curve, it sounds so uncool.
Road Racers call them corners.
Well, in the corner...
...you steer like this to let the front tires go
outward so the car won't face the inside.
Gimme a break, Takumi!
If the front tires go outward,
you're experiencing understeering.
It shows your poor skill,
and it's totally uncool.
You let the rear go
outward when you drift.
You're strange.
You're incredible, Takumi.
Right.
You're the one who
doesn't know, Iketani.
When the car is drifting, it's supposed
to be understeered.
It was the advanced answer of those who
have mastered the four-wheel drift.
I'm impressed.
Here's a customer.
Let's get to work.
O...okay.
Welcome.
Welcome!
Takahashi Keisuke's FD?
High octane, fill it up.
Okay.
You're really devoted, sir.
Of course.
I thought I'd seen that S13.
It's from the Speedstars.
Can I ask you something?
You should know about it.
There's a ghost on Mt. Akina, isn't there?
A ghost of an extremely fast Eight-Six.
Man, does he want
to fly or something?
Please don't joke around with me, sir.
I was joking about
the ghost part...
...but it's about a black and
white panda Trueno...
The exterior looks like a normal Eight-Six,
but it's an incredible monster inside.
A local guy should know about
such an incredible car.
Well, it's okay.
If it's your secret weapon for Saturday,
I'm looking forward to it.
Tell the driver of the Eight-Six...
...that I won't let the same
guy defeat me twice.
I lost because I wasn't familiar with
the course and got careless.
Thank you!
Takahashi Keisuke lost...?
What does he mean?
I didn't know any
Eight-Six could do that.
It can't be...
But the one at Takumi's house
is also a panda Trueno.
Is what the manager said true?
The fastest on the downhill
is still that Eight-Six?
Okay, that does it for today.
Isn't it more than usual?
Hey, just don't spill it, okay?
I know.
You look as sleepy as usual, Takumi.
I'm sorry, but my face
is like this naturally.
Don't forget your Eight-Six
on next Saturday, okay?
I know.  You're so persistent, Itsuki.
I have to be persistent or I can't
clear my doubts about you.
I wish Saturday would come early!
I'm so excited!
Hey, since we hope
to be Road Racers...
...we want to be called the fastest
on Akina some day, right?
I don't really care either way.
Well, it's probably impossible,
even if you try...
...because you don't have a bit of talent, being
scared in the rear seat of Iketani's car.
But I'm different!
Well, it was a bit scary...
...but I could look at the sharp corners,
clenching my teeth.
Iketani must have thought that there
would be no hope for Takumi...
...but I have potential!
Takumi?
Takumi!
Takumi, hey wait!
Even if you're jealous of
my talent, you're too cold.
I'm not...
Say what?
Are you serious?
And Rumiko told my boyfriend
about it.  He's so mad.
I saw it.
You like that?
N...no!
It's a crime to make their skirts so
short without thinking anything.
The school should regulate that.
Lucky!
Takumi, good morning.
M...Mogi?
Oh, I have something to talk to you about.
Come with me.
Hurry.
W...what the hell?!
What's going on?!
What happened?
Well...
...I have something...
...I want to tell you.
What is it?
Well...I...
...bought a new bathing suit!
It's super cute!
Is that what you wanted to tell me?
Bingo.
Because I was so excited and I wanted
to tell somebody about it.
Wanna see it?
What color do you think it is?
You want to see it soon, don't you?
Well, I want to, but...
I'll let you see it as much as you
want when we go to the ocean.
Until then...
...just...look...forward...to...it.
What about this Sunday?
Are you free?
Yeah, I don't have to work.
That'll do.
Promise me, okay?
You can't break promises!
I don't like a person who breaks
promises or smokes.
Damn, it's so difficult.
The dull corners now appear to be
the scary and tight ones.
Those familiar corners challenge
me so differently!
It's no use.
Even if I push myself to the limit,
I can't shorten the time.
I thought if I depressed the accelerator
more, I could cut the time, but...
...it's not that easy.
Is this the best my technique can do?
There's no way I can compete with them!
Hello!  Excuse me!
Hello!
Excuse me!
I can hear you.
Wait a moment.
How may I help you?
Is he the Eight-Six driver who's
the fastest on Akina?
Is he the Road Racer who can
beat Takahashi Keisuke?
What do you want, sir?
I'll have a fried tofu.
Thanks.
What am I doing?
Well, I'm Iketani...
...and I'm with a team called
the Akina Speedstars.
I... heard a strange rumor that the
fastest on Mt. Akina's downhill...
...is an old guy from a tofu shop,
who drives an Eight-Six.
I don't know who said that,
but it's not me.
Please don't pretend
not to know!
Even if I searched
the entire city...
...I won't be able to find another tofu
shop man who drives an Eight-Six!
Here.  140 yen.
O...okay.
Okay, thanks.
Well, I'm in a complicated situation...
Would you hear me out?
Don't trouble me.
I'm working now.
You look bored!
No one else is here!
How rude, saying something directly
that should've been held back.
I'm sorry, but I'm desperate.
Actually, a team called the Akagi Redsuns
challenged us to a time attack.
There are some highly skilled guys with the
Redsuns, and we're no match for them.
I don't want to be defeated
as a local driver!
So, what do you want me to do?
Mr. Fujiwara, I want you to teach me
how to tackle Akina.
That's impossible.
Just a little is fine.
I'll be satisfied, even if it shortens
the time by a tenth of a second.
Please!
I know how you feel, but driving technique is
not something you can obtain in a few days.
You have to think over and over how you
can make the car run as you like...
...and keep on driving.
When I was actively driving,
I tackled Akina even in my dreams.
Technique isn't something to be taught,
you must acquire it yourself.
I'm sorry that I can't be of help to you.
Mr. Fujiwara, I'll visit you again.
Think it over and over
and keep on driving...
I'm trying, but I can't cut my time.
Why?!
Dammit. I can't figure it out,
no matter how hard I think!
I can't dodge him!
Please, escape to the inside!
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Tsuchiya Keiichi is an active racer
supervising this show.
He is well known as the "dori-kin"
or drifting king for his amazing
car drifting skills.
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
The bell sound in Takumi's
Eight-Six indicates he's over
100kmph (60mph approx.)
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
Okay, today's guest is Fujiwara Bunta, the stubborn
old guy from the Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Mr. Bunta, your philosophy says that
driving technique can't be taught...
...and must be learned
by oneself?
You sounded so cool,
and I really liked it.
Well, okay.
Then, could you tell us the highlights
of the next episode?
Wait until you see it.
Well, then look forward to
the next episode of Initial D!
Next Time: ACT.3
Downhill Specialist Arrives