This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
That was dangerous!
How dare you drive like that!
Hey, you...
Hang on!
Are you alright?
Sorry about my carelessness.
I'm sorry...really...
Hey, hold on, I'll call an ambulance!
Downhill Specialist Arrives
ACT.3
WHAT?!
Iketani had an accident?!
When?!
Last night he hit the guardrail
driving the downhill on Akina.
How is he?
Thank you very much.
His injury isn't too serious.
Just minor whiplash.
But he's really torn up about it.
His car was heavily damaged, too.
Then what about the race on Saturday?
It's hopeless...
Anyway, we have to find a substitute
for Iketani somehow.
Welcome...
Oh, Iketani...
Is it alright to be walking around?
Yeah, it's okay.
Where's my car?
In the back garage.
Nothing's been done yet.
We can't start until we get all the parts.
Excuse me.
I want fried tofu.
Coming.
Thanks...
You had an accident?
Yeah...
There isn't much time till the race.
What're you going to do?
I came to ask you a favor
about that, Mr. Fujiwara.
Favor?
Yes.
Can you drive in the race instead
of me the day after tomorrow?
I beg you, Mr. Fujiwara!
My neck...
Don't die.
You can understand how
a Road Racer feels, right?
The local drivers can't be defeated!
Hey, even if I do, I'd just be an
old man in the wrong place.
I... grew up driving Akina...
...so I can tell that those Redsuns guys are looking
down on all of Akina's Road Racers.
That's why I'm so frustrated!
I want to show them there's a skilled
Road Racer on Akina!
Mr. Fujiwara, you can
do that because...
...you've defeated Takahashi,
the fastest of Akagi, once already.
Please, Mr. Fujiwara!
What is it?
We're closed for today.
Don't be so rigid.
Fill it up with high octane.
How cheeky...
High octane for the Eight-Six,
you said?
It was you who told Iketani
that ridiculous rumor.
Yeah, I didn't mean to tell a lie.
So, what about it...?
He came over today with bandages
and neck brace on.
He asked me to drive instead of him.
I can't hate that kind of guy, though.
If you don't, then why not drive instead?
Iketani's a nice guy.
Forget it.
It's like an adult poking
his nose in a kids' fight.
That's not my style.
Then why don't you send
a kid to a kids' fight?
Are you talking about Takumi?
Yeah.
He's really good, isn't he?
Not yet...
...but if it's Akina's downhill, he's good
enough not to lose to anyone.
Well, he can't defeat me, though.
Here comes your fighting instinct.
I wonder what made him so stubborn.
Even if he's asked, he's not the kind
who'll accept so easily and drive...
Well, I'll come up with a plan for the
sake of the bandaged Iketani.
Don't break your promise!
I hate people who smoke
and break promises.
Let me use the car on Sunday, okay?
Sunday...?
You can't.
Why not?
I'll do the delivery in the
morning as usual.
That's not it.
I have a meeting of the Society of Commerce
on Sunday, so I need it.
Really?
This is bad.
I really need the car this Sunday.
It must be a girl.
None of your business.
Don't be so stubborn,
and let me use it...
...because the car isn't
that great for your use.
I'll go without asking, okay?
The car won't run
without a key.
I'll put it on a string and
wear it around my neck.
That's mean!
If you're so desperate,
I can consider it.
Really?
But I have one condition.
Condition?
Saturday night, beat the pants off a smartass
kid who claims to be the fastest on Akagi...
...on Akina's downhill.
H...how come?
Then I'll let you use the car.
Plus, you get a full tank of gas.
Full tank of gas...?
Full tank of gas...
That's so irresistible...
...'cause I'm almost broke.
What're you going to do?
L...let me think about
it for a while.
Fine, think as much as you want.
Takahashi
I'm coming in.
Oh, Keisuke, good timing.
I wanted to ask you something.
What is it, Brother?
It's about the Eight-Six
you saw on Akina.
Can you logically explain
why it was so fast?
Oh, gimme a break.
I'm not good at that kind
of thing like you are.
Like I always say, the most important
thing in driving technique is "this."
You can figure out anything
by driving behind your opponent.
From the opponent's habits and weaknesses,
to how well the suspension is set up.
Your analysis skill is
almost monstrous.
To me, you're incredible because you
can keep up with me without thinking.
If you can apply theories to
your driving skill, it's ideal.
I was defeated the other day because
of unfamiliarity and carelessness.
I've never had such
a disgrace before.
The inside of that Eight-Six
must be monstrous.
Monstrous, huh?
I'm getting interested.
Maybe I should watch
the race tomorrow.
Takumi!
Saturday has finally come!
So what?
What do you mean, "So what?"
The race!
The race against the Akagi Redsuns!
You promised me you'd borrow the Eight-Six
and we'd go see it together.
Oh, speaking of which...
Things are getting complicated.
What is it?
Don't even say that you can't go.
Well, it's not that, but...
If you cancel, I won't be seeing you anymore,
no matter what the reason is.
I've kept counting the
days to go until today.
I know...
Excuse me.
I want fried tofu.
Oh, you again.
You're so persistent.
Mr. Fujiwara, please come
to the race today!
I might be able to go.
I said, I might be able to go to
tonight's race on Mt. Akina.
Really?!
My neck...
Hey, are you alright?
Are you really coming?
I can't say it's definite...
...but the chance is fifty-fifty.
When it's gonna start?
The friendship rally
begins at 9:00...
...and the time attack
begins at 10:00.
Ten o'clock...
If the Eight-Six doesn't appear
by ten, give up on me.
Then you'll have to do
something yourself.
I'll be waiting, Mr. Fujiwara.
I believe that you'll definitely come.
I'm not sure.
I said fifty percent.
No, you've already decided to come.
I'll be waiting for you, along with
all the team members.
Well then, Mr. Fujiwara, I'll be waiting
at Akina's peak at 10:00.
I can't help myself when it comes
to an eager guy like him.
If Takumi refuses,
should I drive myself...?
Boy, I'm getting excited.
Something good happened?
You're acting a little different than usual.
Am I?
I'm always like this.
You look happy for some reason.
Actually, I'm going to the beach
with my friend tomorrow.
I'm really looking
forward to it.
Friend, you mean a guy?
No!  It's a girl of course.
If that's what it is, I can buy you a new
bathing suit at the department store.
It's alright.
I bought myself one already.
I don't need two.
I want to see you in the bathing suit.
That's strange.
You've seen everything.
You're a pervert.
I wonder if it'll be sunny tomorrow.
Don't ask such a dumb question.
It'll be sunny all over the country.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to the beach.
Beach?
SAY WHAT?!
I'm so envious!
I wanna go to the beach, too!
Don't tell me...
...YOU'RE GOING WITH A GIRL!
IS A GITL GOING WITH YOU?!
Yeah.
WHO IS IT?!
Do I know her?!
Is she cute?!
Does she have big boobs?!
Really cute.
Mogi Natsuki...?
Yeah.
You're so cruel, going ahead of me.
Sorry, but the situation didn't
give me a chance to ask.
Some other time, okay?
Don't cry.
What's gonna happen during the race today?
I heard that the Redsuns have won
every race they've challenged.
The outcome is so obvious.
The Akina team will be totally nailed.
But the fastest in Gunma aren't the Redsuns...
...but us, the Night Kids of Myogi.
Takeshi, it's about time.
Alright, let's go.
The R32 is a pure thoroughbred,
born to run fast.
It'll never be defeated by the
rotary potatoes of Akagi.
Incredible.
There's gonna be a little
party on the mountain.
The story about the race
between Iketani's team...
...and the fastest team on Akagi,
has been talked about everywhere.
I wonder which side's gonna win.
Well, Takumi's Eight-Six
is Bunta's car as well...
...so it won't be defeated.
I'm getting excited
after such a long time.
There're so many people!
I've never seen such big
galleries on Akina before.
The Redsuns drew them here
to show off their speed.
It'll be so disgraceful if we lose.
By the way, about the Eight-Six
you talked about earlier...
Is that really true, Iketani?
Yeah.
It's so hard for me to believe
in that Eight-Six.
I heard that Takahashi's FD3S is moderately
tuned for the mountain path.
Still, they say it produces at least 350 HP.
It's got so much power.
Even if it's downhill, the Eight-Six
will be no match for it!
Iketani, did you get hit
somewhere really bad?
Even if it's the Eight-Six,
it's not a normal Eight-Six.
Takahashi Keisuke himself said that it
looked like a normal panda Trueno...
...but it's a monster machine
under the skin.
Trust me.  He'll come for us.
If he doesn't...?
The galleries are so big...
...and I don't want them to say
the Speedstars ran away.
In that case...
In that case...?
Kenji, for the sake of the team,
you drive like hell to win!
Y...you must be kidding...
Many cars are coming up.
I hear the rotary sound also!
The Redsuns!
There they are!
They've finally arrived.
The Takahashi brothers are incredibly popular.
They're the sons of a doctor who
runs a big clinic in Takasaki.
We can't compete with the rich.
Driving skill depends on how much
gas and tires are wasted.
What the hell is Takumi doing?!
The race is gonna begin!
Even though I made sure,
that stupid Takumi...!
Idiot, jerk!
You're not my friend!
Ouch!
I won't be able to make it in time.
I'd better go on my scooter.
Let's start the time attack
at 10:00 as planned.
If it's late, there'll be no other
traffic, making it easier.
We'll use radios at the start
and finish to time them.
We'll put officials at the blind corners, so
the drivers can go as fast as they want.
If there's oncoming traffic, we'll use
lights to signal the drivers.
I see.
They seem so experienced.
Yeah, I guess they do time
attacks in many places.
Well then, it's gonna be a free run
till 10:00, so let's have fun.
The galleries are packed.
The Eight-Six isn't here.
What's going on?
Are they going to hide their secret
weapon until the last moment?
It's the bottom of the ninth, one out,
with the bases loaded.
What is it?
Have you decided to go?
I don't feel like it though...
Why not? Don't you have
the confidence to win?
If you drive like you always do,
you won't lose.
There it is!
It's Keisuke's FD3S!
Incredible!
The entry speed was so fast!
That's Takahashi Ryosuke this time!
Watch out!  Move!
Just like Takahashi Ryosuke.
His skill is the real thing.
Incredible! They don't
hit at that distance?
That's the famous parallel drift!
It's a difficult one to approach.
It can't be done without the skill to control
your speed and line during a drift.
But that's only a performance.
They drive differently when they race.
The ghost of Akina hasn't arrived.
You're my only opponent.
Come out, Eight-Six!
Aren't you giving me a paper cup?
You don't need one, because
you're not carrying tofu.
It's not for a delivery, so have fun.
Full tank of gas.
Don't forget.
I know.
I'm going then.
Okay.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
R32: 1992 Nissan Skyline GT-R
One of the
fastest
japanese
production
cars.
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
Today's guest is famous for aggressive
driving, from the Redsuns, Takahashi...
Give that to me!
Show yourself, ghost of Akina!
Don't tell me you're scared
and ran away?!
Do you think you can win this time?
Shut up!  There's no doubt!
I'll get revenge no matter what!
Next time on Initial D, finally,
"The Battle Begins."
Which will win in the high tension battle
between the Eight-Six and FD?
Next Time: ACT.4
The Battle Begins!
Don't miss it.