This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
Show yourself, ghost of Akina!
ACT.4 The Battle Begins!
How's the booster pressure?
It's okay.
Don't forget to check the tire pressure.
Okay.
We'll win today's race.
It's a piece of cake.
Shut up and keep on working.
Geez...
Hey, hand me that cross wrench.
What're they doing?
Changing the tires of the FD.
They seem to have a few sets in the van.
Changing the tires according
to the situation?
They're serious.
Dammit.
It's ready anytime, Keisuke.
Arigato.
Hey, isn't it 10:00 yet?
It's still 9:40.
Shit.
Brother, that Eight-Six
hasn't showed up yet.
I'm getting pissed.
I was sure it would represent Akina.
My prediction was wrong.
It's such a turn off.
Unless I humiliate them by winning
the time attack by a big margin...
...I can't ease my anger.
Iketani, it's almost time.
Yeah, I know.
Who's that?
Senpai!
Iketani!
Itsuki...
W...what about the time attack?
It's about to start.
Great, I made it in time.
Who's gonna run for the Speedstars?
Kenji, you'd better prepare yourself.
You're representing the team?
Good luck, I'm with you!
This is the starting point.
Are you ready?
This is the finish.
Everyone's in position.
We can begin any time.
Okay.
You heard that.
Shall we begin?
So he didn't come after all...
I'm counting on you, Kenji.
Okay...
Gimme a break.
How can you be my opponent?
Kenji, you don't look good.
You're sweating a lot.
It's painful looking at you.
Even if you say so...
Guts!  Put your guts into it!
Alright, let's begin the countdown!
Ten seconds...
Hold a second!
This is the finish line!
A car just passed by.
It could interfere...
Should we wait until it reaches the peak?
This is a public street.  There might
as well be oncoming traffic.
Don't worry, let's begin!
Okay.
Wait.  Can you ask him what
kind of car it was?
Can you tell what kind of car it was?
Let me see...
It's got retractable lights.
It's probably an Eight-Six Trueno.
Give it to me.
What color was that Eight-Six?
Why're you asking me such things?
White and black.
A panda Trueno.
He's here!
Here comes my target.
What do I do?
Continue counting down?
Stop counting down, and wait
until the Eight-Six arrives.
The One-Eighty beside me
isn't my true opponent.
Right?
Yeah, you're right.
Kenji, you can relax.
I'm saved.
Your eyes are watery.
Same as yours.
That old man has come to save the
pride of Akina's Road Racers.
That's more than enough.
It doesn't matter if we win or lose.
What the hell...?
I feel awkward.
People are standing at every corner.
What're they doing?
I've come to a strange place...
What the heck...
...if I win, the tank will be full, and I can
go to the beach without hesitation.
What's wrong, Takeshi?
He's good.
The rear of the car, just leaving
the corner, looked very steady.
Didn't you see?
Even if you say so...
It looked like any other ordinary Eight-Six.
Cars driven by those who can control
their car like their hands and legs...
...give off auras.
A strong aura surrounds Takahashi
Ryosuke's driving.
It's still weak for his brother, Keisuke.
But that Eight-Six had a strong aura.
If he's representing Akina, we can't
predict which one's gonna win.
Almost.  He's really here!
The fastest on Akina's downhill.
A legendary super technician.
We can show the Takahashi brothers
the true potential of Akina!
Come on, Eight-Six...
I'm looking forward to seeing
what kind of driver he is.
I haven't felt such anticipation in a long time.
He put things off till the last minute.
But that trick won't work on me.
Let me watch carefully.
There it is!
Clear the street!
Guide it to the starting line!
What's that car for?
They were waiting for that car?
But that's only an Eight-Six.
Shit.  Where did all these people come from?
Fujiwara Tofu Shop (Private Vehicle)
Excuse me...
Could that Eight-Six be...?
Takumi...?
T...that's...
So he's the one.
Takumi!
What's going on?
What happened to your father?
I came here because Dad told me to.
Even if the car's here, it won't do anything
unless your father is, too!
What should we do, Iketani?
This wasn't supposed to happen.
I shouldn't have come after all.
That shitty old man pisses me off.
Takumi, didn't your father say
anything besides that?
Dad only told me to go to the mountain peak
and defeat the FD on Akina's downhill.
Your father told you to drive?
Yeah.
Can you defeat...
...Takahashi Keisuke?
I won't know unless I try...
...but I defeated him once.
Defeated him once...?
He'll give me a full tank
of gas if I win.
So, if you let me try, I'll win,
no matter what.
Excuse me...
Umm, excuse me, excuse me.
Takumi, you complete moron!
Ouch!
What's wrong with you?
Takumi, how can you be so stupid?
I'm so embarrassed just looking at you!
Just move the car, and don't interfere
with the time attack!
Get in the Eight-Six...
Hold on a sec, Itsuki.
Iketani, I'm very sorry!
He's so dumb, and he doesn't
know anything!
Please forgive him!
Takumi, your father isn't the only
one delivering tofu, right?
You do too, don't you?
For the past five years,
I've been the only one.
For the past five years?
I finally get it, Takumi.
Okay, you'll drive the time
attack on the downhill.
W...what're you saying, Iketani?
If an amateur like Takumi pushes
too hard on Akina's downhill...
...he'll lose control
and die instantly!
Don't worry, just go to
the corner and watch.
I'm glad you're here, Takumi.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Dammit, I'm tired of waiting.
He's so young.
Your name?
Fujiwara Takumi.
I'll remember that.
I'm Takahashi Keisuke.
I won't make the same mistake twice.
Is it alright?
A race between an Eight-Six
and an FD is so unfair.
Its power is totally outclassed, and the FD is
Japan's best cornering machine.
The Eight-Six is no match for it on
the straightaways or corners.
All I can do is believe.
I'm starting the countdown.
Okay.
Ten seconds to start!
Nine...
...eight...
...seven...
...six...
...five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one...
Go!
Takahashi Keisuke's FD is so fast!
350 horsepower isn't just for show,
and his clutch meet was perfect.
This won't be a race.
The full acceleration of the Eight-Six
almost looked like it wasn't moving.
Takumi...
Judging from the start dash, that Eight-Six
has 150 horsepower at most.
It's far from the monster Keisuke says it is.
The reason why the shift timing is quick...
...is because it has a close transmission,
just like a rally car.
That suits Akina's tight
hairpin curves perfectly.
Even so, I can't find any factor for that
Eight-Six to defeat Keisuke's FD.
The monster isn't the car.
Could it be the driver?
I won't hold back.
It's not my style to go full out on the straightaway,
but this is a time attack...
I won't see the Eight-Six in
my rear view mirror again.
What the hell...?
This is the first corner.
That Eight-Six took an incredible line!
It was 5 cm from the guardrail!
I've never seen any car
that turns so fast!
What?!
He's gaining on me.
His car is getting closer!
No, it's not.
Something so absurd can't happen.
A...are you serious?
Takumi's father is a great Road Racer?
Yeah.
I've seen him a few times...
He looked like an ordinary tofu shop guy.
You can't judge a person by appearances.
The manager told me that he's still
the fastest on Akina's downhill.
Anyway, that old man sent
Takumi here instead...
...so we have to believe in him.
Yeah, it's much better than me driving.
But no matter how fast his
dad is, if it's Takumi...
Actually, it seems that Takumi has
defeated Takahashi Keisuke once.
Takumi has defeated Takahashi Keisuke?!
You must be kidding!
I can't believe it.
That stupid Takumi actually did?
He didn't even know what Eight-Six meant.
W...what's going on with that Eight-Six?!
It entered the corner at incredible
speed while skidding the rear...
...and exited at very high speed!
I don't know if it lost control!
It's just so exciting to watch!
He caught me!
What's going on?
It's driving me crazy!
Shit!
Initial acceleration in second gear is almost
the same, but he can stretch it longer.
The gap widens on the straightaway.
This is from the straightaway in front of the
skating rink!  They've just passed us!
Keisuke is being pushed!
Akina's Eight-Six is damned fast!
Holy shit!
I've never seen anyone charging
on Keisuke's FD so close!
I'm getting goose bumps.
He's pulled away on the long
straightaway again...
...but the hairpins are coming up,
so he might be in trouble.
Did you hear, Ryosuke?
We've made a misjudgement.
We didn't expect Akina to have
such a skilled driver.
Incredible entry!
That Eight-Six performed an entry
oriented kamikaze drive!
He lacks any fear of the downhill?!
I'm faster on the straightaway,
but he's still charging in.
He's better at cornering work.
It's a Road Racer's worst disgrace to
be tailed by an underpowered car.
I won't accept that, no matter what!
That shitty old man won't call it
a win unless I overtake that car.
It can't be helped, because the
prize is a full tank of gas.
The attack point is the
five hairpin curves ahead.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
Finally, the race has begun, Takumi!
Yeah.
Did you practice for this battle?
Not really.
It's just like delivering tofu.
So your daily work is effective!
That's about right.
Do you have any secret plan
to overtake the FD?
It's not really a secret, but...
You have to win to use the Eight-Six with a
full tank of gas to date Natsuki, don't you?
Next Time: ACT.5
End of the Dogfight!
Yeah.
Next time on Initial D...
...something's gonna happen
in the five hairpins.
Don't miss it!