This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our law.
That's our low!
He caught me!
What's going on?
It's driving me crazy!
This is from the straightaway in front of the
skating rink!  They've just passed us!
Keisuke is being pushed!
Akina's Eight-Six is damned fast!
I've never seen anyone charging
on Keisuke's FD so close!
I'm getting goose bumps.
Incredible entry!
That Eight-Six performed an incredible
entry oriented kamikaze drive!
That shitty old man won't call it
a win unless I overtake that car.
It can't be helped, because the
prize is a full tank of gas.
The attack point is the
five hairpin curves ahead.
End of the Dogfight!
ACT.5
Shit!
What's happening?
It feels like my FD is slower than usual.
Did the secondary turbine stop?
This is the peak.
Can you hear me?
Ryosuke?
They'll pass through the five hairpins soon.
I want your live report.
Make it as detailed as possible.
Okay.
They're just around the corner.
I can hear the squealing sounds.
They'll pass by soon.
Here comes Keisuke's FD, and
the Eight-Six is following!
There's no gap between them!
That Eight-Six is incredible!
It's performing perfect braking drifts!
Keisuke's turn-in is slower!
He's also good at exiting!
It's so close to the guardrail!
They're entering the second hairpin!
There's no gap at all!
They're even at the exit!
The FD is moving to the outside,
and the Eight-Six is...
He's not slowing down for the hairpin?!
What the hell is he thinking?!
The Eight-Six is heading for the
hairpin at incredible speed!
Did his brakes go out?
What the hell was that...?
Keisuke was passed so easily on the inside!
That's ridiculous!
That doesn't tell us anything!
Explain what happened!
Well...even though we saw it...
You know how a car can't turn beyond
its tires' grip speed, right?
But the Eight-Six, even though it was
on a disadvantageous inside line...
...turned strangely, just like
it was on a roller coaster.
I don't understand what happened!
I know what the Eight-Six did.
It's so silly, but no one else could do it.
And it can only happen on Akina.
I've found an incredible idiot.
I'm looking forward to this.
The one who will defeat the
downhill specialist of Akina...
...will be me, Nakazato Takeshi
of the Myogi Night kids.
This is the finish line, I can hear their engines.
They'll be here soon!
Here they come!
Which one...?!
It's the Eight-Six!
My god, what happened?!
Keisuke's FD just showed up, but he's
too far behind to close the gap!
The Eight-Six is way ahead!
Shit!
How could my FD be defeated
by an Eight-Six?
How is it possible?
A 350 horsepower car was outrun
by a crappy Eight-Six?!
They've crossed the finish line!
Keisuke lost!
He did it!
Am I still having a bad dream?
I was defeated by the Eight-Six,
not once but twice?!
That stupid Takumi won!
Incredible... incredible.
I'm so thrilled.
My head is spinning.
He did it.
Yeah.
Iketani, don't cry, you idiot.
I'm so impressed.
Let's ask him to teach us things
like drift control and line taking.
Put a Speedstars sticker on
his car without telling him!
Okay, I'll do that!
I'll leave that to you then.
We were totally defeated.
We have to admit that.
What about the uphill time attack, Ryosuke?
It's meaningless, even if
we win on the uphill.
By tomorrow...
...everyone will know that the Akina Eight-Six
defeated the undefeated Redsuns.
We'll have our revenge with my FC soon.
A full tank of gas...
You promised.
You promised, okay?
So he won.
I knew he would before he left.
The right side is where the Eight-Six passed me.
I can't understand why the Eight-Six turned
faster on the inside edge than my FD.
It scares me every time I recall.
Maybe he really is a ghost.
Keisuke, tell me what happened.
Did you notice anything strange?
Come to think of it, I heard
a strange scraping sound.
Strange sound...?
I see.  I got it.
I can tell you why you were defeated.
He used this.
The gutter?
Yes.
He dropped his inner tires into the gutter on
purpose, to withstand the centrifugal force.
That way, it's theoretically possible to obtain
cornering force which exceeds tire grip.
It's such a plain, simple,
and silly idea...
...but you just can't do it on the
spur of the moment.
He's probably done it many times.
He must push himself to the limit on Akina.
SHIT!
Well, I like the mountain passes because
things like this can happen.
After such a long time, I finally feel like I've
found a target that truly excites me.
Let's suspend the match next week.
We can't step up unless we record
a perfect win on Akina.
I'll defeat the Eight-Six!
Bunta, are you there?
It's me.
So hot.
Oh, Yuichi.
Good timing.
I have a local commerce meeting now.
Why don't you give me a ride?
Say what?  Are you using me
as a taxi driver?
I heard Takumi was incredible.
That's all that Iketani and the others
can talk about this morning.
He's not really that great.
The skill level of kids these
days isn't very high, is it.
He doesn't even like driving a car.
Really?
I can't believe it since he has such skill.
To him, driving a car means nothing
but helping the shop.
He's had to do it since middle school, so
he doesn't feel any sense of enjoyment.
I see.
He's uninterested, or should I say bored.
But I think he felt something after the
race on Akina's downhill yesterday.
Come to think of it,
the Eight-Six was gone.
Where is Takumi?
I'm not sure, but he seemed
excited and left home early.
It's cold!
Takumi, you're good at driving.
Really?
I usually get sick in cars...
...so I brought some medicine with me.
But thanks to your driving,
I didn't feel sick.
This is the first time I've been in a car
so long without getting sick.
Do you ride in cars that often?
N...not that often...
...like when the whole family takes
a trip in my father's car.
Strange girl.
I just drove like I do to keep
the water from spilling.
I felt strange yesterday.
I noticed as I was rapidly closing
in on the car ahead of me...
...I was getting excited.
I've never felt that
driving was very fun.
Even today, it's fun to drive with
Mogi in the passenger seat.
Cars are pretty interesting.
Hey, Takumi.
Hey, hey!
You were thinking about something.
You weren't paying attention.
You're so mean.
How can you leave such a cute girl
alone and go into your own world?
Sorry.  What were we talking about?
I asked you if you have
some girl you like.
Not really.
I do have someone I'm interested
in a little, though.
What about you?
I have...
...someone I'm interested in a little, too.
What do you mean?
Don't copy what I say.
Man, I don't know how many times
I was asked the same question.
"Who was in that Eight-Six?"
I was asked so many times, too.
He defeated Takahashi Keisuke,
so he might as well be famous.
I created hype by saying that it was
the Speedstars' secret weapon.
I have to get Takumi to join the
Speedstars or I'll look bad.
Senpai, leave that to me!
I'm Takumi's best friend.
He'll listen to me.
Are you sure, Itsuki?
Don't worry.
I know his weaknesses, too.
Could you let me join the Speedstars, too?
If Takumi does, then I'll let you in, too.
Right?
Y...yeah.
Lucky!  What a great deal!
But what'll you do without a car?
Thanks for asking!  I've decided.
Oh, you finally saved up enough money?
I'll make my dad a guarantor, and
get a loan to buy an Eight-Six!
Takumi has a panda Trueno, so
I'll find a red or black Levin...
And someday, we'll be called the
fastest Eight-Six pair on Akina.
But, Itsuki...
...Takumi's Eight-Six isn't normal.
Right.  It was faster than the 350 HP FD.
It must be heavily tuned.
I'd like to take a look at its engine someday.
I'd like to ride with him when he attacks
Akina's downhill at full speed.
How about you?
Yeah!
I wanna ride, too!
I'll reach an untouched zone
I can't even imagine.
It must be greater than
any roller coaster.
Damn that Takumi!
Wait a minute, Takumi.
Excuse me, but would you take a picture?
Sure.
Why're you taking a picture?
We came so far.
It's for our souvenir.
Smile, smile.
Ready?
Sorry, one more picture.
One more picture, please.
That's enough.
It's not.
That white FC...
It's Takahashi Ryosuke.
There goes the Redsuns number one driver.
Why's he here?
To avenge his brother.
What else?
It's right after yesterday's match.
He must be pretty frustrated because
that Eight-Six took all the fame.
An unfamiliar 32, isn't it?
That black 32 has a menacing presence.
Who's in it?
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
Note: the Trueno
and the Levin
share the same
AE86 chassis.
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
Damn, that Takumi is a traitor!
You look so angry, Itsuki.
He left his best friend behind,
and went to the beach with Mogi!
You wanted to see Natsuki in
her bathing suit, didn't you?
Damn right!
Takumi must've done things like
this and things like that...
...or even everything!
Next time on Initial D,
the signs of a new battle.
Next Time: ACT.6
A New Challenger
Don't miss it!