This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
A car with good straightaway
speed is following me.
Why don't I wait for him?
An R32 GT-R?
Let me see how good it runs.
Fine with me, that's what I want.
A New Challenger
ACT.6
Is this place alright?
I'm fine.  My house is just around the corner.
You said this car is dorky, but I like it.
It's lively, small and cute.
What's it called?
Trueno.
A Trueno...
Let me ride in the Trueno again.
It was fun today, Takumi.
Bye-bye.  I'll call you again.
Cute, she said.
What do you think?
I can keep up with Takahashi Ryosuke.
The GT-R is unbeatable after all.
No matter how good the driver is,
I guess that's the best a dated FC can do.
I'm Takahashi Ryosuke,
a member of the Redsuns.
I know.
I'm Nakazato Takeshi.
I'm with the team in Myogi
called the Night Kids.
Nakazato Takeshi of
the Night Kids...?
The fastest downhill Road Racer on Myogi.
I'm honored to be known by a superstar
like Takahashi Ryosuke.
But the Night Kids' Nakazato I heard of...
...was driving an S13.
Well, whatever.
And what is a Road Racer
from Myogi doing on Akina?
Hey, come on.
What about you?
You're from Akagi, and I know we're
here for the same reason.
I came here to see the
Eight-Six I saw yesterday.
A 32 driver is going to
challenge the Eight-Six?
With a 32 tuned to 380 HP?
How...?
I can tell by the exhaust sound on
the straightaway and power.
But the outcome's pretty obvious.
The Eight-Six is no match
for the 32 on the uphill...
...and you can't defeat the Eight-Six
with your 32 on the downhill.
Say what?
My 32 can't beat the
Eight-Six on the downhill?
Don't be offended.  I'm just
telling you my opinion.
You sound pathetic.
You don't have to be so hesitant just
because your brother was defeated.
It's only an Eight-Six!
You'll find out if you race him...
...that only I can defeat him.
Don't mess with me.  Having
said that, I won't back down.
I'll defeat the Eight-Six, and
make you eat your words!
Your confidence won't last long!
Don't forget about Nakazato of Myogi!
You'll learn that the rotary
is no match for the 32!
...was driving an S13.
That's right, I changed at that moment.
Damn, I can't pass him,
no matter how hard I try!
Even if I close in on the corner,
he pulls away on the straightaway.
My technique as a Road Racer is better!
Damn, will I lose it?
I can't keep up with
a 32 with this car?
The best of Myogi can't defeat
a 32, which doesn't even drift?!
A car has its limits.
No matter how good the driver is,
it won't run beyond its capabilities...
...even if it's the Eight-Six.
Good morning.
Good morning!
Yo.
Here, Iketani.
What's that?
Fried tofu.
We had some left from yesterday,
so Dad told me to give it to you.
I see.
I'll put it in the fridge.
He's concerned about me.
By the way, Takumi...
Is it true that you've been delivering tofu to
the hotel by Akina Lake for five years?
Yeah.
You're so secretive.
You could've told me.
I couldn't talk about it openly.
I would've gotten in trouble.
T...that's true.
We were only middle school
freshmen five years ago.
So you've been driving
longer than me.
Every day on Akina, whether it's raining
or snowing, since middle school.
It was early morning,
so nobody saw me...
That's not what I'm talking about...
...but weren't you scared of those corners?
I was scared in the beginning...
...but my fear was gone after six months or so.
As I picked up the speed, the tires
would naturally start skidding...
...and it took me another six months
until I could skid and stop as I like.
So you mastered the downhill
in only a year?!
When you do it everyday,
you get used to skidding.
It was boring... so I tried to get as close
as I could to the guardrails.
Ordinary people don't do
such dangerous things!
I never thought it was dangerous...
...and when I'm in a good mood,
I can get as close as 1 cm.
One centimeter...?!
It's really boring work unless
I find something interesting to do.
I've never thought about improving
my driving techniques.
It's tiring, and I just wanna
get home as fast as I can...
...so I drive as fast as possible on the
way home since I'm not carrying tofu.
Takumi, can I ask you something?
How do you drive when you carry tofu?
If you drive too rough, you'll
damage the tofu, won't you?
I can't drive that fast on the way up.
Dad puts water in a paper cup,
and I put it in the cup holder.
If I don't spill the water, I won't damage
the tofu, even if I drive fast.
It's pretty difficult.
In the beginning, I spilled a lot
even when I drove slowly.
Makes sense.
Brakes, steering wheel,
gears and the gas pedal...
If I'm too rough with any of those,
I spill the water.
Dad told me to rotate
the water in the cup.
Rotate the water in the cup...?
I think it's got something to
do with surface tension.
The water rotates extremely
close to the edge of the cup.
I rotate the water in every
curve when climbing.
It took me a while to drift
without spilling the water.
Drift without spilling it?!
Can you do that?
Don't lie to us, Takumi!
You're just joking, right?!
The most important factor in
driving is shifting the weight.
The drift king, Tsuchiya Keiichi,
said the same thing.
In order not to spill the water in the cup, he had
to learn extremely delicate weight shifting.
Especially if it's drift...
No one can do that!
I'm not lying.
Just because you defeated Takahashi
Keisuke, don't get overconfident!
As far as I'm concerned...
A customer.
Welcome.
High octane.  Yes, sir.
He's incredible, Bunta.  He'll go beyond
being a mountain Road Racer.
Thank you very much.
Takumi, I want to ask you a favor.
Can you give me a ride,
and drive hard on Akina?
You're going to use the car
at this time of night?
I can't, can I.
It's okay, 'cause it's not very important.
I don't mind.
Are you sure?
Don't you need the car to go
to a meeting or something?
You'd better think about it some more.
What's the matter?  You sound like you
WANT me to have something to do.
It's not that, but...
Then go ahead and use it, but come
pick me up at the meeting place.
So you do have a meeting.
I'm getting really excited.
It's like riding one of those scream
machines in a theme park.
Damn, I'm so envious.
I don't think it'll be that fun.
I'm ready, Iketani.
Okay, Takumi.
Push it to the limit.
Move away, guys.
It makes a wonderful sound...
You can never hear that from a turbo.
Here comes the first corner.
I'd better pay close attention to see the
difference, and steal his technique.
H...hey.
Hey!
Takumi, the brakes!
How...how's he controlling the
car in this situation?!
What's going on?
Is this really a car?
Incredible.
It's ringing at this point?
That means he's already going
beyond 100 km/h?!
The next corner is coming up!
Hey, the Eight-Six is coming back.
I wonder why.  It's too soon if he went
to the base of the mountain.
He passed out.
Takumi...
...how many corners?
T...three...?
I witnessed...
...the echoing death cry on the frightening
Mt. Akina downhill...
...as Iketani in the third corner...
...passed out!
I guess he's for real.
Manager, why're you here?
Well, I was a little curious.
I guess I'm out of place.
Please, enjoy.
I've heard of him.
Nakazato of the Night Kids
is unbeatable on Myogi.
I don't trust the skill of 32 drivers.
Only the car is fast.
Is that so?
You don't think so, Brother?
Here comes Keisuke's hatred of the 32.
But, Ryosuke...
...I don't think it's a good idea for
Nakazato to go ahead of us.
If the Night Kids defeat the Eight-Six
we couldn't defeat...
...people will start thinking our skills
are less than the Night Kids.
That's how a rumor spreads, and I think
that's Nakazato's intention.
I don't think we have to worry.
Nobody in the Night Kids can
defeat that Eight-Six.
As long as they race on Akina's downhill,
no one can defeat him.
Nobody but my brother can defeat him.
That Eight-Six is so good and fast.
I don't get it.
Why can't the latest high powered
car defeat the Eight-Six?
Sometimes, having too much
power is a disadvantage.
The turbo power is a welcome
aid on the straightaway...
...but it disturbs the control of
the car when exiting a corner.
It's like a double-edged sword.
In the case of the Eight-Six...
...once the line is determined, it can
go fast as the driver demands.
In a technical course, where
the straightaways are short...
...an underpowered car can
run at its full potential.
So the turbo power of Keisuke's
car worked negatively...?
On Akina's downhill...
...the total time for using my 350 HP
maximum was very limited.
As soon as it boosted
to max, I had to brake.
It was really frustrating.
That's the characteristic of the FR, which only
uses the rear tires to transmit the power.
Hey, wait.
What about a 4WD like the 32?
With ATTESA E-TS system, which provides
stable traction during acceleration...
...it can use the full potential
of its turbo power, can't it?
Nakazato might defeat the
Eight-Six with his 32.
Thank you very much!
Welcome!
But I feel strange.
The way I look at you is different.
What do you mean?
Why don't you have another bean jam bun?
When you eat a bun like that,
you look like your usual self.
You're just a sleepy headed moron.
Don't call me a moron.
But...
Once you sit in the driver seat of the Eight-Six
and go off into the night on Akina...
Bang, squeal and boom!
You're the star Road Racer
of Akina, an admired hero!
Am I?  Really?
I'm embarrassed.
I said not now!
You're only a moron eating a bean jam bun!
Actually, I feel weird.
How?
Not just during the race, but also when
I gave Iketani a ride yesterday...
I just drove like I normally do, but I don't understand
why you guys got so excited.
I've never made people so excited.
Driving is getting more interesting.
Hey.
The black 32.
I've seen it a lot these days.
Damn, he's tailgating me.
Try not to let it pass!
Okay.  The power difference is less
significant on the downhill.
Even the Eight-Six defeated the FD.
Small fry...
He passed us on the outside!
It's almost scary. Its exit
acceleration is incomparable.
As I thought, in reality, an underpowered car
can't overtake a car with a bigger engine.
This is an incredible machine.
After I changed cars, my rivals
became insignificant.
I no longer had any opponent
I could take seriously.
Those showy drift plays
aren't my style.
With grip driving, I can push myself
to the limit, and thrill myself.
Otherwise, I can't be satisfied.
Come on, Eight-Six of Akina!
I instantaneously sensed that you're
good enough to be my opponent.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
A normal Nissan Skyline GT-R R32
has 280 HP with a 2.6L 6-inline
cylinders engine. However, many
are highly modified and output
power rated 400-700 HP.
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
ATTESA: Advanced Total
Traction Engineering System
E-TS:
Electronic
Torque Split
(i.e. Nissan's
state of the art
AWD system)
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
I heard that you were a famous
Akina Road Racer, Manager.
Sort of.  I used to drive with Bunta.
And Takumi will race against Nakazato
of the Night Kids next, won't he?
Yeah, but he doesn't like to race.
Then we won't be able
to see the race?
Wait a moment.  I have a good
idea, so just leave it to me.
Next time on Initial D,
"A Road Racer's Pride."
Next Time:
A Road Racer's Pride
Don't miss it!