This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
Are you serious?
With that Mogi Natsuki?
Everyone was after her.
She's got such a hot body...
She'll listen to anything I say.
I'll teach her slowly.
Teach what?
You know.
All girls are the same.
Even if they resist,
they'll be obedient anyway.
I took her up to the
roof the other day...
Knock it off already!
What's the matter with you, Takumi?
Is that the way you're supposed
to talk to your seniors?!
Don't, Takumi.
You're pissing me off,
you assholes!
Say what?!
Stop, Takumi!
Stop!
ACT.7
A Road Racer's Pride
You're so mean, Takumi.
How can you leave such a cute girl
alone and go to your own world?
I asked you if you have
some girl you like.
I have someone I'm
interested in a little, too.
Iketani.
Hey, where did Iketani go?
Iketani?
The one I've witnessed...
...on the frightening Mt. Akina downhill
where a death cry echoes...
...in the third corner,
passing out!
That Iketani went on
a delivery a while ago.
I see.
If Iketani isn't around,
I guess I have to ask Takumi.
I want you to take a sales
slip to Yamada Trading.
You can use my car.
Okay.
Manager...
You know... I have a license, too.
Why do you only ask Iketani or Takumi?
Well, on that...
Put your hand on your chest and think.
Do you get it?
Nope.
In other words, I can trust Iketani
and Takumi's driving...
...but if it's you...
...my precious car might
come back with a dent.
A dent?!
That's why.
Shit, once I get an Eight-Six, I'll
become a good driver quickly.
A 32!
Welcome!
Cool!  The 32 is so awesome...
N...Night Kids?!
Hey, I'm Nakazato.
A local guy told me that I could speak to
the Speedstars' members if I came here.
Can you tell me when I should visit
Akina to see the Eight-Six?
Don't you know what
I'm talking about?
Aren't you a member
of the Speedstars?
Member of the Speedstars?
It sounds so wonderful.
I guess I came to the wrong station...
No, you came to the right place!
I'm the best friend of the
driver of the Eight-Six.
Say what?
We're called the fastest Eight-Six
downhill pair by our team.
Really?
Well, he's a little better than me.
I've never heard that the Speedstars'
skill level was so high.
Anyway, I can contact the Eight-Six
driver you're looking for.
He's my best friend.
Then I'll count on you to tell him.
Next Saturday at 10:00 pm...
Next Saturday at 10:00 pm...?
...Nakazato of the Night Kids will be
waiting at the peak of Mt. Akina.
"...at the peak of Mt. Akina."
There'll only be one race.
Wait...is that...?!
Wait a minute!
Hey...
I'm in big trouble.
Wasn't that a challenge for Takumi?
Holy shit!
How should I tell him?!
Takumi!
What're you doing there?
Don't worry about that, Takumi.
Anyway, if you're free this Saturday...
...do you feel like driving on Akina?
Nope.
Why not?
Sorry, but unless I have
a special reason...
...I won't go out and drive.
Takumi, thanks.
Come on in and have some coffee.
Okay.
Hey!
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Good work.
Hey, Takumi.
Let me ask you something.
Hypothetically speaking, if a Road
Racer challenged you...
...you'd race him, wouldn't you?
I don't like that, so I wouldn't.
Then I'd be in trouble!
Why would you be in trouble?
Well... never mind...
But a Road Racer has to
race when challenged.
That might be so if you're a Road Racer...
...but I don't want to be a Road Racer.
No way.
And I don't like the idea that I "have to"
race when challenged.
This is bad.
Extremely bad.
What am I gonna do?
Two more days till the race.
I'll show that Eight-Six guy
and Takahashi Ryosuke...
...that I'm number one!
Iketani!
You accepted the match against the
Night Kids of Myogi, didn't you?
If you did something that important,
you should've told the rest of us.
I don't know anything about that.
What're you talking about?
What do you mean?!
Everyone's talking about it!
It's gonna be a single match on the downhill
between the Eight-Six and a 32!
The Eight-Six and...?
Never heard of it.
But they say that Nakazato of the Night Kids
came here himself and made the challenge!
Takumi, did you accept his challenge?
I don't know about it.
No one knows about it?
That's strange.
I'm sorry...
Itsuki, don't tell me...
I...I accepted it.
I'm sorry!
Nakazato of the Night Kids
came here yesterday.
Neither Iketani nor Takumi
were here at that moment.
I...
I was talking to him, pretending to
be a member of the Speedstars...
...and it just happened.
Why'd you keep something so
important a secret until now?!
I was going to tell you,
but I couldn't find a chance.
I'm sorry, Takumi!
Forgive me.
It was my fault...
Even if you say so...
Forgive me, forgive me...
Hey, that 32 is here again.
It's gonna race the Eight-Six of the
Speedstars tomorrow night, right?
I'll definitely come and watch.
Yeah.
Nakazato will challenge the Eight-Six that
Takahashi Keisuke couldn't beat...
We can't miss it.
It looks like a match between the
Speedstars and the Night Kids...
...but in reality...
...it's a clash of pride between the Redsuns'
Takahashi brothers and the Night Kids.
Whoever wins, Takahashi Ryosuke
won't just stand by and watch.
Sleepless nights will come one
after another this summer.
Anyway, this isn't good.
What should we do?
Since those rumors have spread
so widely, we can't withdraw.
I'd better ask Takumi to drive myself.
But even if it's Takumi, we're at a disadvantage
because the opponent's a 32.
Nakazato of the Night Kids is as famous
as the Takahashi brothers.
It's gonna be a tough battle.
It might be a hopeless battle...
And if I think about it,
I just can't ask him.
We can't...
Here.
Hey, Dad...
How good is the 32?
The 32...?
That's... great.
Could you defeat the 32
on the downhill?
I'd win.
Whether it's a 32 or not
makes no difference.
Do you think I could win?
I don't know.
But it'd be a close match.
Why're you asking me?
Are you going to race against a 32?
No reason.
I just... wanted to ask.
I'm off.
So the next one's a 32.
I guess I have to change the
settings on the Eight-Six.
I don't know, but it'd be a close match...
I had the feeling I'd see you
if I came here at this time.
It was about this time
when I first saw you.
I heard that you're gonna race against
Nakazato of the Night Kids.
People are talking about
you all over the place.
Let me tell you that
I didn't agree to race him.
Say what?
He challenged me while I was away,
and I'm not interested in racing.
What do you mean you're not interested?
Nakazato of the Night Kids personally
challenged you, didn't he?
Why don't you accept?
And beat the shit out of him!
You should be able to do that!
Why are you saying that?
It's none of your business.
It sure as hell is...
...because you defeated me!
Only the Takahashi brothers of
the Redsuns will defeat you.
Until then, don't lose, even
if it's against the 32!
I said I'm not doing it!
Besides, I don't have any reason.
Reason?  What do you mean?
Why does a Road Racer
need a reason to race?
I'm not a Road Racer.
Stop screwing around with me!
Are you trying to be sarcastic?!
You must've been driving a lot
to acquire such great technique!
Why would someone other than
a Road Racer drive so much?
I don't mean to drive that
way because I want to.
I have to drive to help the shop.
Don't lie to me!
How can you learn such great technique
if you drive unwillingly?!
That's not it.
You don't understand.
You're the one who doesn't understand!
How could someone who hates
driving master drift?
Only those who like to drive can
master that kind of technique.
You might not have noticed...
...but you like to drive in your heart.
Listen, if you like to drive a car, that's
enough to be called a Road Racer.
If you're a Road Racer, you should have
pride in the techniques you've learned!
If someone challenges you, you accept it.
That's the pride of a Road Racer.
I'm disappointed I came to see you.
I hadn't realized...
...that I like to drive a car?
But that doesn't mean I "must"
accept someone's challenge.
I just don't want it!
Hey, Itsuki, where's Takumi?
He's on late shift today.
I see.
Iketani...
I'll go to Mt. Akina tonight and apologize
to Nakazato of the Night Kids.
Itsuki...
If I beg him, and explain what happened,
he might understand.
Originally, it had nothing to do
with the Speedstars.
I wonder if there's a way to convince Takumi.
I don't think it's possible.
I know him too well.
He really hates it when someone tries
to force or order him around.
He looks quiet...
...but once he makes up his mind, he gets
stubborn and won't change it.
That part of his personality
is identical to his father's.
He doesn't like the idea of accepting
someone's challenge automatically.
That's why he's resisting.
If we force him, he'll get mad.
When he was a sophomore, he got pissed,
and beat up a senior in the soccer club.
Takumi did?
Manager, I'm finished outside.
Good work.
Well then, I'm heading home.
Takumi.
Sit down over here for a sec.
I heard a rumor that you're
going to race a 32 tonight.
Well, I...
You'd better not, because
that's a tough opponent.
Well, about that...
Don't say anything.
I understand without you telling me.
I know all about it.
I know that you didn't accept the battle.
Itsuki accepted it without
asking, didn't he?
Yeah...
But you're too nice.
You don't have to save
face for your friend.
I'm telling you.  You'd better
stay away from the 32.
You don't know much
about cars...
...so you don't know what kind
of car the 32 is, do you?
Is a 32 that good?
Good, he took the bait.
It's far better than good.
It's totally overwhelming!
It's got a drive train that combines the
advantages of both FR and 4WD.
It's so unfair.
The GT-R is totally different from the Eight-Six.
Maybe if the driver wasn't good...
But your opponent is a famous
Road Racer, isn't he?
It's different from what Dad said.
He said it would be a close match.
Hey...
Are you listening?
You got famous by defeating
the team from Akagi.
You should keep it.
It's not wise to race against someone
you have no chance of beating.
Right, Takumi?
The opponent is a 32, so even if you don't
race, no one will think you ran away.
Run away...?!
Manager...
...thanks for your advice.
I don't think it's important to gain
fame as a Road Racer at all.
So you're not gonna quit...
I won't.
Having heard how good it is...
...I want to see how good it is myself.
I'm not afraid of the 32.
Excuse me.
His reaction is surprisingly
similar to his father's.
Temporarily closed due
to private reasons.
Fujiwara Tofu Shop
Temporarily closed?
I hadn't heard anything!
We're poor, so he should be working.
Damn, the car!
If he's gone out drinking,
it's hopeless.
That shitty old man won't
come home until morning.
If I don't have a car,
I can't go anywhere.
I should've asked him this morning!
The galleries are really packed!
There are more people this time than there were
during the race against the Akagi team.
What did they come to see?
I'll bet it's not the 32.
Of course, it's the drift
of the Eight-Six.
He keeps the gas pedal open one corner
after another, and they say he's so fast.
I can't wait to see it!
Oh, I see.
If he shows up, could you
tell him to call home?
Thank you.
It's no use.
I can't find him.
Shit!
You stupid old man!
Bring back the Eight-Six!
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
Itsuki spoke too freely, and
accepted this battle.
The 32 or the Eight-Six, which one
do you think will win, Kenji?
Of course, I say
the Eight-Six...
...but it's impossible, even if it's Takumi, because
the GT-R's the fastest car in Japan.
Besides, we don't know
if Takumi will arrive.
If not, once again, you might have to...
Don't say that!
Next time on Initial D,
"Just Before the Time Attack."
Takumi, please come!
Get here quickly!
Next Time: ACT.8
Just Before the Time Attack!
Don't miss it!