This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
The galleries are packed.
It looks like there're more people here
than during the match against the FD.
That means the battle between Takumi
and Nakazato of the Night Kids...
...has attracted a lot of attention.
What should I do?
I'm feeling even more depressed.
The mood won't allow us to
simply say it was a mistake.
Takumi...
...please come!
ACT.8
Just Before the Time Attack!
Shit.
Where did that stupid old man go?
Do you think you could win?
I'd win.  Whether it's a 32 or not
makes no difference.
And... do you think I could win?
I know that you didn't accept the battle.
I'm telling you.  You'd better
stay away from the 32.
Takumi, the opponent is a 32, so even if you don't
race, no one will think you ran away.
Run away...?!
The Night Kids are here!
It's Nakazato with his 32!
It looks so powerful.
That black 32 deserves to
be the king of the street.
So they're the Night Kids.
They sure came in with a big group.
S...Senpai, if we're going to apologize,
the sooner the better!
Yeah, but...
We still have time.
Let's go and ask him!
I don't think it's a good idea to
drag him to a hopeless battle.
We won't know unless we try.
It's impossible.  You'll understand
if you cool down and think.
The opponent is a 32!
The power is totally different, and
it's got 4WD ATTESA E-TS.
I thought so at the beginning...
...but since I got here, I started to believe.
The Eight-Six would have no
chance on the circuit...
...but this is a mountain pass.
Since Takumi has been driving here for five
years, we don't know what'll happen.
When Takumi drives, the Eight-Six
becomes extraordinary.
It turns into a super machine
with infinite potential.
Because I rode next to him, I can tell.
His driving is beyond our imagination.
Oh, the incident of that frightening
downhill with you screaming.
And you passed out in the third corner.
His downhill driving is that different!
And there's one more person
who feels the same way.
W...who's that?
There's one more person who
has seen his driving up close.
T...that's...
Yes...
It's Takahashi Keisuke of the Redsuns.
The Takahashi brothers are here!
Now that the stars are on stage!
I'm getting so excited!
Keisuke!
Ryosuke!
You're so cool!
They're good looking,
so they attract girls.
Damn, only skill should make
a Road Racer popular.
We can't defeat them in any way...
And they're rich.
I knew they'd show up.
I'm looking forward to the battle.
I'll prove who's the best
in the Gunma Prefecture.
It's not the Eight-Six or the
Takahashi brothers...
...it's me, Nakazato Takeshi
of the Night Kids.
Asshole...
The Eight-Six hasn't shown up yet.
I'll have to go and convince Takumi!
Get in.
What's wrong, Itsuki?
I'll stay, Iketani.
I can't face Takumi.
I see.
Wait until the last moment, okay?
I'll bring Takumi, no matter what.
He will... Takumi will come.
Besides...
...I like this place.
I'm getting used to this.
Oh, dear Ryosuke!
Why...
I'm frustrated to death.
I want to go to Mt. Akina so much.
I don't know if I like to drive
that much or not...
But I've been driving alone for five years,
whether it was snowing or raining.
I've driven Akina more than anyone.
I want to test how good I am.
I want to challenge the GT-R...
...with all my skill.
I've never felt this way before.
I'm not giving up, even though
I don't have a car.
Instead, my desire to drive
is getting stronger.
Dammit, Dad.
Where're you wandering around?
Takumi!
Iketani...
Say what?
Your dad left with the car,
and hasn't come back...?
Yeah.
Don't you know where he is?
I thought he'd be at a bar, so I called
all the places I could think of.
And you couldn't get a hold of him.
The Eight-Six isn't here and
we can't even persuade you!
This is unexpected.
Senpai, you came to persuade me?
Yeah.
The mountain is in an uproar.
Nakazato of the Night Kids and the Takahashi
brothers are entertaining the galleries.
But you're today's main attraction.
Wait a minute.
Please, don't.
No matter what you say,
I can't do anything.
You won't change your mind, will you.
I don't mean that.
Actually, I was going to go.
What?!
But without a car, I can't do anything.
I've been so depressed,
sitting here alone.
How could this be...?!
It's so frustrating!
Without a car... Without a car...
That's it!
Hey, Takumi, what about
borrowing Kenji's 180?
That's a good idea!
It's got the same FR layout, and it has
a turbo, so it's more powerful!
If you drive it, it'll run fast!
I don't think so.
W...why not?
I don't want to drive someone else's car.
It has to be a car I'm familiar with.
That's true.
It's not a good thing among Road Racers
to drive someone else's car.
I'll wait as long as I can.
That's all I can do.
It's 9:45.
I guess they didn't make it.
He's late.
What time is it?
Almost 10:00.
We aren't gonna make it.
Where are you, Dad?
Please, come home!
We don't have time.
He's back.
That rhythm of revving up twice when
turning from the interstate...
...that sound...
Dad's coming home.
You can tell by just listening
to the exhaust sound?
Is that really your car?
I can tell.
I'm positive.
The Takahashi brothers are here.
Yeah, they can't ignore this.
He told me that I'd be defeated.
That Takahashi Ryosuke is known for logical
thinking, but he doesn't seem that good.
I'll defeat the Eight-Six in front
of him, and humiliate him.
Let's do it.
If you're faster than the Eight-Six, which
defeated Takahashi Keisuke...
...we're faster than the Redsuns!
It's a good opportunity to let those
galleries know one thing.
Drift driving can't defeat grip driving.
It's your favorite phrase.
Of course.
Drift is just a performance
to excite the galleries.
It's not a technique to race with.
That sounds just like you, Takeshi.
When I was driving the 13,
I learned drift, so I can tell.
When the master of drift uses a grip technique,
he can drive even faster.
It was shocking when you
were defeated by that 32...
Sorry, I wasn't supposed to say that.
I was changed at that moment.
I switched to the 32, the monster that
defeated me, and my skill improved.
Who can call a person a Road Racer
if he doesn't pursue better driving?
All everyone talks about is drift, drift,
and thinks highly of those drivers.
I can't stand that.
Come on, Eight-Six!
Drifting with the FR layout
is old hat.  I'll prove that!
As usual, he isn't showing
up until the last minute.
Do you think he'll really show up?
He said he wasn't interested, didn't he?
No, he'll be here.
I'm sure of it.
He'll definitely be here.
Well, that's what this is all about,
so let me use the car, Dad.
You'd better hurry, Takumi.
It's almost time.
Sorry, but I'm borrowing Takumi.
When we return, I'll buy ten fried tofu.
I...I'll buy Ganmodoki, too.
W...wait!
Takumi's eyes looked different.
What's going on?
Oh well, he'll be able to race
evenly with that setting.
The mountain pass is close.  I wonder
if you can keep up with him, Kenji.
Oh, come on, Iketani.
That's a 1.6 liter non-turbo.
I've got a 2.0 liter turbo.
I'm not sure about the downhill, but if he
pulls away on the uphill, I'll lose face.
I'm one of the top three of the Speedstars.
He's so fast.
Me too!
Exit the corner, then full acceleration!
He's gone.
The Eight-Six has vanished...!
Takumi was also looking away in
the entrance ceremony picture.
Two more minutes till 10:00 pm.
I guess they didn't make it.
I'd better give up and apologize.
No, Iketani told me to wait.
If I go off on my own again...
But it was my fault, and it has nothing
to do with the Speedstars.
I'd better prepare for
one or two punches...
There are so many of them!
I don't think I'll be forgiven
with only a punch or two!
No way!
I want to run away.
They won't forgive me easily
if the Eight-Six doesn't show up.
Even if I kneel to the ground, they won't
forgive me.  I might be killed.
Father, Mother, help me.
Please, God.
I've never slept with a girl,
and I don't wanna die!
There!
There he is!
Oh no, they found me!
I can't even run away!
I'll be killed...
What're you doing, Itsuki,
sitting in the middle of the road?
Ta...Ta...Ta...
You're in my way.
I'm gonna run over you.
Takumi, you came!
Yeah.
Sorry I'm late, Itsuki.
Takumi...
Road Racers have to accept
challenges, don't they?
Takumi...
Stop it!
Hey, Itsuki!
That's more like it.
This is Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Oh, it's you, Yuichi.
You're there?
I don't know what's going on.
He wanted to go to the
mountain himself.
Like father, like son.
Besides, Bunta, tonight's
opponent is a GT-R.
Honestly speaking, do you think
he has a chance of winning?
The Eight-Six finally showed up.
Keisuke, he came as you predicted.
Yeah.
Weren't you going to tell him
the weakness of the 32?
I was going to, but I decided not to.
After seeing his face,
I started hating him.
He's my enemy, after all.
Besides...
...even if he doesn't know
its weakness, he won't lose.
Did you give him any advice?
Not really.
Even if it's the GT-R,
it has its weakness.
The weakness of the 32 is...
...the weight of the body.
Understeering due to the
super heavy front load.
Suspension tuning and driving technique can't
change its fundamental characteristics.
After pushing hard on the downhill, the
front tires and brakes will weaken.
Even if the brakes are tuned...
...by the time he reaches the
base of the mountain...
...he has to cope with understeering
at the corners' entrances.
His chance of winning lies at the entrance
of the corners in the second half.
The key point of this battle...
...is whether the Eight-Six can keep up
with the 32 until then or not.
I changed the suspension setting
of the Eight-Six a little.
The suspension?
How?
Heavy understeering when
the gas pedal is open.
What?!
Heavy understeering?!
Drift is Takumi's style.
What's on your mind, Bunta?
Will he be able to keep up with
the GT-R with that setting?
Don't you get it, Yuichi?
If the driver is skilled...
...he can depress the accelerator harder
when it comes to the FR layout.
He has to deliver tofu, so the setting
is usually compromised a little bit.
He can open the throttle longer
with the current setting.
If the driver is skilled...
...I'm sure he can handle it.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
Nakazato, how's your chance of
winning against the Eight-Six?
Psheesh.
It's so obvious.
So, the 32 will win.
But Takahashi Ryosuke...
He's hesitant because his
brother was defeated.
I'll show them that I'm
the fastest in Gunma...
...and grip driving is superior.
He'll just be eating my dust!
What's that "psheesh?"
It's only action, action!
Next Time: ACT.9
The Battle to the Limit!
Next time on Initial D,
"The Battle to the Limit!"
Psheesh!
Don't miss it!