This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
Why...
I'm frustrated to death.
I want to go to Mt. Akina so much.
I don't know if I like to drive
that much or not.
But I've been driving alone for five years,
whether it was snowing or raining.
I've driven Akina more than anyone.
Well, that's what this is all about,
so let me use the car, Dad.
You'd better hurry, Takumi.
It's almost time.
There!
There he is!
Oh no, they found me!
I can't even run away!
I'll be killed...
What're you doing, Itsuki,
sitting in the middle of the road?
Ta...Ta...Ta...
You're in my way.
I'm gonna run over you.
Takumi, you came!
Yeah.
Sorry I'm late, Itsuki.
Takumi...
Road Racers have to accept
challenges, don't they?
Takumi...
Stop it!
Hey...
Battle to the Limit!
ACT.9
He's young.
He must've gotten his license recently.
How could a kid like him
have such techniques?
I thought he'd be older than me.
So that's the GT-R.
It's far better than good.
It's totally overwhelming.
It's got a drive train that combines the
advantages of both FR and 4WD.
I'm Nakazato of the Night Kids.
What's your name?
Fujiwara Takumi.
I'll remember your name.
Let's get started.
Severe understeering is better during acceleration
if the driver is good, you say?
If the characteristics
have changed...
...don't you think he'll get confused
when he attacks hard?
You should've told him about that.
It wouldn't help, even if I told him.
He's not smart enough to change his driving
habits by thinking about them.
Say what?  Then he'll...
It's okay.  Don't worry.
He's not smart...
...but his physical responses are good.
It's too late if you respond to thinking
based on feelings in the seat.
Your hands and feet have to respond unconsciously
to control the drift, right?
You don't have to worry.
His sense of accelerating the car
while skidding is exceptional.
Even if the suspension settings are
a little different, it won't bother him.
He'll easily find the best way
and fully control the car.
The Eight-Six is the kind of car
that can train the driver.
This is the finish line.
No other cars are around.
Anytime is okay.
Iketani, start when you're ready.
Alright.
Let's start the countdown!
Ten seconds till start!
I'm counting on you, Takumi!
Keisuke...
...I'll let you observe this battle
from the VIP seat.
Hurry, it's about to start.
Five seconds!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Go!
The 32 has the lead.
But Takumi isn't too far behind.
Here they come.
Put on your seatbelt.
It's the FC.
Takahashi Ryosuke rocket-started his car.
He's gonna follow them!
My god, it's gonna be a super
battle between the three?!
It's gonna be the match to determine
the fastest in Gunma!
That GT-R driver isn't flooring it.
Is he waiting for me?
It wouldn't be fair to get
a lead on the straightaway.
I want a battle.
The real start is the corner's entrance!
Nakazato is going easy on the pedal,
and waiting for the Eight-Six.
I hope he won't regret this easygoing attitude
during the second half of the race.
There they are.
This is the first corner!
Three cars are coming in back to back!
Incredible.  It's just
like Bunta said.
What the hell?
Is this a joke?
He won't be able to follow me with
that overly active "crab walk."
Watching him up close,
his drift is almost an art form.
Four wheel drift at full throttle with
minimum counter steering...
Do you know how great that is?
He can control his Eight-Six like his arms
and legs in a critical situation.
I can't control my FC like he does.
I'm so impressed.
But Nakazato is slowly pulling away.
Will he be able to win this battle?
This is it.
This is the feeling.
This high tension of boiling blood...
This is a battle!
I'll push myself to the limit!
How much longer can
you keep up with me?
It's different...
The car's running slightly different.
The car doesn't lose stability...
...and I can depress the gas pedal early.
Dad must've done something
while I was working...
...because it wasn't like
this earlier this morning.
I see.  That's why he wasn't home.
I don't know why, but I like it.
The car doesn't skid too much,
so I can step on it without worrying.
Incredible!
Unbelievable drift!
This is the first time I've seen someone who
can let their car skid on a straightaway.
It's unusual.  You can't do that unless
the car maintains its speed.
What was that?
That's not the kind of
drift we're used to!
Awesome!  Once you've seen it,
you won't forget it!
Incredible!
The Eight-Six is still
keeping up with the 32!
Takumi seems to be able to
keep up with the 32.
I...incredible!
He can match Nakazato of Myogi and
the superstar, Takahashi Ryosuke.
He's too good to be my best friend!
He's so cool!
Speaking of Takahashi Ryosuke,
his FC isn't part of the battle.
He's just a third person.
Yeah, Nakazato is the opponent.
I know he's at a disadvantage
racing the 32...
...but since it's Takumi,
he'll win, right?
Yeah, he will!
That's right!
He's pulling away.
Nakazato's good enough
to match his big mouth.
He's balancing the load well,
and coping with understeering.
It's a driving technique to make
use of the power of the GT-R.
It looks boring, but he doesn't drive wastefully,
giving no overtaking opportunities.
Hey, Brother, how can
you be so laid-back?
If he wins, we'll be disgraced.
The battle isn't over yet.
In the first half, the straightaways are relatively
long, and the slopes are gentle.
There are many disadvantageous
factors for the Eight-Six.
From here, the slopes
will be steeper.
The downhill specialist
will show his true skill.
The 32 is good at these
low speed hairpin curves.
If I make use of the powerful brakes
and slow down as I should...
The load shifts to the front
on the downhill...
...so it doesn't exhibit understeering
on acceleration.
And the acceleration in the lower gears
is better than any other car.
The strongest car on the circuit is also
the fastest on the public street!
The emblem on the rear is from
the R of the unbeatable legend.
Can you keep up with my R?
Hey, Iketani.
What?
I've been thinking lately.
Is Takumi an unusual Road Racer
who's only fast on Akina's downhill?
I wonder how he'd drive
on other downhills.
Haven't you thought about that?
Yeah, I'm very curious about that.
But for now, this battle is important.
Don't be defeated, Takumi.
Takumi...!
Incredible.
My eyes can't focus.
Now he's getting serious.
He's started grabbing the
gutter with the inner tires.
That's it.  That's the technique
I lost to.
I never thought I'd be
able to see it again.
My brother's stopped talking.
He can't relax.
I've ridden with him many times, but
I've never seen him drive like this.
He's serious.
Akina Skate Ring
He's closing in...
The Eight-Six is catching up!
Impossible!
Fine then.
Now that you have done so well, my prejudice
against a ten-year-old car is completely gone.
It's a wonderful machine with
first class fighting capability.
I won't hold back!
I'm so glad he's making
this so exciting...
I haven't been so excited since
I switched to this car!
He can't catch up with the 32
at the exit of a hairpin corner.
Even if the Eight-Six gains on the 32
at the entrance, the gap will widen.
Nakazato's got guts, pushing so hard
on the downhill with a heavy 32.
What?!
The Eight-Six is gaining on
the 32 in a high-speed corner!
How can he four wheel drift so close to the
guardrail going faster than 100 km/h?!
It's got nothing to do
with the car's performance.
His brain lacks a few lugnuts.
If he makes a mistake, he'll die!
I can see the secret of his fast driving.
Since the Eight-Six
is underpowered...
...if the car loses speed, it loses
time picking speed back up.
So he doesn't slow down wastefully.
Now I understand why he managed to
stay right on my butt like a ghost.
I can't pull away.
The time he stays on my tail
has gotten longer.
Dammit!  He's tough!
The distance to the guardrail is
about 20 to 30 cm for Nakazato.
That's about right for most Road Racers,
no matter how good they are.
But the bumper of his Eight-Six
almost rubs the guardrails...
...and it passes the shortest distance
through the corners.
He's in a class by himself!
How can he perform such
precise drift control?!
I've been steering hard,
keeping the ABS on.
So the load to the front tires
is greater than I expected.
It's getting tough.
The five hairpins are ahead...
What?
The place where you were overtaken
will be the key point.
I didn't expect the battle between the 32
and the Eight-Six to be this close.
It's indeed a battle to the limit.
Who will win?
This is from the five hairpins.
I can hear the squealing!
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
Ryosuke, most of the people said
that the 32 was superior.
The length of a normal R32 is 4640mm.
Width is 1720mm, weight 14...
In other words?
In other words, the length of a normal
R32 is 4640mm.  Width is 1720mm...
In other words, on the
downhill, Takumi is...
In other words, the length of a normal
R32 is 4640mm.  Width...
Never mind!
Next time on Initial D:
"Dangerous Five Hairpins."
Next Time: ACT.10
Dangerous Five Hairpins
Don't miss it.