This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
Five seconds!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Go!
I've been steering hard,
keeping the ABS on.
So the load to the front tires
is greater than I expected.
It's getting tough.
The five hairpins are ahead...
What?
The place where you were overtaken
will be the key point.
ACT.10
Dangerous Five Hairpins
The Eight-Six is right on his tail!
I don't believe it.
Nakazato is fighting so desperately!
What's going on?!
Look!  That's the braking
drift of the Eight-Six!
Awesome...
The FC...?
Takahashi Ryosuke!
I watched Keisuke being overtaken by
the Eight-Six in these five hairpins.
That Eight-Six used
the gutter to turn.
He blocked the inside.  He's trying
not to let him squeeze in!
That Nakazato...
What're you going to do, Eight-Six?
What?
From the outside?!
Watch out!
I...it's gonna crash!
Don't screw around with me!
I won't let you pass from the outside!
Just like the 32.
Sharp acceleration at the exit is great.
Besides, that Eight-Six...
He kept skidding in such
a narrow curve.
Three more corners...
...and this battle will be settled.
He's going to overtake from
the outside again!
So frustrating!
It pisses me off when
he gets outside of me!
The 32 is acting strange.
Nakazato has lost his concentration.
Keep your eyes on them, Keisuke.
The Eight-Six's gonna overtake him.
Overtake him...?
But the inside is blocked.
How?
Takumi's trying to overtake him?
Really?
Great!
Way to go, Takumi!
I'm humiliated in front of so many galleries,
almost being overtaken from the outside.
Because I get too close
to the inside...
...the car misses the ideal line, and the
entry speed has to be slower!
That's right.  I only have to make a space
slightly narrower than a car!
That way, my entry speed can be faster!
Good, he's not gonna take the inside!
The Eight-Six disappeared!
It can't be...!
Dammit, it understeered
at a critical moment!
He tried to go outside, and then he
changed the line while braking!
The Eight-Six is capable of doing that?
But don't think that you're going to win!
If we accelerate side by side, I'll be able
to pull ahead at full throttle in 2nd gear!
I'll show you the true
potential of the 32!
I lost.
The 32 and I have lost.
No, that's not right.
Only I lost.
The car didn't lose to the Eight-Six.
An incredible Road Racer like him exists...
It's shocking, but I feel refreshed.
Although I lost, I tried my best.
What a pain.
The bodywork will cost 70,000 yen ($700).
I'll train myself and challenge him again.
He did it!
Takumi won!
He did it!  He did it!
He did it!
Takumi did... Takumi did it!
N...no way.
The Eight-Six overtook the 32 in the
fourth corner of the five hairpins!
How could the Eight-Six defeat the 32?
The Eight-Six did?
Really?
I don't believe it!
It's just like you said, Bunta.
Just like him.
It's fun to watch interesting
things, isn't it, Keisuke?
Yeah, the attack of the
Eight-Six was incredible.
He pretended to go outside, but changed
the line during full braking.
It's got wonderful ABS.
What are you saying?
Don't be dumb, Keisuke.
How could an Eight-Six
be equipped with ABS?
Because...
That was human ABS.
Those Road Racers who've gotten used
to modern cars equipped with ABS...
...would never be able to master severe pedal
control just before locking their tires.
ABS is computer controlled, so it can't surpass
the right foot of a well-trained driver.
I'm finally excited after such a long time.
That Eight-Six is definitely
worth defeating.
Why're you standing there?
No reason.
Hey, Dad...
...about this car...
What?
It's alright.
It's nothing.
I'm going to bed.
I bought an Eight-Six!
I kept it secret, but it was delivered today!
It's still clean!
So you begged your dad,
and made him a guarantor!
The shop was nice, and I got a good
price for the condition of the car.
Looks really good!
It could be a find.
I'm surprised!
You really bought one, Itsuki!
Of course, Takumi.
I can't let you get too far ahead of me.
From now on, I'll try to be one of the two
fastest Eight-Six downhill Road Racers.
Such a big talker.
I couldn't sleep last night
because I was so happy.
I know what you mean.
I couldn't sleep the night before
my S13 was delivered.
That's right.
It's really my car.
My car.
I feel like I'm having a dream.
Normal wheels and 70 aspect ratio
tires look pathetic but adequate.
Hey, start up the engine, Itsuki.
Sure.  No problem.
It doesn't sound so good.
I guess it's because the muffler is normal.
Don't worry.
I'll change the muffler.
I want to make it sound
as good as Takumi's Trueno.
I have a bad feeling.
Pop the hood, Itsuki.
I thought so.
Manager...?
You're mistaken, Itsuki.
Mistaken...?
This isn't an Eight-Six.
It's an Eight-Five.
Eight-Five...
You mean an AE85?
Comparing the Eight-Six and Eight-Five,
the body is the same...
...but the performance differences are like chocolate
and shit, a goddess and an old maid.
The Eight-Six has a double overhead cam engine,
and the Eight-Five has a single one!
DOHC and SOHC are totally different!
You bought a car without knowing that?!
How lame!
Sorry, sorry, Itsuki,
but it's so funny!
Wait, Itsuki!
You guys laughed too much.
Think how Itsuki feels.
Sorry...
S..sorry...
Itsuki!
Leave me alone!
Don't bother me!
Even if you say so...
It was my fault for looking for a car
by myself to surprise everyone.
That explains why it was
so cheap for an Eight-Six.
I got so excited without knowing it.
I'm so embarrassed I could die.
You're laughing inside, aren't you?
No.
I'm... envious of you.
Envious?
Don't give me that BS!
It's not BS.
You're still in high school
and you have your own car.
My own car?
Yeah.  What's wrong with an Eight-Five?
It's got an engine, tires and it runs.
Even if it doesn't have power,
it can pick up speed on the downhill...
Why don't you practice hard
and learn some techniques?
Cars are interesting.
You know, you've changed.
Have I?
Yeah, you were uninterested
in cars before.
Takumi, I feel like I could
like my Eight-Five.
I'm not that good anyway.
Right.
Don't agree so easily!
I'd better drive on Mt. Akina tonight...
Takumi, come with me.
Sure.  With your Eight-Five.
Takumi...
I'll pick you up around 10:00pm!
Promise me, okay?
Okay.
Don't go to bed, just wait for me!
Didn't see the Eight-Six.
I wanted to see it.
It's hard to imagine that an
Eight-Six defeated a 32.
Isn't that an Eight-Six?
Could it be...?
Man, it's so fun driving
the mountain pass!
It's slow on the straightaways...
...but it runs well in the corners,
doesn't it, Takumi?
Yeah, more or less.
What're you doing?
Well, if I look at it from a distance...
...my Levin looks cool.
Why're you so cool, my Levin?!
I'm glad I bought this Levin!
How optimistic you are.
They're just brats.
They couldn't be.
The technician who defeated
the 32 couldn't be one of them.
Right.
How old are you?
Do you have a license?
If you don't, you'll be in trouble.
I...I do.
I look young, but I'm eighteen years old.
What's with them?
They're so rude.
What's the point of picking on a child?
I don't like young Road Racer
wannabes driving Eight-Sixes.
You're a local, aren't you?
We came here to see the famous Eight-Six.
Do you know about it?
Don't you have a mouth?
You know about it, don't you?
Well...I know about it...
But I don't think it will
show up tonight.
That sucks.  And after we
came all the way up here.
Let's go home.
If you're trying to be a Road Racer,
try not to be so pathetic.
What's wrong with this Eight-Six?
These normal wheels make me
sick just looking at them.
It's so lame.
At least change the muffler.
It sounds so uncool.
Do you know anything
about an Eight-Six?
Well, it's not an Eight-Six,
it's an Eight-Five.
So even if I changed the muffler,
it won't sound good.
I still want to change it though.
Eight-Five?
Even if you want to change
the muffler...
...you won't find one anywhere
that fits the Eight-Five!
None, anywhere.
My eyes are watering!
I've never seen anyone
driving an Eight-Five.
A brat deserves an Eight-Five!
Let's go home.
I laughed so hard I cried.
Try hard and don't let
a scooter tailgate you!
I'm pissed.  I can't let them
get away with that.
Itsuki, let me use your car for a while.
Takumi!
Get in the car, quickly!
What're you gonna do,
chase them?
The suspension on the Eight-Five is so weak,
and the tires are normal!
I don't care.
Hey, Takumi, don't!
It doesn't have the limited
slip differential, and...
Who cares.
Put your seatbelt on!
It might be a little scary, but just
trust me and bear with it.
I won't wreck your precious car.
Here we go.
Ta...Takumi!
Taku...Taku...Taku...!
My...my...my Eight-Five...
Please drive gently with my Eight-Five!
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
The Levin shares the
same chassis as the
Trueno, but has square
headlights instead of the
flip-up ones. This model
was never available in
the USA.
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
Itsuki has bought the weakest
model available.
AE85:
AE86 body with a 3A-C (1500cc)
engine, no LSD, with only drum
brakes on the rear. Outputing power
rated at 80 HP only.
Not what you'd call a racing machine.
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
SOHC: Single
Overhead Cam
DOHC: Dual
They are different
engine designs.
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
Are you crying, Iketani?
I'm so happy!
My S13 will finally be back!
Oh, that ill-fated specialty car, the S13,
which crashed in episode two.
Hey, Iketani, what's wrong?
By the way...
...I heard a red EG6 showed up on the mountain
pass aiming for Takumi's Eight-Six.
Do you know anything about it?
Nope.
Next time on Initial D,
"Dangerous Shingo Appears."
Next Time:
Dangerous Shingo Appears!
Don't miss it.
Hey!