This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
What's wrong with this Eight-Six?
These normal wheels make me
sick just looking at them.
My eyes are watering!
I've never seen someone
driving an Eight-Five!
A brat deserves an Eight-Five!
Try hard and don't let
a scooter tailgate you.
I'm pissed.  I can't let them
get away with that.
Here we go.
Ta...Takumi!
Taku...Taku...Taku...
My...my...my Eight-Five...
Please drive gently with my Eight-Five!
Dangerous Shingo Appears!
ACT.11
It's alright, Takumi!
T...Takumi...
S...stop, Takumi!
Nice move!
What the...?
Hey, a car's tailgating us.
It must be those Akina brats.
They'll need ten years of
practice to challenge us.
I see.
I'll outrun it easily.
Takumi, it's alright!
STOP!
SLOW DOWN, TAKUMI!
I don't believe it.
Is this really my Eight-Five?
The car behind us is pretty good!
Could it be...
I don't know what's goin' on,
but that's the Eight-Five!
That's the Eight-Five we
saw at the top earlier!
It can't be!  How could an Eight-Five
keep up with me?
Y...you're right!
It's that Eight-Five!
Those brats must've lied to us!
It must be...
...an Eight-Six!
Okay, go!
What's this...
It doesn't accelerate,
even on the downhill.
And the tires...
I don't believe this.
They don't have any grip at all.
He's incredibly fast!
It's so slow.
Oh well...
...I don't have any choice
but to do it that way!
I won't let you pass, no matter what!
What the...?!
What the hell was that?!
How I was overtaken?
That's not an Eight-Five...
...it must be an Eight-Six.
A highly tuned Eight-Six.
Or so I thought, but that rolling...
Could that really be an Eight-Five?
We were totally outrun.
That Eight-Five gave me the creeps!
Could that be...
...A GHOST?!
Is coffee alright?
Here.
Arigato.
Now I understand what Iketani meant.
Your downhill driving is unusual.
Is it?
I don't think so.
You dummy.
You just don't know it.
I never thought a car
could run like that.
My point of view has been changed.
It was so shocking.
Was it that scary?
Sorry.
You don't have to apologize, Takumi.
I'm so happy I can't sit still.
The performance of a car isn't the issue.
Good skill can make an Eight-Five
run fast like that.
I really like this car a lot.
I'll take good care of it, and I'll practice
hard starting tomorrow.
I don't mind if people laugh at me.
I like my Eight-Five best.
That's right.
Let's ask some girls to go
driving in my Eight-Five.
S...sure.
Don't go without telling
me next time, okay?
No matter what, Takumi!
I know.
Beach, girls in swimsuits...
Wait for me!
Alright!
My S13...
Finally, it's returned with the
same handsome face as before.
I'm almost ready to cry.
Itsuki, are you trying to run me over?!
I'll start driving hard tonight.
I'll lower the grade of the tires
and practice drifting.
I'll join you.
Look at this sticker!
It's alright, isn't it?
Well...I guess so.
Manager, look at this.
I'm finally a member of the Speedstars!
Hm...you'd better get it off.
Alright, that's it.
Maybe I can smooth it out...
And before I forget the feeling of
the downhill drive with Takumi...
Say what?!
You rode with Takumi in his Eight-Six?
I did...
...but not in his Eight-Six though.
What's with that suspicious grin?
Tell us everything!
What should I do...?
Do you want to drink oil, Itsuki?
Okay, okay!
I let him drive my Eight-Five, and he
pushed it hard on Akina's downhill.
It was incredible!  I've never had
such an experience before.
My Eight-Five started skidding
way before the corner...
...and the reflection on the windshield
went by sideways so fast!
It's a godsent skill!
He drifted your Eight-Five?
It doesn't even have LSD.
It happened so quickly.
He passed two cars, driven by jerks
in the hairpins on the downhill.
It felt so good!
Do you believe that story, Manager?
Even if it's Takumi, it's just
an ordinary Eight-Five.
Usually, it'd be impossible,
since it's an Eight-Five.
You don't have to say that much.
Even if you don't believe me,
fact is fact.
If he can do that with
an Eight-Five...
...he has much better adaptability
than I thought.
The Eight-Five and Eight-Six share the same body,
so maybe the characteristics are similar.
I don't think so.
The suspension of a normal Eight-Five...
...and Bunta's heavily tuned Eight-Six
are like chocolate and shit.
They're totally different.
Chocolate and... shit?!
So Takumi can push
any car to the limit.
Yeah.
I think he can push any car with
an FR layout to its full potential.
They say that you can't use any
tricks to drive the Eight-Six.
You have to master the basics
in order to push it to the limit.
The Eight-Six is a car
that trains the driver.
That's what Bunta always says.
The car that just passed by
had a Night Kids sticker.
It had the suspension
of a road racer.
If you pay attention to
how a car bounces...
...it's easy to tell whether the
suspension is modified or not.
Besides, we've seen the Night Kids
so often on Akina lately.
I wonder why they come here.
Well, their leader, Nakazato,
was defeated...
...so I don't think anyone will ask
for a return match.
It serves him right.
After being defeated by the Eight-Six, Takeshi
won't be so influential in the team anymore.
What would you like to have?
Two coffees.
Okay.
Besides, Shingo, I heard that the driver
of the Speedstars' Eight-Six is young.
I don't know about him...
But if I defeat the Eight-Six, then me and
Takeshi's positions will be reversed.
I'll be the fastest of the Night Kids.
Are you going to do it, Shingo?
I know you're fast on the downhill,
but your opponent won't be so easy.
I'd be able to equal him by racing
normally, but that'd be boring.
I have an interesting idea that will guarantee
a 100 percent chance of winning.
Just wait and see...
...and I'll let him experience an
impressive and dangerous downhill.
There's only room for one downhill specialist
and that should be me.
The days of the Eight-Six are over.
I'll push it to the bottom of the valley
and send it to the junkyard.
Shoji Shingo of the Night Kids is the fastest
downhill driver in the Gunma area.
Where's Ryosuke?
My brother?
He's staying in his room, staring at
his computer every day.
I don't know what's so interesting.
No other Road Racer in Gunma could use a
computer to race faster, except my brother.
Hey, Hiroshi, what do you think would happen
if Akina's Eight-Six and my brother raced?
What do I think?
There's no way Ryosuke would be defeated.
The Eight-Six's secrets are out in the
open because of the last race.
All data was registered systematically
in Ryosuke's brain...
...and he must've completed
a winning simulation.
No other Road Racer knows
cars better than my brother.
His technique is outclassing.
I can't imagine my brother being defeated.
So...?
But I feel like the Eight-Six
won't be defeated either.
Beautiful high speed drift...
Exquisite braking control...
He's equally exceptional.
As a Road Racer, driving the FR layout,
maybe I'm addicted to his driving.
Keisuke...
If they race, one of them will lose.
I don't want my brother to be defeated...
...but for some reason, I also don't want
to see the Eight-Six defeated.
Odd, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
Did you get wet?
No.
Pick it up for a second.
Takumi, why don't we go somewhere again?
The mountains, highlands or
the beach would be nice, too.
It's summer break.
We'll share a lot of memories.
Sure.
If it's with you....
...I don't mind staying overnight.
When will you have a day off?
Sunday again...?
The schedule's not up yet.
Then why don't we go driving
on the next holiday?
With your car.
Don't go without telling
me next time, Takumi!
Ummm...do you mind if Itsuki
comes along, too?
Itsuki, too?
Yeah.
If you can arrange a girl for him,
it would be great.
He's a nice guy, but he's clumsy
about finding a girl.
You're a really good friend.
I don't mean to be like this, but...
Okay, I'll talk to my friends.
You will?
I'll find a pretty girl who matches Itsuki.
You look cool!
Maybe I'd better give it a try.
I'm getting better at using the parking
brake to let the rear skid.
Steering timing is the key.
So you use the parking
brake to start drifting.
But, Iketani, when I was sitting
next to Takumi...
...I didn't see him using
the parking brake at all.
Takumi has an advanced technique to initiate
the load-shift by only using the foot brake.
We have a long way to go
to achieve that.
We've been happy skidding our cars by stepping
on the gas pedal at a corner's exit.
But it's an elementary technique called
"power slide," and it's different from a drift.
In a real drift, like you see
Takumi doing...
...you enter a corner while skidding
and minimize the slide at the exit.
That's the fastest manner,
and it looks cool.
I see.
You must've studied a lot.
I had lots of time until my S13 returned.
I studied by reading a lot.
I'd like to try the sidespin.
I'm getting excited!
I've got the hang of it,
so I'll move to the next step.
I'll try the sidespin in a moderate
curve instead of a straightway.
Good luck, Iketani!
Watch out for other cars!
We'll join you later!
It's difficult to control a car freely.
I want to be like Takumi.
I want to sit next to Takumi again.
And it'd be really helpful if I let him drive
my car and watch how he drives.
I didn't notice that.
Where did he come from?
Dammit!
He tapped my bumper!
Don't screw with me!
You've gone too far!
I won't let you pass me!
Pass me if you can!
Akina Skate Ring
Speedstars?
I made it.
The load shifts forward just
before the turn-in...
...so the car loses control easily
by being tapped on the rear.
The stability of FR cars is so poor.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
LSD: Limited Slip
Differential
FR: Front Engine
Rear Wheel Drive
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
What do I want most right now?
Yes.
Time to be with Takumi.
I want to go dating more often,
and share lots of memories.
But even though it's summer break...
...Takumi is busy working, so we can't
see each other very often.
Even if we're dating and I'm close to him, he
looks away and doesn't pay attention to me.
Well, this'll take too long.
Next time on Initial D:
"FR Killing Death Match."
Next Time:
ACT.12 FR Killing Death Match!
That makes him mysterious and charming
though, don't you think?
Don't miss it.