Information　びょうそくでつたわるじだい
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
でもChoiceのしかたがわからない しげの
demo Choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love
なんてノンキなヤツにラリアート３かい
nante NONKI na YATSU ni ha RARIAATO sankai
マニュアルどおりにただだきあい
MANYUARU douri ni tada dakiai
あいがないことにきがつかない
ai ga nai koto ni kigatsukanai
ちつそくするまえにさけぼうぜHo!!!!!!!
chitsusoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!!!!
In the midnight dream
いきさえつかない　ねむれないまち
iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
すきもみせずにわらいあって
suki mo misezuni warai atte
うそさえSafety　ホントがEmpty
uso sae Safety  HONTO ga Empty
あぶないぐらいにwanna shut and break out!
abunai gurai ni wanna shut and break out!
Now we gotta start Let's get move
Let's move into the brand new world
Let's dive into the brand new trip
ひろいせかいにおびえてる
hiroi sekai ni obieteru
はじまったばかりの
hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat
きっとかがやく　around the world
kitto kagayaku around the world
Trip to the world
Yo! here we go unknown world へと
Yo! here we go unknown world he to
うまれたばっかりのたびびと
umareta bakari no tabibito
なれないあしどりもまたあいきょう
narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
キメるとこだけバシッと!
KIMEru toko dake BASHItto!
So many people in this world
ときにちゅうしょうとかもないわけじゃないけど
toki ni chuushou tokamonai wake ja nai kedo
ツマンナイとこはWarpしてこう
SHIMANNAI toko ha Warp shite kou
すじだけはとおしていきてる
suji dake ha tooshite ikiteru
That's our low!
I made it.
ACT.12
FR Killing Death Match!
That sonuvabitch... hit me on purpose!
I won't let you get away!
Akina's potato is keeping up with me?
That little...
Don't screw around with me!
His turn-in is unbelievably fast!
Brake lights...?
His brake lights are on during
high speed cornering?
Damn, I can't keep up with him.
He's got incredible technique!
The turn-in of that EG6 might
be faster than Takumi's.
Who the hell is he?
Thank you very much!
And he really pissed me off.
Braking while cornering?
And at high speed?
Yes.
I've never seen anything
like it before.
Really?  It happens often.
I brake in corners so often.
Oh shit, I'm too fast.
I'm scared, tap, tap.
We aren't having such a
low level conversation.
That EG6 cleared the corner
at a very high speed.
EG6?
It's the Civic.
A Civic.
Then why don't you
simply say Civic?
Although the Civic is FF,
it's popular among Road Racers.
It's got a 1.6 liter, non-turbo engine
like the Eight-Six...
...but it's very powerful thanks
to its VTEC engine.
Civics and Levin/Truenos have
been rivals for a long time.
You can't neglect the Civic because
you're driving an Eight-Six.
I can't yield to the Civic
because I drive the Levin!
Anyway, I can't believe how he braked after
a high speed entry into a corner.
He's using a left foot
braking technique.
Left foot braking?
You don't use that technique
with FR cars very often.
But you can use your left foot for braking
for sensitive control at the limit.
FF cars like the EG6 experience understeering
when you step on the gas pedal.
It's an advanced technique, when
while depressing the gas pedal...
...they use left foot braking to lessen the
rear load and stay on the ideal path.
If he used that, he must be
a really good FF driver.
He must be very fast.
He's fast, but that sonuva...
I managed to avoid an accident because
I practiced spinning using the parking brake.
My S13 could've been
"hospitalized" again.
He won't get away the
next time I see that EG6!
I'm home.
Hey.
Oh, you had a phone call a while ago.
From who?
I don't know.
It was a girl.
She was cute.
She said she'd call back.
How do you know if she's cute or
not by talking on the phone?
Being a man for a long time,
my instincts can tell.
Experience counts in both women and cars.
Well, good luck.
Shut up.
I'd better go to the meeting.
Hello, this is Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Hello, Takumi...?
Mogi...?
Sorry.
Were you sleeping?
It's about our plans...
Hey, this had better not
be a joke, Takumi.
If it turns out to be,
it'll end our friendship!
So she's coming with another girl?
It'll be alright.
Mogi definitely said
she'd bring her friend.
I wonder if she'll be cute?
Nice body or maybe incredibly beautiful?!
Well, well?!
I don't know. She's Mogi's
junior high friend.
Actually, I'm not so picky
about her looks.
If I keep my hopes too high,
I might be disappointed.
So you kept your promise, Takumi!
I'm so happy to have
a good friend like you!
You're overreacting...
Just watch.
With a girl by my side,
I'll be the fastest on Akina!
How dare you!
Shit!
My Levin, my...!
They should be here by now...
Takumi, did you wait long?
Mogi, don't surprise me like that.
I'll introduce you.
This is friend Saori.
This is Takumi and Itsuki.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
Cute babe.
So you're a Road Racer?
Me?  Yeah.
I'm on the team called
the Akina Speedstars.
And I'm number three or four.
Well, Akina's Levin is
well known in Gunma.
How cool!
What's a Road Racer?
Oh, come on.
Don't you know, Natsuki?
Road Racers are...
Way to go, Saori.
She's better than I hoped for.
Hey, Itsuki, watch out!
Should I drive?
No, it's okay.
Sorry about that.
It's a bad Road Racer habit.
How do you feel?
I'm fine now.
His driving is so rough.
Hey, Takumi and Natsuki!
This is great!
Why don't you guys take a ride?
They're getting along well, aren't they?
You know, I could take you guys home.
Oh, it's okay.
We haven't seen each other for a while,
so we want to talk more.
Itsuki, thank you.
It was fun.
See you again.
See ya.
S...Saori...
Saori, see you again!
Great, great, great!
She's the best!
I'm talking about Saori.
I feel so alive!
Saori!
Hey, drive carefully.
Don't worry, don't worry.
Thank you so much, Takumi!
She said "again."
I'll ask her to go driving.
Hey, look ahead!
Sorry, sorry!
Thank you very much!
Alright, is there anything else to do?
Work, work...
Itsuki's so excited.
I wonder if he found a girl...
I don't know.
If so, I won't forgive him
for getting ahead of me!
By the way, Takumi...
...do you feel like driving my S13?
It's refreshing to drive a
different car once in a while.
No, thanks.
I'll pass.
Besides, it's your precious...
I'm begging you, Takumi!
I want to learn from your driving.
Please!
Shingo, are you serious about
racing Akina's Eight-Six?
You'll see.
Well, let's go.
C'mon, Akina's Eight-Six.
I'm looking forward to seeing you...
Are you sure about this?
I'm begging you, Takumi.
Just drive normally and I'll be satisfied.
It'll be very helpful.
Come on, just this once!
I don't know...
I haven't driven other cars, so I don't
think I can drive it fast.
Iketani's only asking this much.
Why don't you drive?
That's right, Takumi!
Give him a little respect!
Alright then, just this once.
Don't expect too much, okay?
Oh, you will?
Yahoo!
Lucky you, Iketani.
Don't pass out, okay?
Don't worry, don't worry.
This is the second time.
Push it hard, Takumi.
Okay, we're going.
Right.
What should I do?
Well... how about braking drift?
Okay.
H...hey.
You're gonna do it right away...?
A...aren't we going too fast?
I wonder if Iketani will be alright.
Or once again...
I'll witness...
...the echoing death cry on the frightening
Mt. Akina downhill...
...as Iketani, in the third corner...
...p...p...p...passes out!
Will it happen again?
I...incredible.
He's drifting a car he's
driving for the first time.
Is my S13 actually this fast?
It's different from my car...
...but I've got the hang of
how to drive this car.
B...but you only cleared
the third corner...
Here comes the drift.
Drift...?
Then until now...?
I think I turned the corner
as I imagined.
Incredible...
He's so incredible...
I don't know what's going on.
They're back.
Hey, you're still conscious.
You've improved a bit.
So, Iketani, did you get any hints
for braking drift?
He?  Not a one.
I don't know what happened.
Say what?
What was the point of asking
Takumi for the favor then?
Even if you say so, Kenji...
...Takumi performs incredible
techniques so easily.
I "learned" that his level is totally different,
and I can't learn from him yet.
That's a big improvement.
An EG6!
I'm sure it's the one from last night.
Sonuva...
Hey, you're the one!
You hit my car from
behind, didn't you?!
Who are you?
Don't play innocent!
You remember this two-tone S13, don't you?
Oh, that one?
Don't give me that crap!
Apologize!  You could've caused
a big accident!
Gimme a break.
It was your fault.
Say what?
You were so slow I couldn't
predict your actions.
I didn't expect you to enter
the corner so slowly.
I couldn't brake in time,
and I touched your tail.
How dare you!
Stop, Iketani!
What an asshole!
Iketani's pride is torn to pieces!
If you want me to apologize,
we'll race by our rules...
...and if you win, I'll kneel
down to the ground.
By your rules?
What do you mean?
It's not so difficult.
We call it a gumtape death match.
Gumtape death match?
Just bind your right hand to the
steering wheel with gumtape.
That's the only rule.
We race under those conditions.
Bind the right hand to the
steering wheel with gumtape?
The left hand is free for shifting, right?
The right hand to the steering wheel...
You can't pass the steering wheel
from one hand to another!
You can't steer!
It's too risky!
I don't want to race you.
Oh, yeah.
I heard that there's a fast Eight-Six
downhill driver in the Speedstars.
I don't know who the brat is,
so why don't you send him out?
Tell the Eight-Six brat that I'll be waiting
here at 10:00pm next Saturday.
We'll settle everything with
a gumtape death match.
Catch ya later.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says “You gotta be wild & tough”
そう　たにんはかいざいしない
sou  tanin ha kaizai shinai
never stop　とまりたくない
never stop  tomari takunai
ぎせいになったあいがcryしても
gisei ni natta ai ga cry shite mo
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Peakめざしてsweep the winding street
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street
Beep beep!　けいこくおとはso cheap
Beep beep! keikoku oto ha so cheap
Sheepたちはみちあける
Sheep tachi ha michi akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streak my dream
Easyなmotivation
Easy na motivation
すべてはsimulation
subete ha simulation
にげてみたって
nigete mitatte
どこでもsafety zone
doko demo safety zone
なにかをてにいりて
nani ka wo te ni irete
なにかをわすれてく
nani ka wo wasureteku
せかいはこわれても
sekai ha kowarete mo
かわらない
kawaranai
Beasty shout
だれのてにさえおえかい
dare no te ni sae oenai
はげしいゆめ
hageshii yume
じかんさえもいまこえてく
jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream
やみをはりさいていく
yami o hari saiteiku
Life a streak to the peak
せかいじゅうの
sekai juu no
こごえきったよるをけしてく
kogoe kitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream
みちをひらいてく
michi o hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
コンマゼロイチびょうでKnock down
KONMA ZERO ICHI byou de Knock down
よいんおこしきえてこうto the next town
yoin nokoshi kiete kou to the next town
ほこりまう
hokori mau
はいしゃちにはう
haishachi ni hau
i理屈だけのノーガキ達
rikutsu dake no NOOGAKI-tachi
じゃまクサイからシカトしていこう
jama KUSAI kara SHIKATO shite ikou
StreakerさっていくStreetのむこう
Streaker satteiku Street no mukou
Something they would know
Rage your dream
つづくはてないみちを
tsudzuku hatenai michi wo
あいもかこうもふりむかず
ai mo kakou mo furimukazu
FF: Front Engine
Front Wheel Drive
Gumtape: Duct tape
ゆける
yukeru
あなたかがやいてる
anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream
いまをいきている
ima wo ikiteiru
Love fortune: "Your relationship
will develop further next week."
Oh, Itsuki, something good happened?
Finally, I'll have a girlfriend!
Really?  Omedetou!
So, who is it?
The girl we double dated...
Oh, Saori.
Right.
There's more to this fortune.
"Don't be persistent or you might
be in trouble, so be careful."
Huh?
Next time on Initial D:
"Itsuki's First Date."
Next Time:
Itsuki's First Date
Don't miss it!