This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
INITIAL
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...deserves a lariat three times.
We make love according to the manuals.
We don't notice the lack of love.
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho!!!
In the midnight dream.
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
We smile without dropping our guard.
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.  Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
You're afraid of a big world.
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Ho! Here we go to an unknown world.
You're a newborn traveler.
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Let's warp uninteresting things...
..and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
Sonuva...
Hey, you're the one!
You hit my car from
behind, didn't you?!
Gimme a break.
It was your fault.
Say what?
You were so slow, I couldn't
predict your actions.
I didn't expect you to enter
the corner so slowly.
I couldn't brake in time,
and I touched your tail.
How dare you!
Stop, Iketani!
If you want me to apologize,
we'll race by our rules...
...and if you win, I'll kneel
down to the ground.
By your rules?
What do you mean?
It's not so difficult.
We call it a gumtape death match.
Gumtape death match?
I heard that there's a fast Eight-Six
downhill driver in the Speedstars.
Tell the Eight-Six brat that I'll be waiting
here at 10:00pm next Saturday.
Catch ya later.
What's with him?
He challenged Takumi.
But he doesn't know Takumi's face.
Takumi, take his challenge, whether
it's a gumtape death match or not!
Defeat the guy, and make
him kneel down!
Don't be stupid, it's
too risky, Itsuki!
He won't be able to steer
during the race.
But, Iketani, Takumi has defeated
the FD and 32!
He won't lose just because
of some customized rule!
Idiot, that guy must've practiced
a lot under that rule.
Takumi, don't race at such
a disadvantage, no matter what.
I don't have any intention of racing.
Yeah, that's good.
Just ignore him.
Itsuki's First Date
What?
A gumtape death match?
Yes.
That's ridiculous.
And what about Takumi?
He's calm and uninterested like usual.
He doesn't feel like racing.
I want Takumi to race!
He'll outrun that jerk, make him
kneel down, and we'll feel great!
He's driving a Civic, the archrival
of Levins and Truenos.
Yeah, when we were young,
we used gears and rules...
...but the gumtape death match was
one of the most dangerous battles.
Is a gumtape death match
really that dangerous?
I don't quite get it.
Itsuki, get in your car
and give it a try.
Then you'll see.
Well...
Okay, steer full to either left or right, while keeping
your right hand on the steering wheel.
O...okay.
I can't turn any farther!
Okay, leave the steering wheel as it is
and get out of the car.
Okay.
Now see how far you steered.
O...okay.
It only turned that much?!
I thought I steered a lot.
See?
How would you turn in the corners?
You couldn't drive in the mountain passes.
You can only use steering
to initiate the turn.
You must slide the rear tires
to clear the corners.
All of them.
But Takumi's good at drifting,
so he'll be able to pull it off.
It's not that easy.
He can't countersteer, which
makes drift control difficult.
If he oversteers a bit,
he'll go into a spin.
But if he understeers at the entrance,
it'll be over.
This rule gives FF cars an advantage.
The opponent is an EG6, right?
Yes.
Since the EG6 has an FF layout, he can cope
with oversteering using the gas pedal...
...and he can also minimize the "under"
by using the parking brake.
In order for an FR like the
Eight-Six to race safely...
...just like a circus tightrope walker...
...he has to drift throughout the race
and maintain extreme control.
He'd better not do it.
Damn, if he heard that,
he might become interested.
Umm, Manager...
Hey, it's Kenji...
Iketani, it's about that jerk
from the other day.
I did a little investigating.
He's Shoji Shingo of the Myogi Night Kids.
Shoji Shingo of the Night Kids...?
He's supposed to be their number two...
...but he claims to be the fastest
of the Night Kids on the downhill.
But he doesn't choose normal means
to accomplish his goal...
...so the other members
don't trust him.
He especially doesn't get along with
their leader, Nakazato Takeshi.
I see.
So he wants to defeat Takumi
to gain influence in the Night Kids.
He's going around spreading
a nasty rumor.
What?  A rumor...?
Yeah.
"The Speedstars are scared, and
we won't accept his challenge."
It doesn't say anything about it
being a gumtape death match.
So we're the only ones who'll look bad.
What an asshole!
Yeah.
He's trying to drag Takumi into
racing him, no matter what.
Takumi...
M...me...?
Means nothing to me.
I won't accept his challenge.
That's good.
Even if you've been challenged,
it's too ridiculous to accept.
Don't sweat it.
O...okay.
So, what about the battle
with the Eight-Six?
I'm ready any time.
It's their move now.
Wait and see.
I'll drag that Eight-Six brat out.
It'll be an interesting battle.
Takeshi...!
Shingo, you seem to be planning something.
I don't care what you do...
...just don't disgrace the name
of the Night Kids, okay?
What's so funny?
Aren't you the one who's disgraced
our name already?
Say what?
Who was the one who was totally outrun
by a brat in a dated Eight-Six?
And in a high powered 32, at that?
Shingo...
A loser should go bark somewhere else.
I don't want you preaching to me
as if you'll be our leader forever.
Nakazato, I'll avenge you.
You should thank me.
Shingo, you'll eventually see
how great the Eight-Six is.
Man, Takeshi is on the way out.
Really, he was so lame.
From now on, the leader of the
Night Kids is you, Shingo.
Before that, I'll send Akina's
Eight-Six to the junkyard.
Hello, this is Takeuchi...
Is this Saori?
Oh, Itsuki...?
Sure, I remember you.
Go driving to Akina Lake?
Okay.
I'll be waiting at the bus stop at 1:00pm.
Yeah.  Bye.
Alright!
My 18 years of life without
a girlfriend is finally over!
I'll do it!
Here.
Oh, Dad...
What?
Is a gumtape death match...
Nothing.
Never mind.
Gumtape death match, huh?
You're so...
...good at driving.
If it's with you....
...I don't mind staying overnight.
I think of her a lot...
Thank you very much!
Where's Itsuki?
He was washing a car a while ago.
I wonder where he went.
I see, I see.
So...
...you're neglecting work
in a place like this.
I...I'm just taking a break.
It's unusual to see you reading.
T...that's...
Let's see...
Love manual?
How to romance a girl?
Well, that's...
Reading a book like this means...
...you've got a date?
Y...yes.
With that babe, Saori,
you talked about?
How dare you get ahead of me!
I bought the book on the way home yesterday,
and I've been studying hard.
When it comes to things like this,
I don't think I can depend on you.
You're straightforward.  It can't
be helped because it's true.
Things are so convenient these days.
We had to find out everything
by ourselves in my time.
Let me see...
"It's an established fact, to get close
to a girl by the third date..."
"...create a romantic mood
for the first kiss..."
I'm perfectly prepared, Manager.
So I'm taking a day off,
like I told you earlier.
So that's what it's all about.
I guess it's alright.
I'm envious of you!
This is it.
Saori...?
Over here, Itsuki!
Gorgeous!
Welcome...
I don't need any gas...
I want to hear your answer about
the gumtape death match.
You told the Eight-Six guy
about it, didn't you?
Yeah.
He has no intention of racing you.
That's what he said.
That's funny.
Akina's Eight-Six driver is a coward.
The gumtape death match
scared him off, huh?
That doesn't matter.
I'll do anything to make him race.
So cute!
We Road Racers don't say, "turn into the curve,"
we say, "tackle the corner."
I want to get a license.
Why don't you?
I'll teach you how.
Okay, I'll think about it.
Akina Fuji...
It's so beautiful!
"Girls react to the mood.
Do the first kiss in a romantic setting."
First kiss...
It's the right chance!
Go for it, Itsuki!
Itsuki!
I'm sorry.
The mood is heavy.
I'm in trouble.
Found you.
An EG6...
He tapped my bumper.
Does it mean I should
get out of the way?
He's right on my butt!
Shit, I have to be decisive
in front of Saori!
Saori, I'm gonna speed up a little bit.
Please bear with it for a while, okay?
STOP!
It's a battle between Road Racers...
...I can't stop!
At...at least Saori...
Hey, we have a problem!
Itsuki had an accident!
Where?
On Akina's mountain pass!
He was taken to the city hospital!
You two go check on him!
Right.
Are you alright, Itsuki?
Senpai, Takumi.
What happened?
They're overreacting.
It's not as bad as it looks...
...but they're keeping me
here to be sure.
What about Saori?
She was with you, wasn't she?
She only got a scratch,
so she went home already.
I steered hard so I wouldn't
crush the passenger side.
What happened to the car...
...your Eight-Five?
It spun just right, so it only suffered
minor damage to the trunk.
It's done.
Take care.
Thank you.
I was going downhill on Akina,
and an EG6 tailgated me.
An EG6?
Him again?
Probably, because it was a red EG6.
I was suddenly bumped
from behind in a corner.
That asshole did it again!
Shit!
I'll do it!
Whether it's a gumtape death
match or not, I'll do it!
Takumi, wait!
Takumi...
S...sorry!
Don't be taken in by his strategy!
A gumtape death match is too dangerous!
Don't do it, Takumi!
I won't lose, no matter what.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says "You gotta be wild and tough."
I don't let others meddle in.
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
The sheep should make room.
`Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin' my dream.
Your motivation is easy.
Everything is simulated.
Even if you want to break out,
you'll end up in a safety zone.
You obtain something while
you lose something else.
It won't change, even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang, another round, never slow down.
Knock down in comma zero one second.
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Dust rises and the loser falls down to the ground.
The puffery, full of logic...
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
In the never-ending street...
...without looking back at your love or your past...
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
You live in the present.
You've caused Itsuki to have an accident.
You're playing dirty, aren't you, Shingo?
I don't care, as long as
Akina's Eight-Six shows up.
Come on...
I know my chances of winning the
gumtape death match are 100%.
It won't be fun to simply defeat him,
so I'll arrange an interesting show.
N...next time on Initial D:
"Improving Genius of Drift!"
I'll make him experience
true fear in the downhill.
Initial
Next Time:
Improving Genius of Drift!
Don't miss it!