This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love nante...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
Now, we gotta start.  Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Kimeru took dake bashitto
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
That's our law.
I was suddenly bumped
from behind in a corner.
That asshole did it again!
Shit!
I'll do it!
Whether it's a gumtape death
match or not, I'll do it!
Takumi, wait!
Takumi...
S...sorry!
Don't be taken in by his strategy!
A gumtape death match
is too dangerous!
Don't do it, Takumi!
I won't lose, no matter what.
Improving Genius of Drift!
Welcome!
Welcome!  Please move
the car over here.
High octane or regular?
Welcome!
Need your ashtray cleaned?
Takumi's going to accept
the gumtape death match?
That's bad, extremely bad!
He got pissed because
Itsuki was hospitalized.
I understand how he feels,
but it's still too reckless.
It's Saturday.
Where's Takumi?
He took the day off.
With Itsuki in the hospital,
we're super busy.
No matter how good Takumi is, accepting
a gumtape death match without practice...
I'll talk to Takumi after work.
I have to stop him somehow.
Sorry, but can you help
us out for a while?
Welcome!
"If you lose your sense of duty to a friend,
our society will come to an end."
It's natural for Takumi to feel that way.
I don't think he'll listen.
Maybe we should let him try.
No, he's at too much of a disadvantage
against an FF car.
I'm so surprised you called.
It's the first time you've called me.
A lot of things made me mad.
After thinking about so many things,
I started thinking of you.
I felt like I could relax.
I'm glad you did.
How are Itsuki's injuries?
He was wearing his seat belt.
It's not as bad as it looks...
...but he has to go through a lot of checkups,
so he has to stay in the hospital.
I'd better go see him.
Yeah, he'll appreciate that.
You look a little scary today.
Sorry.
You're not yourself.
But I like you this way, too.
Takahashi
Brother!
What's up?
Akina's Eight-Six...
...is going to have a gumtape death match
against the Night Kids number two driver!
What?
Moreover, the opponent is an EG6.
What the hell is he thinking?
The gumtape death match is
a trap to kill FR cars!
It's only common sense that
an FR won't defeat an FF!
Common sense, yes...
But he's the driver.
If he drives, he'll blow mere common
sense out the window.
What should we do?
Should we go?
Excuse me...
I'm closing the store.
I already sold out of
fried tofu and Ganmo.
We didn't come for that today.
Do you know where Takumi is?
Takumi?  No idea.
He took the Eight-Six this afternoon,
and he hasn't come home.
I don't know where he went.
Sir, have you ever tried a gumtape
death match before?
Yeah, a long time ago.
What if Takumi tried it?
Takumi...?
I don't know.
He's not very good, so he might end up
at the bottom of the valley.
Iketani, let's go look somewhere else.
Okay.
Sir, if he returns, tell him not to do
the gumtape death match!
Excuse me.
Gumtape death match, huh?
Shingo, let's get going.
Yeah.
Wait for me, Eight-Six of Akina.
There's no way I can lose.
Your Eight-Six will be
smashed into Akina's cliff.
Well, see you.
Call me again, okay?
Sure.
Now then...
So many people are here already...
I don't like them around here.
We came here to stop Takumi.
Here come the Night Kids!
Oh, only the slow S13 dude?
What happened to the Eight-Six?
Ignore him.
I wonder when Takumi will get here.
He's gonna be here soon,
it's almost time.
Here comes Akina's Eight-Six!
Fujiwara Tofu Shop...?
Is this some kind of joke?
Takumi, it's not too late.
Don't race in such a
ridiculous battle as this!
Why not?
I won't lose to a guy like him.
He's driving an FF car.
Don't you get it?
Oh, the kid from the other day...
You're wasting my time.
What're you talking about?
Don't tell me you're
thinking about pulling out.
Iketani, I won't quit,
no matter what.
It's almost ten...
It's about time to begin.
Takumi, I believe in you.
You will win.
Please win!
I wonder if he'll be okay.
Maybe we should've forced him to stop?
All we can do now is trust him.
It's okay.
The finish is ready.
Shall we start?
Okay.
I'm counting down!
Ten seconds!
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go!
It's begun.
Don't push too hard, Takumi.
Shingo intentionally laid off the
accelerator and stayed behind.
So that he can watch the Eight-Six
fall from a cliff, right?
Only a genius can avoid an accident
in an FR under these rules.
That Eight-Six won't reach
the third corner.
Don't get too confident.
The B16A engine is a masterpiece.
If I'd been serious, that dated 4A-G engine couldn't
have outrun me during the start dash.
Let me see how many
corners you can clear.
But is it really possible to turn with one
hand taped to the steering wheel?
There they are!
Hey, the Eight-Six looks
like it's going too fast!
This is bad.
He seems slower than usual.
You seem quite eager... but aren't
you forgetting something?
There you go.
You're finished.
I made it.  How lucky.
I thought the tendon in my arm
was about to snap...
H...he recovered.
Incredible!  I thought he was done for!
I can't watch.
Hey, hey, hey, where
did all your pep go?
I can't just stand here.
Let's follow them!
T...there's no way, Iketani!
We can't catch them with our skill!
I'm not thinking about catching them.
If Takumi is involved in
an accident and gets hurt...
...we have to help him
as quickly as possible!
Hey, I'm coming with you!
I see.  I've got this battle
figured out!
Shit, how can he...?
He's clearing corners with
minimum countersteering.
I don't believe it.
The gumtape death match can't
be mastered on the first try.
The more conservative you drive, the greater
the chance you'll fall into a pit.
I practiced so many times keeping
my hand on the steering wheel...
...before I could turn into the
corner with tape on.
In a long straightaway, engine
power is more significant.
When it comes to a normally
aspirated 1.6-liter DOHC engine...
...no engine in the world
can surpass the B16A.
The ecstasy at the sound of the engine
revving up rapidly into the red zone...
I'd die for it.
It's awesome!
Do you get it?  If I feel like it,
I can pass you anytime I want.
Hey, hey, you'd better hurry.
Why don't you drive harder?
My heart pounds every
time I clear a corner.
I'm afraid I'll see a wrecked Eight-Six.
Quit saying that, it'll bring bad luck.
As long as nothing happens...
Yeah...
Besides, Takumi's potential is surprising.
I can clear corners
at my desired speed.
The car can go faster
if I don't steer too much.
Shit, why doesn't my
pressure disturb him?
At the beginning, he was
driving unsteadily...
...but his driving is getting sharper and
sharper, as if he's a different driver.
Here they come.
They're close.
I guess they've both survived so far.
If he couldn't get this far,
my expectations were too high.
Then the Eight-Six wouldn't
deserve to be my target.
There!
Oh shit, someone's coming up!
Four wheel drift within the lane without
crossing the centerline...?!
What incredible technique!
And he pulled it off so easily.
He wasn't even fazed
by the oncoming car.
Is his hand still taped?
Has it come off already?
I think he figured out this
death match very early.
Which means...
You don't have to depend
on steering...
...you can also clear a corner
by shifting the weight.
He learned it quickly.
Man, what a guy!
He's definitely improved.
Shit, this is totally unexpected.
Now that he's made it this far, I have to
accept that it's not just luck.
But I'm not as easy as Takeshi.
As long as I win, I don't care how.
Don't blame me.
The Eight-Six of Akina will simply turn
to scraps of metal in a junkyard.
Unbelievable!
After he spun out, he turned 360 degrees,
and kept going as if nothing happened!
Damn, it's gotta be luck.
It must be coincidence.
Shit.
If it were a high speed corner,
it would've been finished.
It doesn't matter.
I'll win this battle.
It's a bummer that
I couldn't trash it...
...but I won't lose if it's a speed match,
because I'm familiar with this rule.
I'll just outrun you.
Now I'm pissed.
He did that on purpose.
I won't lose to a lowlife
like you, no matter what!
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
My pride says "You gatta be wild and tough."
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
Never stop tomaritakunai
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Sheep wa michi wo akero
Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin my dream.
Easy na motibation
Subete wa simulation
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
Tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
I won't forgive him,
no matter what.
I won't lose, no matter what.
Who is it?
Takumi?
I won't forgive him,
no matter what.
No matter what...
...I WON'T LOSE!
Now, to continue.
Next time on Initial D:
"Angry Takumi's Maniacal Drive!"
I won't lose...
Initial
Next Time:
Angry Takumi's Maniacal Drive!
Don't miss it!