This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
INITIAL
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...deserves a lariat three times.
We make love according to the manuals.
We don't notice the lack of love.
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho!!!
In the midnight dream.
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
We smile without dropping our guard.
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.  Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
You're afraid of a big world.
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Ho! Here we go to an unknown world.
You're a newborn traveler.
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Let's warp uninteresting things...
..and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
Don't blame me.
The Eight-Six of Akina will simply turn
to scraps of metal in a junkyard.
Now I'm pissed.
He did that on purpose.
I won't lose to a lowlife
like you, no matter what!
Angry Takumi's Maniacal Drive!
Watch out!
He didn't mind hitting the guardrail!
And he used the reaction
to initiate his drift!
What's that Eight-Six driver thinking?!
No way.
The Eight-Six is gaining on me.
That's impossible!
Is he trying to kill himself, or what?
That Eight-Six driver has gone nuts.
If an ordinary driver gets angry...
...he'll keep making mistakes
and won't be able to run fast.
But he's different.
His natural driving sense allows him
to push the Eight-Six to its limit.
The angrier he gets, the faster he drives.
The result of this race is obvious, Shingo.
Shit...
Although I'm pushing my EG6 to the limit...
How could this be happening?
It's strange.
I've never been so afraid of attacking
the downhill before.
He's on my tail!
I don't believe this.
The EG6 is the best of its class, but it's
being pushed hard by an Eight-Six...
It has nothing to do with being fast or
slow, it's fundamentally different...
That Eight-Six is a monster.
But I'll be fine as long as
I don't let him overtake me.
After I clear the five hairpin curves,
the finish is near.
This battle is mine!
I won't let you take the inside.
Is he going to hit me this time?!
Dammit!
I thought he was going to hit me...
...but what was that cornering just now?
He stayed inside at full speed,
and passed me so easily.
How could I be overtaken?!
I don't get it!
Will Takumi be alright?
I don't think we have
to worry anymore.
We've come this far, so he must've
figured out this death match.
He might have pulled away from that EG6.
If so, that annoying jerk from the Night Kids
must be sweating a lot.
Yeah.
He might be regretting challenging
Takumi already.
I dragged him into this
gumtape death match.
If I lose, I'll be the laughingstock
of the team.
I'll keep my reputation by
ending this race with a tie.
The power of my B16A will make our cars run
side by side in this short straightaway.
You can't get away.
The end of this battle...
...will be a double crash!
One's coming!
Which one?
It's gotta be the EG6.
The Eight-Six?!
W...what's that Eight-Six's problem?
He almost killed me.
What happened?
The EG6 isn't coming.
W...what happened to Shingo?
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream, kaze no naka de mabushiku
Rage your dream, shining bright in the wind...
...sakebu anata yumetachi to
...you shout with your dream.
Rage your dream. kodou tomaru kurai ni
Rage your dream. It almost stops my heartbeat.
I can feel. Tsuyoku kanjiteru
I can feel it so strongly.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang another round, never slow down.
My EG6...
Could that be Takumi...?!
No!
You lost it?
You're lucky the damage isn't too severe...
Hey, are you alright?
Any injuries?
Get in my car.
I'll take you to the hospital.
It's quicker than calling an ambulance.
You don't have to do that much.
Just make a phone call.
Don't be stubborn.
It hurts, doesn't it?
When we have an accident, we're
supposed to help each other.
We're locals, so we know
an emergency hospital.
Thanks.  I appreciate it.
He's incredible.
Who the hell is that Eight-Six driver...?
Takumi, Takumi!
Are you awake?!
Come down here!
What?
I'm awake, 'cause it's that time.
Just come down, quick!
So, what're those?
You must've hit the car somewhere.
There are three scratches that look like the
kind made by touching the guardrail.
I don't remember anything.
It must've been you.
I didn't drive it yesterday,
so it was you!
Look at those scratches
on the bumper and fender!
It's true!
Who did that?!
You did!
Ouch.
Why'd you do that?
What?
Come to think of it, I barely remember
hitting something with the car.
What's wrong with you?
You're too young to be senile.
I raced this really disgusting guy yesterday,
and he pissed me off in the middle of it.
So I got really mad for some reason, but then
I came home and went to bed quickly.
I don't know how it happened, but you aren't
very good if you hit something with your car.
If it had been me, I wouldn't have hit
anything, no matter what.
So, did you win?
Yeah.
I see.
Is it alright to do that, Itsuki?
The examination didn't show anything bad...
...so I'll be leaving the hospital soon.
These flowers are for you.
I'll arrange them...
Arigato.
I heard all about it, Takumi.
You won the gumtape death match!
Yeah.
You're incredible, Takumi!
You can handle FR killer rules.
You're really a genius.
Itsuki, I wanted to win that battle,
no matter what.
Not just because he pissed me off...
...but also because I didn't want to lose.
I've never felt like that before.
You're becoming more and more
like a Road Racer.
No, it's n...nothing like that.
Okay, once I get out of the hospital,
I'll improve my technique.
That way I won't disgrace the name
of Akina's Levin/Trueno pair.
What're you guys talking about?
Oh, nothing.
By the way, what about Saori?
Is she doing fine?
Is she alright?
Yeah, she told me
to say hello.
Oh, really?
Okay, once I'm out of the hospital,
let's all go driving together again!
Sure.
Yeah.
It's good to know that Itsuki's fine.
And his Eight-Five will be returned soon.
I... lied to him a little.
Saori told me that she was really scared
when the accident happened.
She doesn't want to remember
that moment, so...
So, even though she knows Itsuki's a nice guy,
she wants to leave things behind.
Saori won't come after all...
Dammit!
Road Racers don't need a girl!
Hey, what's up?
I'm gonna take the car to a body shop, but
I wanted to see your aged face before that.
Takumi hit the car really hard.
But in that race, it was unavoidable.
That idiot.
But it's a good sign.
You're acting strange.
Your car's fender is dented
and you're still smiling.
His driving style changed.
He was good, but he lacked something.
He's trying to drive fast.
He broke through a wall.
How do you know, Bunta?
I know because I look at
the Eight-Six every day.
I can see how he drives so well.
Is that so?
I'll stop by on the way home, so
let's have a drink later, Yuichi.
See ya.
Bye.
A crazy son... and a crazy father.
He hasn't changed a bit.
Kamameshi Restaurant
I couldn't help stopping the car.
I don't have any dirty thoughts,
but I can't leave her alone.
Well, I...I don't want you
to think I'm suspicious.
I'm just curious about
what happened to your car.
I don't really know what happened.
I tried starting it many times,
but the engine won't start.
If you don't mind, I'll take a look.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
In cases like this, it's probably
an electrical problem.
Let's see...
S13...
Speedstars...?
Can you fix it?
Yeah.
Man, I've never been so close to
a woman other than my mom!
Oh no, my heart's gonna burst!
She's ultra cute!
Smells nice.
I'm smelling a babe for the
first time in my life...
Oh no, what if I smell of sweat...?!
Okay, I think it'll run.
Start the motor.
Alright.
It started!
Great!
Thank you very much.
You really saved me.
It was nothing.
That's not true.
I admire people who are
good with machines.
I'll make it up to you later.
How can I contact you?
It's okay.  You don't have to
worry about it.
I see.
Damn!
This could be the only chance God
will give me in my entire life...!
I'm an idiot!
Stupid, moron!
I'm such an IDIOT!
Ummm, excuse me.
Here.
I'm Sato Mako.
Call me.
Mune ni nokoru nanigenai kotoba dakega
Only casual words remained in my heart.
Mayoi michi wo nukeru basho shitteita
I knew the place to free me from my delusion.
Anata ni deatta hi kara nanika ga kawarihajimete
Something started to change since the day I met you.
When I finally noticed, I had been
standing dazed for thirty minutes.
Itsushika koko ni tatteita
I realized that I kept standing here.
That's for your love.
This isn't a dream.
Omoide ni kaeru hodo tsuyoi wake ja nai kedo
It wasn't a memory so strong to recall.
I met an angel under
a restaurant sign...
Yorisotta ano koro ni
When we got close...
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Bloom red like a rose.
The Kamameshi sign and the
restaurant does exist.
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
...into the bright future.
Let's make it sure over and over.
This passion will be eternal.
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
The flower of miracles.
You appeared before me so suddenly,
like a bright flash of light.
I lost my heart to your beauty!
Hey, Iketani, what happened?
I can't live without you!
Are you a queen or an angel
who fills my heart?
It's no use.  He's completely
in his own world.
Next time on Initial D:
"The Angels of Usui Mountain."
Angel...?!
Oh, my sweet Mako!
Initial
Next Time:
The Angels of Usui Mountain
Don't miss it!