This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love nante...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
Now, we gotta start.  Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Kimeru took dake bashitto
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
That's our law.
You're hopeless!
So lame!
Your driving sucks!
Wataru hasn't improved at all.
Yeah.
Hey, here it comes!
Oh no.
Hey, clear the road!
Hurry, it's almost here!
Watch the best driver carefully.
Wow, it's awesome.
No one can copy that.
Don't worry.
Overtake it.
We're gonna pass an oncoming
car at the exit of the corner.
Open the inside!
Next, no oncoming car.
Get 5 cm closer to the inside.
It's sandy.
Just right, and you're in a good
mood and driving well.
No one can defeat you now.
The Angels of Usui Mountain
N...no way!
A girl you met for the first time
gave you her phone number?!
I can't believe that!
Something's definitely wrong.
That's right, Iketani!
Life isn't that easy!
I...I...
A Road Racer doesn't need a girl!
Besides, it doesn't sound like you if there's
nothing wrong with this kind of situation.
What do you mean it doesn't
sound like me, Kenji?
Are you making fun of me?
I don't mean it like that.
It just sounds too good to be true.
I hate it.
I don't like your envious thoughts.
Her long brown hair that waved in the wind...
Her charming eyes when she turned to me...
God must have sent an angel
to a guy who works hard!
I'll go to Karuizawa to see
Mako tomorrow.
Alright, back to work.
Hey, why don't we follow him
to see how cute she is?
Yeah, let's go.
We've got to see this girl.
But what if Iketani notices us?
Don't worry.
Iketani can't focus on anything
else right now.
I've got to check out
this girl called Mako.
Welcome!
Hey, don't get in Iketani's way.
We won't bother him!
When he gets dumped,
we'll cry together.
For the sake of our friendship.
Gets dumped, you say...?
She can't be as good looking as he says.
He tends to exaggerate, and
he easily convinces himself.
You're right.
I think it was when we were
in middle school...
We went to Akina Lake to fish.
We didn't catch anything until I caught
a small one just before we went home.
He was so excited, and said...
..."It's so big!" out loud.
It was this small.
Strangers came to see it.
I was so embarrassed at that time.
Iketani can really exaggerate things.
Kenji, take a look!
Damn, I was so absorbed in talking,
I wasn't paying attention to my right foot.
I was supposed to follow him,
but I caught up with him.
Sorry, Iketani!
Forgive me.
We just wanted to see
what Mako looks like.
It's true.
We have no intention of bothering
you on your date.
Don't be mad.
We'll turn around at the next interchange.
It can't be helped.
You don't have to leave.
I don't mind introducing you to her.
Really?
Great!
But...
...don't follow us after that,
or I will get mad.
Okay.
So...
...they're my friends.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sato Mako.
H...hi.
H...hello.
Well, Mako...
Okay.
Are we dogs or something?
It's not a dream.
I don't believe it.
I'm so shocked.
How could Iketani find such a cute girl?
Road Racers don't need a girl.
Kenji, why don't we cry together?
What do you mean?
Are you saying I'll never find a girl?
It was just a joke!
What should we do now?
Well...
Karuizawa isn't the place for three guys
to hang out this time of year.
Why don't we go to Usui's mountain pass?
S...sorry.
Do you have a favorite car, Mako?
It's not quite my favorite...
...but I used to dream of
the previous model RX-7.
The FC?
You have good taste.
You're a Road Racer, aren't you?
Well...can you tell?
I usually try to drive like everyone else.
And... What do you think of Road Racers?
I think it's alright, because
I also like cars.
Really?
Road Racers are better at driving
than ordinary people.
If you have money, you
can buy a good car...
...but you can't buy technique.
I prefer someone who can use
technique when needed...
...to someone who has
an expensive imported car.
She's great.
She's my ideal girl.
So this is Usui's mountain pass...
This is the first time I've seen it, and it's a much
harder winding road than I imagined.
It's incredible.
It's one corner after another,
and the road is narrow.
It's nothing like Akina.
I wonder who's the fastest on Usui.
Umm...you are...
Y...yes...?
From a man's point of view...
...if there's a girl who likes mountain passes,
and tries to be a Road Racer...
...what would you think about that?
Sil-Eighty?
Yeah, the blue Sil-Eighty is said
to be the fastest.
Don't be surprised by this, though...
The driver is a woman.
A woman?!
Female Road Racer?
Y...yeah.
I like it.
I think it's okay.
It's great.
A female Road Racer would
be wonderful to talk to.
Is that so?
Yeah.
I see.  I get it.
She wants to be a Road Racer.
And her dream car is the FC.
A girl driving a Sil-Eighty...?
What's a Sil-Eighty?
Is it an import?
No.
The Sil-Eighty is a 180 with
a Silvia front  on it.
A Silvia and a 180 are combined,
so it's called a Sil-Eighty.
And the driver is a girl, and she's the
fastest on Usui's mountain pass.
I want to see this.
If you wait until nightfall, you'll be able
to see it on Usui's mountain pass.
But don't even think about challenging her,
because none of the locals can defeat her.
It's called the Akina Speedstars.
I assembled the team, and we have
the fastest driver on Akina.
He's my junior worker.
Speaking of the skill,
I guess I'd be second.
What's wrong, Mako?
Oh, nothing at all.
Sorry.
I must be boring you with
all this talk about cars.
No, not at all.
I like cars a lot, so it's fun.
Really?
That's good.
Ah, do you think drift is cool, too?
Well... a little.
You have to drive hard
like me to master that.
It's a dangerous technique.
Are you good at drifting?
A little...
I'm happy for some reason.
You are...?
Thank you.  It was fun today.
Ah, Mako...
Yes?
Are you...
Well...
Is there someone you're
going out with now...?
Well...
Do you have anyone?
I... don't have a boyfriend.
So, please call me again, Iketani.
Hey, Iketani...
Can you hear me?
Iketani, get a grip.
I'm...
Why're you guys still here?
We were concerned about you,
so we couldn't go home.
So how was it?
Did it go well?
Today is such a wonderful day!
Let's go eat.
It doesn't happen very often,
but it's gonna be my treat.
And it's not a bad idea to take a look at
the Usui guys' driving, too.
I guess it went well.
So miracles do happen.
Pretty good.
Everyone on Usui is highly skilled.
Hey, Takumi...
...you'd never seen a mountain pass
other than Akina, right?
How was it?
"How was it?"
I wasn't driving, so I don't know.
Are you sure?
You looked so serious.
I did?
Your eyes looked totally
different from now.
I can't believe they're
of the same person.
What do you say?
Do you think you can drive it?
I can't tell unless I try.
Here it comes!
The Sil-Eighty?
Nonstop counter drift?
What the hell?
She's really good.
See that?
The road is narrow,
so it looked so exciting.
I talked big and told Mako
that I'm good at drifting...
...but in reality, I panic when
the rear starts to skid.
This is bad.
I've gotta practice hard,
or my angel will be gone!
Let's go down.
Okay.
Every mountain pass has
an incredible driver.
Hey, look... Iketani
is driving so fast.
There are three in here,
so I can't keep up.
You'd better keep your distance.
The rhythm is bad.
Something's wrong with his car.
Do you think something's gonna happen?
I don't mean that something
will happen, but probably...
Probably?
He screwed up, just like you said!
Just like Takumi said.
Oh shit, a car is coming!
That was close.
Who's that idiot?
The rear skidded, he got scared, released
the gas pedal, and oversteered.
That's the most uncool spin
only an amateur would do.
Hey, 13 dude!
If you don't move your car quickly,
you'll endanger other cars!
I'm moving it now.
It's so embarrassing!
How uncool.
Let's pretend to be strangers.
I'm really sor...
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Usui Mountain's fastest driver is...
...Mako in her Sil-Eighty!
I feel like I could die.
He took the day off?
He didn't even call.
That workaholic, Iketani?
I don't believe it.
He must've been really shocked.
He didn't talk at all afterwards.
When we stopped at a service
area to use the restroom...
...he looked out of it, and
his eyes weren't focusing.
We were so sorry for him,
we didn't know what to say.
I had a bad feeling.
She's too cute to be Iketani's girl.
After all, Road Racers don't need a girl.
Lonely driver, Itsuki.
That's my motto.
I hope the shock doesn't last too long.
Kouichiro, phone call!
I don't want to take it.
Tell him I'm sleeping.
It must be Kenji anyway.
It's a girl!
Sato Mako!
You said you wanted to talk.
If you're making fun of me, please stop.
No, I'm not making fun of you.
I never thought that you'd be the
driver of that incredible car.
I saw your Sil-Eighty drifting at full speed.
They say you're the fastest on Usui.
If so, you could have told me.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to lie to you.
It was shocking for me, too.
And I thought I should
tell you the truth...
Truth?
I'm... actually the quiet type.
Quiet...?
That's hard to believe, because you can
perform such a dynamic drift.
You know how some people's personalities
change once they get behind the wheel?
I'm that type.
When I drive fast, guys don't
see me as a girl.
So I thought I should quit.
I've made up my mind.
I'm quitting road racing this summer.
For my last memory of this summer...
...would you let me race against Akina's
Eight-Six on Usui's mountain pass?
That's my wish.
If you make my wish come true...
...you can have my virginity.
Wait a minute.
Don't say such a thing!
Am I not enough?
It's not that.
He's my friend, so I can't
make a deal like that.
I understand.
Her target was never me,
it was always Takumi.
It's obvious.
Otherwise, a cute girl like her would
never be interested in me.
Okay, I'll see what I can do.
Really?
But don't misunderstand me.
I'll cooperate, but not because
I want something from you.
Iketani...
I just want to make your wish come true.
It's alright.
Although it was only a short time,
I was seriously in love with Mako.
As long as she's happy,
I'll be satisfied.
People would call me a fool...
...but I really loved her.
Even though it was my misunderstanding,
I really loved her.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na
hitomi ni miserate yuku
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Two faces were given to the Nissan S13 series (for the Japanese market):
Silvia: earlier model with a coupe body, in production only till 1993
with fixed headlights (like Iketani's)
180SX: comes with a hatchback body with flip up headlights,
exported on a large scale, in many variations
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitsu da to ieru
Nissan released a limited production model with the
front end of Silvia and the rear end of the 180SX
(hence named Sil-Eighty). These cars are rare and
prized among S13 fans.
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Kagayaku mirai e
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Kiseki no hana yo
Mako, how could a cute girl
like you go after Iketani?
Even if you ask me why...
And that shocking comment...!
I guess it was too bold...
There are so many handsome guys!
But why?  How can Iketani be the one?!
Even if you ask me...
After all, Iketani is...
I don't understand, no matter
how hard I try...
Next time on Initial D:
"Sudden Death Death Match."
Initial
Next Time:
Sudden Death Death Match
Don't miss it.
Sorry, I...