This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
INITIAL
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...deserves a lariat three times.
We make love according to the manuals.
We don't notice the lack of love.
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho!!!
In the midnight dream.
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
We smile without dropping our guard.
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.  Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
You're afraid of a big world.
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go to an unknown world.
You're a newborn traveler.
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Let's warp uninteresting things...
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
Please, Takumi.
It sounds so pathetic that I can't
tell Kenji about it...
...but I thought I needed to explain it
to you so you understand.
I don't like it.
I can't forgive her.
Takumi...
Don't think poorly of Mako.
She's a nice girl.
How can you defend her?
I don't understand.
You shouldn't go that far.
I beg you, Takumi.
Please!
Hey, Takumi, you've never seen a mountain pass
other than Akina, right?
How was it?
I wasn't driving, so I don't know.
I'll... race her.
R...really?
Thanks!  You've saved me!
I don't know if either of you
will be satisfied, but...
Takumi...
Anyway, I'll go to Usui
with the Eight-Six.
Sudden Death Death Match
Are you sure, Kenji?
I can't believe Takumi is going to Usui
to race against the Sil-Eighty!
Me neither.
He's not the type to go
racing in other places.
I wonder how Iketani convinced him.
I don't know.
Iketani won't give me a real answer.
We talked about what'd happen if Takumi
drove on an unfamiliar mountain pass...
Yeah.
Well, I can understand
that he wants to see it.
Even so, it's so stupid racing the Sil-Eighty,
the fastest on its home ground.
Is Takumi going to race on Usui?
Yes, Manager!
And is the Sil-Eighty that good?
It's not just good!
It took Usui's narrow passes so freely...
...and it even used a feint motion.
Takumi watched the Sil-Eighty with us,
so he should know better.
But Takumi will win!
You're as airheaded as usual.
Remember the guy at the gas station said
that even the local guys can't defeat her?
Maybe Takumi doesn't care
if he wins or not.
Damn, I'm out...
I'd better take the Eight-Six for a spin,
and go buy some more.
What the hell?
My Eight-Six turned into an Eight-Five?
I borrowed the car.
I left you a substitute.
Takumi
Your dad must be really
surprised by now...
...because his Eight-Six turned
into my Eight-Five!
Iketani, I want to ask you something.
What is it?
Whose side are you on
for today's battle?
Whose side...
I just set up this battle...
Do you mean that?
What about Takumi?
Aren't you causing your friend trouble
so you can look cool in front of Mako?
I'm not doing that.
Yes, you are!
Let me ask you, then...
Do you think Takumi has the
slightest chance of winning?
Well, Iketani?
Give me a straight answer!
That's...
There's no way he can win.
He only knows Akina's
mountain passes.
He's never driven Usui's passes,
and it's such a difficult course.
He has wonderful technique...
...but sometimes technique doesn't
mean a lot in racing.
There's familiarity with the
course, for example!
Without practice, it won't be
a fair race, even for Takumi.
You know that...
W...well...
Of course, any man is more or less
powerless with the one he loves.
For my last memory of this summer...
...would you let me race against Akina's
Eight-Six on Usui's mountain pass?
But don't let your friend down by
losing yourself to a woman.
Haven't you forgotten that Takumi and his Eight-Six
saved us at an important moment?
Akina's Eight-Six is our pride!
If you don't cancel this battle...
...our friendship is over!
Kenji, I understand.
Sorry. I should've talked
about this with you earlier.
I've been thinking about this for a while.
I don't understand why you're
going to quit racing.
We were obsessed when we started
racing two years ago.
Our goal was to be
the best in this area.
It's still fun today.
Or isn't it?
I don't know how
to say this...
...but I don't feel the tension
these days like I used to.
I don't know why.
I thought, "It's time."
I think it's time to quit.
Is it?
I really don't understand very well.
I want a boyfriend...
I want to find my love, like you.
You don't have to quit
racing to find a guy.
I do...
I don't think you can
understand how I feel.
You have someone you like, don't you?
Honestly speaking, I had a guy I admired.
I didn't know.
My leading question worked.
You never told me about it.
Of course you didn't know.
He doesn't live nearby.
I was dreaming of him from a distance.
What's wrong with you?
You're almost like a romance novel
character who's extremely modest.
You're twenty already.
It doesn't matter.
I was happy just dreaming
about him.
"Dreaming...?"
You should look at reality.
Sorry...
I want to see what we've accomplished
in the last two years in my last race.
To put a period to it, right?
Sounds thoughtful of you.
He's good enough to be our opponent?
Yes.
Let me tell you this.
If we race on Usui's mountain passes, we
can't lose no matter who the opponent is.
Or I won't be satisfied.
I know.
We have to win.
Even if it's against Akina's Eight-Six.
Yes, definitely.
So, why don't we cancel the race, since
you're not personally interested?
Iketani and I'll talk to them, so you
can turn around at the next exit.
Do as he says.
Sorry about this, Takumi.
Forgive him, Takumi.
Kenji... I'm not going to turn around.
Takumi...
I want to race, so I'm going.
It's my own wish, and I'm
not going to turn around.
Takumi...
But, Takumi, you know how good
Mako is, you saw her with us.
There're too many disadvantages for you.
Even though it's you, you
won't be able to win.
I know.
I'm not worried about the result.
Don't say such things so casually!
Akina's Eight-Six is famous now, and
you should protect your reputation.
I don't like it.
I've been winning because I'm
familiar with the course.
But I don't like the fact that the
fame is greater than my skill.
I'd feel good if such fame went away.
H...hey.
Why...
I'm going.
I want to push as hard as I can on
a mountain pass I've never driven.
Sorry about my harsh words, Iketani.
There's nothing to say after
hearing that from Takumi.
Right.
He's so weird.
He's different from us.
I don't know if he's great
or simply airheaded.
I don't get it.
Tires are okay.
Tires with this much wear
will grab the road best.
No need to change the suspension settings.
I think the current setting is the best.
If you say so, it should be.
I think you know this, but when it comes to
a duel, you should avoid overusing drift.
And the key is to decide at each corner
whether to skid or to grip.
Especially on Usui, where there
are many consecutive corners.
I'm with you, so you should trust
your technique and push hard.
No one can defeat you.
I'll prove that, so leave it to me.
The two of us drive as one.
I'm getting excited, Sayuki.
Tonight, my tension is so high.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm excited to see how the battle'll go and what
kind of driver we're going to race against.
Hey, Takumi, how're you going to race?
If you have a plan, tell me.
I don't have one.
How can you say that?
Can't you do something?
I don't want to see you lose.
How about this?
Usui is narrow and there
are no straightaways.
Yeah.
So get the jump on her
and take the lead.
What do you mean?
Then, keep blocking so that you can't be
passed, and you'll be able to win.
That's too cowardly.
How can I do that?
But, if they get ahead of you,
they'll pull away, and it'll be over.
You're right.
Any good ideas?
Both are just cars with four tires.
Are you reeeeeeeeeeally the
driver of the Eight-Six?!
I don't believe this.
How old are you?
I'm eighteen.
Eighteen?
A high school kid?
Give me a break.
You're only twenty, so you're young, too.
And they're women.
We can't lose to a younger kid, Mako.
Well, let's get down to business.
These are the race rules.
It's not fair to start
side by side here...
...because the one who's in front
of the other has an advantage.
We don't want to argue
for a jumpstart or such.
My idea won't work.
So, how do we do it?
Let one chase the other.
Get it?
It's run and catch.
If the frontrunner runs away from
the chaser, the front wins.
If not, switch positions and try again
until the game is settled.
It's a sudden death death match.
How's that?
Fine.
We're locals, so we'll let you choose
your position for the first run.
Choose front or rear.
Well...
Wait a minute.
Come over here, Takumi.
With this rule, you should take
the front for the first heat.
Yeah, there'll be a second heat,
so you'll have a chance to practice.
Even if you lose in the second heat,
you won't look too bad.
I know he'll take the front
for the first heat.
We'll win the second heat.
Don't worry.
Thanks for being concerned about
me and giving me advice.
But I don't like it.
What're you talking about, Takumi?
I'll take the rear for the first heat.
Say what?
Think it over, Takumi.
Okay?
This is my battle...
Let me decide.
B...but...
I'll take the rear.
Rear...?
Is he taking us lightly, or is he
just plain stupid?
Okay, I'll leave him way behind.
Who the hell is that?
I'm busy.
This is the Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Hello, is that you, Bunta?
Oh, it's you.
I'm busy.
I'm worried about something.
It's about Takumi...
Are you ready?
Let's start!
...went to Usui to race?
I see.
"I see?"
Is that all you can say?
Don't you worry about him?
Nope.
He's my son, you know.
We'll start slowly, so relax and follow us.
As soon as we clear the first corner,
we'll drive with all our power.
That's the sign of the
start of the race.
Is that all?
Nothing else?
That's all.
I'm busy, so don't call me
about such minor things.
H...hey, Bunta...
Takumi, I was stupid.
I realize it now.
I knew it all along.
Even though you don't like it, you're doing
this to save face for me, aren't you?
I really regret this.
You're the pride of all Akina's Road Racers.
I've done something I can't make up for.
I don't want to see you lose
because of my stupidity.
Takumi won't lose!
But in reality, it'll be difficult.
It's my fault.
Iketani...
Senpai...
...I chose the rear because
I have an idea.
What?
I don't know if I can win, but I'm not
thinking about losing.
Takumi, do you have a plan?
It's not really a plan.
It's just a simple idea.
What is it, Takumi?
Hey, tell us.
No matter how fast they are,
their car can't fly or anything.
Both are just cars with four wheels.
Four...?
So, if their car can take a corner at a particular
speed, I think I can do it, too.
That's what I'm thinking.
Oh, I see!
It makes sense.
That's impossible...
We're going!
Let's go, Mako.
Let's finish this battle
on the first try.
Okay, Sayuki.
I'll show you the best race ever.
Both cars blasted off at full throttle!
Takumi's first visitor race
has finally begun...
But this battle's conditions are
so tough, even for Takumi.
Don't worry.  Don't worry.
Takumi will definitely win!
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
...into the bright future.
Let's make it sure over and over.
This passion will be eternal.
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
The flower of miracles.
Mako, we can't lose on our home course.
We're Road Racers.
Ummm, Sayuki.  What will you do
after Mako quits road racing?
I'll keep on racing!
Sayuki...
So you won't retire, then.
Well, I'll race for a man.
Any cute guy...?
Any cute guy?
Good-bye, Sayuki.
Next time on Initial D: "A Hot Wind and Violent
Drive on Usui's Mountain Pass."
Initial
Next Time:
A Hot Wind and Violent Drive
on Usui's Mountain Pass
Don't miss it!