This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
Money can't buy my love nante...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
Now, we gotta start.  Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
Hajimatta bakari no
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Kimeru took dake bashitto
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
That's our law.
A Hot Wind and Violent Drive on Usui's Mountain Pass
They're fast.
Looks really bad.
Can I make it?
If they can do it, there's no reason I can't.
Go!
Next, almost rub the inside.
Grip the road.
Very good, Mako.
Obstacles.
Move outward.
Not bad.  He isn't an ordinary
Road Racer.
He's on our tail.
Yeah.  Otherwise we wouldn't have any fun.
I wonder how much longer
he can keep up with us.
We haven't gotten serious yet.
This's tough.  I'm not driving
in my own style...
...I'm just copying their style.
This isn't any different than a roller coaster.
Because I'm not in my rhythm, this is scary.
But if I get outrun now, I won't
be able to catch up later.
I've got to keep up!
Not knowing the course is a much
tougher handicap than I thought.
If I lose my concentration, I'll crash into
the mountainside or fall off the cliff.
Just like Akina's famous Eight-Six.
He won't let us outrun him so easily.
The terror of Usui, where the corners appear
one after another, begins now.
A right-hander's, next.
It's narrow.
Okay.
She's fast.
Damn, but I can't let it pull away.
If they can turn, I should be able to!
Takumi said, if they can turn, he
should be able to, didn't he?
Yes, that's what he said.
I don't believe it.
What a simple idea.
What's his brain made of?
But it's a great thing, in a sense.
Only a skilled driver like him
would think about that.
Unless he loses control at a corner's
entrance, he can control the car...
He should be able to!
But his opponent is...
...Mako and her Sil-Eighty, who knows everything
about this mountain's passes.
She must be pushing her
car to the limit...
...so Takumi'll have to enter
corners at the same speed.
His first time on Usui's
unfamiliar passes...
That gives me a chill.
It's scary to even think about.
Yeah.  He'll need plenty of guts,
not just technique.
One mistake...
...will be deadly.
He said his opponent is a Sil-Eighty.
What's a Sil-Eighty?
He's on my tail...
Why?  I'm driving fast enough, aren't I?
Yes, you are.
You're in a good mood.
But he's right on my tail!
Stop looking into the mirror.
It'll disturb your rhythm.
I'm checking what's happening
behind us, so don't worry.
It's just begun.
We have to enjoy this.
It's a great battle.
Okay, I'll leave it to you.
Right, trust your partner.
You and I are the best team on Usui.
If the frontrunner runs away from
the chaser, the front wins.
If not, switch positions and try again
until the game is settled.
It's a sudden death death match.
With this rule, you should take
the front for the first heat.
Yeah, there'll be a second heat,
so you'll have a chance to practice.
Even if you lose in the second heat,
you won't look too bad.
I'll take the rear for the first heat.
Think it over, Takumi.
Okay?
This is my battle...
Let me decide.
Damn, I chose the rear because
I hate having somebody on my tail...
...but I didn't expect
it to be this hard.
Takahashi
The most difficult part of attacking
an unfamiliar course is...
Theory of the Fastest on the Street
...the ability to decide
a corner's entry speed.
The reason why Keisuke was defeated...
...and the reason Nakazato was passed
are essentially the same.
No matter how skilled a driver is, he can't
match one who drives hard every day.
If so, to defeat the Eight-Six on Akina...
I can win...
With my hypothesis, I'll be able
to defeat him, even on Akina.
Damn, I guess I was wrong.
I took a big gamble.
Just a few centimeters difference
at the entrance...
...and the speed difference causes
a big gap at the exit.
Damn, too fast...
I scratched the bumper.
Damn, I won't let it pull away!
A Road Racer grows by experiencing
many terrifying moments.
With extraordinary concentration
and trained driving technique...
...and with my perfect suspension setting...
...he won't lose.
Nagano Prefecture
Karuizawa
I wonder what's happening...
Is the race already settled?
We won't know until they return.
It's impossible.
No matter how you look at it,
it's too unfair.
B...but, Iketani...
...so far, none of the races have
been easy for Takumi.
Nakazato's 32 was monstrous.
And the gumtape death match with that
Shoji guy was his first try at that.
But one thing was always on his side.
They all happened on Akina...
...where Takumi has driven every day
for the last five years.
Senpai, is the course
difference that important?
It'd be different if he had
driven here a few times...
...but this is his very first time.
Well...let me see...
Come to think of it, Iketani...
...I've been wondering.
Who's the girl sitting next to Mako?
Who?  Even if you ask me...
She caught my attention, too.
She got in the car so naturally, even though
they were going to race.
I don't really know her well, but she's been
her best friend since childhood...
...and they've driven together
since they were beginners...
...and they perfected
their driving skill.
So she's like a rally navigator.
If so, Takumi's in an even
more difficult situation.
Don't worry.
Takumi shouldn't lose!
But with a good navigator sitting next to Mako,
she can concentrate on driving.
Obstacle before the corner.
Avoid it and close the inside.
He's still keeping up with us.
How can he follow us
at this high pace?
Mako is in the best condition,
but he's still on our tail.
What a guy...
Mako, C-121 is near.
Let's settle this race.
You can skid from the
entry of the corner.
Let's show him what we can do at the
most difficult corner on Mt. Usui.
Okay, I got it.
I'll show him my car skid from
the entry to the exit.
No one has cleared the corner
at my entry speed.
Haven't Mako and Sayuki come tonight?
I don't know.
I haven't seen them.
I want to see the Sil-Eighty's drift.
This C-121 corner is the highlight.
It's really difficult.
It's more than just difficult.
If you can skid from the entry to the exit,
you're considered highly skilled on Usui.
If you're good on Usui, you're
the best wherever you go.
Yeah.
You have to enter the corner at
high speed with lots of guts...
...or you'll lose speed, and your drift
won't last until the exit.
Everyone fails on their first try.
But if you get used to it,
you can do it, right?
Only a few can.
Only Mako's Sil-Eighty enters
the corner at full throttle.
I don't know how fast she goes,
but no one can copy her.
Someone's... coming down.
The squeals are so loud.
Someone's really pushing it hard.
There it is.
It's the Sil-Eighty!
Mako and Sayuki!
There's a car behind it.
Who is it?
A...are they racing?
Isn't that an Eight-Six?!
No oncoming traffic.
Let's show off, Mako!
Okay!
Go!
They dove into the corner!
I don't know who he is...
...but he must be stupid, entering the
corner at the same speed as Mako!
He doesn't know how difficult C-121 is!
You can't clear the corner
with only courage!
He's got nerve entering the
corner right behind Mako.
Once you enter this corner at that speed,
you can't use any tricks.
The middle section of the C-121 is wide,
but the exit is extremely narrow.
There appear to be many lines you
can take, but there's only one.
Will you be able...
...to stay on that line on your first try?
Im...impossible.
He cleared it.
I don't believe it.
Who's driving that Eight-Six?
Could that be...?
Could that be Akina's Eight-Six
they've been talking about lately?
I...I've got goose bumps.
H...how?
The difficulty of four-wheel drift
at very high speed is ultra D.
Even with all her experience, Mako missed
the entry by five centimeters.
But he... he controlled the car
to follow the ideal line.
We can't win.
We chose a totally outclassing
monster as our opponent.
No, you shouldn't skid
so much in this corner!
You should have told me that before
we entered the corner, Sayuki!
What's wrong with you?
Snap out of it!
It's not like you!
Don't you get it yet, Mako?
The Eight-Six behind us is a monster.
We won't be able to win with our skill.
Say what?!
You always talk big!
The race isn't over, but
you're ready to give up?
I don't like that!
Of course not, but...
I don't care.
I didn't know you were such a coward.
I won't depend on you anymore.
We knew that the Eight-Six was extraordinary
from the beginning...
I decided this race would be my last!
So unless we try our best,
I won't be satisfied!
How can you have gotten so timid?
You're the worst!  You're like baggage
in the passenger seat!
Baggage?
Yes, you're only ballast, worsening
the power to weight ratio!
She's one of those people who changes
personality behind the wheel.
HOW CAN YOU CALL ME BALLAST?!
I'VE GOT A NICE BODY, AND I'M NOT
CHUBBY OR FAT!
But you're a 49 kg handicap!
47 KG!
Now that you've said that,
I can't stay quiet.
Let's do it, Mako!
Drive like hell!
That's more like it.
Turn hard, as if you were going to hit
the cliff in the next corner.
Okay, Sayuki.
Wings of fire, tsubasa ni koi no honoo nosete
Wings of fire. We let our wings carry our passion for love.
Higher.
Wings of fire jiyuu ni hateshinaku takaku tobu
Wings of fire. We fly high so freely.
Wings of fire, futari wa speed ageteyuku
Wings of fire. The two of us pick up speed.
Higher.
I can do it.
Wings of fire, hirogaru kono sora wo kakemeguru
Wings of fire. We fly around in the open sky.
I'm getting better, even while I'm
desperately following them.
I can feel the rhythm
of this mountain pass.
I can drive in my own rhythm.
There are a few corners to go.
But I won't drop my guard.
I'll push harder and
harder till the end!
I won't let this be regrettable.
For the pride of the best on Usui!
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na
hitomi ni miserate yuku
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Sake bara no youni akaku
Song: "Wings of Fire"
A duet by Mako and Sayuki
(original: Jee Bee - Wings of Fire)
Tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitsu da to ieru
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Kagayaku mirai e
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Kiseki no hana yo
Mr. Bunta, does Takumi have a chance of
winning the battle against the Sil-Eighty?
Who knows.
"Who knows...?"
I'm a tofu shop owner, not a fortuneteller.
Oh, can I have Ganmo and fried tofu?
It's the Eight-Six I've thoroughly tuned.
No car can outrun my car on the downhill.
So, it's up to the driver.
Well, wait and you'll see next week.
You're mean.
I'll buy both soft and hard tofu.
Next time on Initial D,
"Race-Settling Super Drift."
Initial
Next Time:
Race-Settling Super Drift
Make sure you see it.
Don't miss it!