This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
INITIAL
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...deserves a lariat three times.
We make love according to the manuals.
We don't notice the lack of love.
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho!!!
In the midnight dream.
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
We smile without dropping our guard.
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.  Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
You're afraid of a big world.
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go to an unknown world.
You're a newborn traveler.
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Let's warp uninteresting things...
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
No oncoming traffic.
Let's show off, Mako!
Okay!
Go!
Im...impossible.
We knew that the Eight-Six was extraordinary
from the beginning.
I decided this race would be the last!
So unless we try our best,
I won't be satisfied!
How can you have gotten so timid?
You're the worst!  You're like baggage
in the passenger seat!
Baggage?
Yes, you're only ballast, worsening
the power to weight ratio.
She's one of those who changes
their personality behind the wheel.
HOW CAN YOU CALL ME BALLAST?!
I'VE GOT A NICE BODY, AND I'M NOT
CHUBBY OR FAT!
But you're a 49 kg handicap!
47 KG!
Now that you've said that,
I can't stay quiet.
Let's do it, Mako!
Drive like hell!
That's more like it.
Turn hard, as if you were going to hit
the cliff in the next corner.
Okay, Sayuki.
Race-Settling Super Drift
Well, good night, Papa.
Yeah.
Natsuki...
...when will I see you again?
I don't know, since school
starts again soon.
Natsuki...
Next corner is sandy, so stay
on the inner edge.
Okay, Sayuki.
No oncoming car.
Drift in the next corner.
I was distracted by the car behind me
and I couldn't drive at my own pace.
Somewhere in my mind, I thought
no one could keep up with us.
But I realize now...
There's no way I can drive fast
if I watch my rear.
I won't look in the mirror again.
Skid here.
There shouldn't be many more corners.
I wonder if Takumi is keeping up with her.
Honestly speaking, I thought
they'd come back right away.
It'll be okay!
Even if he can't overtake them,
he'll outrun them in the second heat.
How could he possibly overtake them?
I don't know how he can keep up.
He chose to be the pursuer on
a course he's never driven.
It started!
Great!
I'm Sato Mako.
Call me.
I'm really sor...
For my memory of this summer...
...would you let me race against Akina's
Eight-Six on the Usui mountain pass?
That's my wish.
If you make my wish come true...
...you can have my virginity.
Iketani...
What?
How come you look out of it?
You must be thinking about Mako.
It shows on your face.
I...I'm not...
You don't have to lie.
Mako is a nice girl.
I agree with you.
Kenji...
I don't know what happened, but you should
go after her again after this battle.
She's too good to give up on so easily.
It's okay.
Drift here.
A car's coming, but you'll pass it
in the third corner...
...so don't worry now
and go full throttle!
Okay, Sayuki.
Next one, the car'll appear.
Some people are racing.
I want to see!
You can tell how good they are by watching
how they drive the downhill.
I...incredible...
Bingo.
Sayuki never misses oncoming cars.
She never misses the headlights, which reflect
off the leaves several corners away.
Grip!  Get close to the inside!
Great, Mako.
This is more like you.
Drift all the way and clear it!
No oncoming car, so drift!
Incredible.
She's dangerously good.
Skilled Road Racers always keep
a slight margin of safety.
They appear to be driving at the limit...
...but they use the full gripping potential
of the tires only at the exits.
They save the tires when braking
and at the turn-in.
Because one mistake means crashing
on the street with no escape zone.
But...
...she doesn't have that margin right now.
Her tension is so high that
she hasn't noticed it.
I wonder if I should tell
her about it or not.
It's my role to tell her, but...
I've decided.
I shouldn't disturb her while
she's driving so well.
I've made up my mind.
We're the best partners, so I'll
believe in your skill, Mako.
You're driving better than ever before.
Damn, what an entry.
She increased her pace.
If she goes any faster,
I'll reach my limit first.
Even now, I'm using the
full potential of the tires.
Damn, I can't...?
Wings of fire, tsubasa ni koi no honoo nosete
Wings of fire. We let our wings carry our passion for love.
Higher.
Wings of fire jiyuu ni hateshinaku takaku tobu
Wings of fire. We fly high so freely.
Koe wo kiku dakede kimochi ga ochitsuku
I feel relieved just by hearing your voice.
Fudangi no futari ga naniyori mo uresii yo
We appreciate each other for unchanged behavior.
Togireta rail no ue samayoi tsuzuketeta hibi mo
There were days we wandered on a broken rail.
Kotae wa mabusikatta kesshite te wo hanasanai
The answer seemed so bright, and we'll never let our holding hands go.
Wings of fire, tsubasa ni koi no honoo nosete
Wings of fire. We let our wings carry our passion for love.
Higher.
Wings of fire, jyuu ni hateshinaku takaku tobu
Wings of fire. We fly high so freely.
Wings of fire, futari wa speed ageteyuku
Wings of fire. The two of us pick up speed.
If you can't outrun him, there'll be
no place to settle the race!
I know.
No oncoming car, so take
it at your best pace!
Higher.
Wings of fire, hirogaru kono sora wo kakemeguru
Wings of fire. We fly around in the open sky.
The Eight-Six slowed down.
Why?
No, Mako!
Your entry speed's too fast!
No, you can't recover!
Just spin to stop!
This is bad!
Please, get by!
We're safe...
Splendid.
I admit our total defeat.
He's incredible.
He's got much better range.
How do you feel?
Even though we lost...
...I'm completely satisfied.
I recalled...
...those exciting feelings from
when we started racing.
We were obsessed with
driving until daybreak.
The pure feeling from those days...
We crossed the limit...
...but you were wonderful till that moment.
It's the best driving
I've ever seen from you.
Sayuki...
So, I'll leave it up to you, Mako.
You can do as you like.
Thanks, Sayuki.
No, no tears.  I'm so happy
to have had a great race.
They're back!
I...I wonder how the
first heat turned out.
Are they going to start
the second run?
Takumi!
Takumi, I can't believe
this myself, but...
There won't be a second
heat, will there, Takumi?
No second run.
Once was enough.
I thought so.
Even though it was Takumi...
No, I didn't want to see Takumi lose.
We lost.
W...what did you say?
What did you just say?
Don't make me say
that we lost again.
He won.
MEGCSINÁLTA!
Honestly speaking, we didn't think we
could lose on our home course.
I just kept following you, so
I wouldn't get outrun...
...so I don't think I won.
You don't have to be so modest.
You should be proud of yourself, because
you have such wonderful skill.
But...
We've driven here so often,
we were very confident.
But we couldn't outrun a visitor.
So that means we lost, right, Mako?
Mako...
It was a wonderful race.
Thank you.
He's so shy.
He's strange.
He's totally superior in controlling a car,
but he's so reserved in other things.
He's like this all the time.
He acts so stupid.
Almost like he's always asleep,
except for driving a car.
How can you say that?
It's true.
But how can you be
so good at your age?
Why don't you go after her again,
after the race?
She's too good to give up on so easily.
Iketani...
T...thanks for tonight.
Mako, I...
Iketani, don't be depressed!
Road Racers don't need a girl, right?
R...right...
When I look closely, he's got
my favorite kind of cute face.
Hey, what's your name?
Fujiwara Ta...
And I'm Takeuchi Itsuki.
Eighteen years old!
My sign is Leo, and my blood type is 0.
My favorite car is...
I...I'm not asking you.
By the way, why don't we go to the
pool together for friendship?
Sounds good, sounds good!
Kenji...?
You'll go, right, Takumi?!
And you of course, Iketani?!
Great!
Thank you so much, Sayuki!
It's a promise!
This is great!
I'll go in my Eight-Five!
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
...into the bright future.
Let's make it sure over and over.
This passion will be eternal.
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
The flower of miracles.
Iketani, you have to be true to yourself!
Otherwise, humanity would've
been extinct by now.
You're right, Manager.
But the first time is very important.
For the first time, don't...
Oh...dear?
I'm just leaving.
Are you going home, Manager?
What did you mean by
"For the first time, don't...?"
Next time on Initial D:
"The End of Summer."
Initial
Next Time:
The End of Summer
Don't miss it, I say.