This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
INITIAL
Silver smoke in a freezing city...
...that's the cost of having an unachievable dream.
A frozen body and unforgettable desire...
You deceive yourself by stepping
on the accelerator.
Although depressed in the night,
your eyes are kept sharply open.
You feel like someone's careless
act could end the world.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Lost in the night with frightened eyes...
Embraced by a ruined dream.
Scared of loneliness, I'm missing you in my heart.
I almost hurt myself.
Love me so much and knock me out.
If only I can give up everything...
...and love you...
...I can be my true self.
I'm...I'm so happy to be here, Kenji!
Itsuki...
...it's wonderful and gorgeous!
Takumi!
Come over here, and let's go
swimming together!
Well, I...
Okay, we're coming!
What's wrong?
Hurry!
We're coming!
I'm so happy to be here, Itsuki!
Senpai...
The End of Summer
You're coming, right, Iketani?
What's wrong?
Isn't this fun?
S...sure it is.
Hey, Takumi, let's go try the Slider.
I...I'll just stay and relax...
Well, he's always out of it.
If you don't mind us going too...
Okay, let's all go together.
Together, together!
Alright, let's go.
Okay, Takumi, let's go!
Well, I don't like the Slider...
How can someone who can do
such a super drift say that?
Sayuki's so forceful.
And she's always like that.
I guess it's okay.
They're having fun.
Is it okay for everyone
to take the day off?
We begged to take a paid
vacation day.
The manager didn't look
too happy though.
She's so bright.
My heart is almost bursting.
At least I've gotten to see
her in a bathing suit...
...so this'll be the greatest memory
of my 21st summer of life.
I'll never forget it.
After all, Mako is beyond my reach.
Iketani...
Thank you for many things.
I need to thank you for a lot.
I learned a lot from that race.
Mako...
I caused you a lot of trouble,
but I won't quit racing.
Really?
That's great!
I didn't want you to quit.
After all, I got conceited because they put
the label of Usui's fastest on us.
No, you can't recover!
Just spin to stop!
I realized that I needed to learn a lot
more about controlling a car.
If I quit racing now, I'd leave
something unfinished.
I'm glad to hear that.
So something good came
out of what I did.
Iketani...
Do you remember the promise
we made by the lake?
You might have misunderstood
because of the way I put it...
...but I wasn't trying to make a deal.
I want you... to be my first man.
I'll be waiting for you in front of the signboard
where we first met around 8:00 pm.
Slow down!
So cute!
I feel her breasts on my back...
I...I feel something on my back...
So pathetic...
Mako, get the ball!
Please!
Takahashi Ryosuke...?
Ready, Sayuki?
Here!
Where're you throwing it?
Sorry, sorry.
I missed.
Why does she have a picture
of Takahashi Ryosuke?
Something wrong?
N...no.
Umm...
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
You said you've never had a boyfriend.
Right...
Even if you haven't...
...you've had a crush or something, right?
Y...yeah...
I wonder why you can't
go out with that guy.
Most guys would be attracted
to you because of your looks.
Impossible.  That'll never happen...
And... what kind of man is he?
He's... a Road Racer.
It was when I was still in high school,
so it was about three years ago...
Some senior schoolmates
took me to watch a race.
I didn't know anything at that time...
...but the way one car went by shocked me.
His driving looked clearly different from
the others, even to my amateur eyes.
I was shocked by this unknown world... and I was
fascinated by the world of Road Racers.
I got my license right after that, and then
I worked hard to buy a car.
I practiced so hard...
...so that I would be able
to get close to him.
My motivation sounds silly...
I've gone to see his driving quite often.
But I've never talked to him.
So, I don't know if I can call it love.
I don't know whether I liked
him or his driving.
But... you liked him.
Yes...
...I liked him so much.
What... is this pain?
Damn, I shouldn't have asked.
She seems so far away.
So her crush was on the superstar
of the Gunma area...
...Takahashi Ryosuke.
Now I know why she likes FCs.
I can't.
I'm no match for him!
Finally, my brother has decided to race
against Akina's Eight-Six.
Are you coming with me, Keisuke?
I'll show you my hypothesis
for the fastest driving.
Brother...
I enjoyed it so much!
I never knew going to the pool
with girls was this fun!
Right, Takumi?
But you were with Kenji
almost all the time.
Mako and Sayuki are great, aren't they?
Your recovery is quick.
You used to say that Road Racers
don't need girls.
They're different.
Itsuki!
I can still see those two
in their bikinis!
It was awesome!
Sayuki's bouncy boobs are amazing,
but it's Mako after all...
She's got a knockout bod,
don't you think, Iketani?
Yeah, true...
Something's wrong with your reaction.
You look blue.
Did you fight with Mako?
No, I didn't.
I'm just tired.
Oh, what's the matter
at this time of night?
Sorry about today.
I asked too much of you.
Oh, it's okay.
You're young, so you
need to have some fun.
I'd be worried if you were only into
cars and didn't have a girlfriend.
Good luck, okay?
Mako is your angel, right?
Is it going well?
Well... not really.
She's beyond my reach after all.
Don't be so discouraged.
Listen, Iketani, girls are...
It's okay, Manager.
I've already given up.
I'm no match for Takahashi Ryosuke.
What do you mean?
What's happened?  I'm barely
keeping up with him.
His FC hasn't been changed, so why...?
My hypothesis for the fastest driving
is refined every time I get new data.
Wait for me, Eight-Six of Akina.
As soon as I've completed it, I'll put
your name on the list of losers.
Kamameshi Restaurant
I arrived before he did.
My chest feels tight.
My heart is pounding.
If I'm like this now, I don't know what
I'll do when Iketani shows up.
What did you say?
Are you stupid or what, Iketani?
You don't know anything about girls.
Eh?
Don't give me "Eh!"
Think!
If she was actually going out with Takahashi
Ryosuke, you'd be out of luck...
...but young girls have those
kinds of feelings, you know?
It's no different than
dreaming about TV stars.
Cool down, and think!
Because she chose you over
Takahashi Ryosuke...
...she took courage and
made up her mind.
Because she believes in you,
she told you how she feels!
Don't you get it?
Don't let your inferiority
complex hold you back!
To love someone means to
accept everything about her!
That's what loving and caring
is all about, isn't it?
What?  Eight o'clock?!
Idiot, you're thirty minutes late already!
I...It's impossible...
It'll take at least one hour to get to Yokokawa
no matter how fast I drive.
I don't think she'll be waiting.
Shut up and go!
You won't know unless you go!
If you don't go, I'll fire you!
Drive like hell.
If you're a Road Racer, this is
the time to drive like hell.
But having said that... I don't
think he can make it.
Well, I guess that's part of being young...
The manager is right.
How could I be so stupid?!
I'll never have another chance
to meet someone like Mako!
Why couldn't I be honest?
I'm Sato Mako.  Call me.
I'll give you my virginity.
I'll be waiting for you in front of the signboard
where we first met around 8:00 pm.
Mako is always serious, but I...I...
I'm so stupid!
My feet hurt...
I hate... sandals.
Mako, I'm not expecting to go
to a hotel or anything.
Well, actually...
No! I just want to see her face!
Please, God!  Give me one more chance!
Don't take my angel away from my world!
Traffic jam?
An accident... at a place like this?
No... God, this is so cruel!
Sorry, Mako...
I got no impression.
This town's made by imitation.
Wanting your sensation.
I'll never wear sandals again.
In this silly simulation...
I wanna rage my dream.
I got no impression grey no kanjo
I got no motivation. Grey feeling.
bokashi mo iresugi machijyuu wa imitation
Shaded off too much, the city is an imitation.
real wo motomete takaburu anata ga
You are desperate in seeking for reality.
chikaku ni yorenai hodo atsukunaru
You get so excited that I can't come close.
Feel your frustration anata no sakebi wo
I feel your frustration and hear your shout.
Taste your vibration furueru hodo ni kanjiteru
I sense your vibration. I feel it so strongly that it shakes me.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang another round, never slow down.
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down on the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logics...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream. tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
Rage your dream. In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream. Ima wo ikiteiru
Rage your dream. You live in the present.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na
hitomi ni miserate yuku
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitsu da to ieru
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Kagayaku mirai e
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Kiseki no hana yo
What's up with that bouquet, Takumi?!
Well...
Oh, they're from Natsuki!
No...
I know!
To the previously unknown
Gunma area racing star...
...Takumi in the Fujiwara
Tofu Shop panda Trueno...
...from some girl in the gallery!
That's not it...
Oh, then it's from Sayuki!
Looks like she's still after you.
No...
They were sent by Takahashi Ryosuke.
Huh?
Next time on Initial D:
"The Challenge from the Superstar."
Initial
Next Time:
The Challenge from the Superstar
Don't miss it!