This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
INITIAL
Silver smoke in a freezing city...
...that's the cost of having an unachievable dream.
A frozen body and unforgettable desire...
You deceive yourself by stepping
on the accelerator.
Although depressed in the night,
your eyes are kept sharply open.
You feel like someone's careless
act could end the world.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Lost in the night with frightened eyes...
Embraced by a ruined dream.
Scared of loneliness, I'm missing you in my heart.
I almost hurt myself.
Love me so much and knock me out.
If only I can give up everything...
...and love you...
...I can be my true self.
Then I cleared the corner like...
I was almost like the wind
at that moment.
I like the mountain passes.
When you buy a car,
you should try 'em.
My car?
It's a Road Racer's dream, the Eight-Five.
The Eight-Five.
Well, ordinary people wouldn't
know about it though...
The Challenge from the Superstar
This year's summer was so exciting...
Why?
"Why?"
Because I bought a car, and you swept through
the Road Racing world like a comet.
Stop calling me things like that.
One, two, three, four...
What're you counting?
Four, four.
It's the number of battles
you won this summer.
First there was the Redsuns'
Takahashi Keisuke and his FD.
Then, the Night Kids'
Nakazato and his 32.
And the gumtape death match
against Shoji Shingo's EG6.
Finally, Mako and Sayuki in
the Sil-Eighty on Usui.
Four wins in a row.
The legend of the unbeatable Fujiwara
Takumi began this summer.
You're no longer just an airheaded kid.
It's not a big deal.
Don't be so shy!
Keep winning, Takumi...
...until I defeat you and become
the fastest in Gunma...
...no, I mean on the Kanto Plain.
The Comet of Akina, Itsuki, so to speak!
Takumi, we only have an opening
ceremony today...
...so why don't we go somewhere
this afternoon?
But... I have to work this afternoon.
You have to work?
I want to ride in your car again...
...because it's so cute.
Even if it's cute,
it's still my dad's car.
You said you want to buy your own car.
Have you saved enough?
I'm saving almost all my money from work,
but there's a long way to go.
How much do you think you will need?
About one million yen.
(~$9500)
One million, huh?
How much have you saved so far?
Still way too low.
Say, Takumi...
...if I gave you 1 million yen,
what would you do?
I wonder what would happen.
You'd appreciate it a lot and think
that I'm very important to you.
Then you couldn't oppose me.
You'd quit working and
love me so much everyday!
No, no, Takumi...
Stop kidding around.
One million isn't the kind of money
kids like us can earn easily.
So what?  It's just an idea.
Can't you even dream?
It's so unrealistic.
So we know that Takumi's technique
works wherever he goes.
It's not just technique.
If he's fast on a course he's never driven...
Thank you!
...he's got good natural senses.
He's a genius.
He defeated all those modern
high performance machines...
...with a 10 year old Eight-Six.
It's awesome.
How can you say that?
Just a while ago...
...you said Takumi would be slow because
he had never driven anywhere else.
W...well, if you say that...
Everyone thought that.
Takumi is unusual.
I thought he'd lose when I heard that
he was going to race on Usui...
...against Mako's Sil-Eighty.
Sorry, Iketani!
My apologies...
Don't worry.
I go by lonely driver, Iketani.
That's Itsuki's line.
Welcome.
Flowers?
You must be mistaken.
This is a gas station...
Takumi, these are for you.
Who from?
From Takahashi Ryosuke.
Takahashi...
...Ryosuke.
From Gunma's number one
superstar to Takumi...?
What does it say?
Let me read it...
September 15, 10:00 pm
At Mt. Akina's peak
"September 15, 10:00pm.
At the peak of Mt. Akina."
Hey, that's all it says?
B...but that's...
Finally, Takahashi Ryosuke has sent him
a challenge for a downhill battle.
Takumi, what'll you do?
Whatever the outcome might be,
he should accept it!
Speaking of the Redsuns, his brother, Takahashi
Keisuke, was defeated by Takumi!
Right.
If you refuse this rematch, it'll be
more disgraceful than losing.
What's wrong, Takumi?
Aren't you having fun with me?
I...it's not that.
But you don't look very interested.
You look out of it.
Well, that's nothing new, but...
You look like your mind isn't here.
If you aren't having fun,
I'm going home.
I am having fun!
Sorry, I apologize.
Then tell me what you were thinking.
I won't forgive you unless you do.
It would be difficult for you to understand
even if I told you.
I'm going home!
Okay, okay.
I'll tell you.
"Battle?"
Are you going to fight someone?
No.  We just call a car race a "battle."
Car race...?
I didn't know you liked
that kind of thing.
I didn't intend liking it.
I was kinda dragged into it.
And my next opponent's
very good and famous.
I haven't been able to help thinking
about it since this morning.
I guess this is pressure.
You're good at driving,
so you'll be okay.
It's not that easy.
If you don't like it,
why don't you ignore him?
It's not that I don't like it.
I'm not going to run away, although
I don't know if I can win.
That's just like you.
You want to race deep in
your heart, don't you?
You look calm, but at the bottom of your heart,
you absolutely hate to lose.
I don't dislike that type of personality.
Let's go home.
Hey, a little longer...
Why don't we talk a little longer?
Umm, I know why...
...you fought the soccer club senior
classman in the locker room.
After you quit the club, one of
the members quietly told me.
You got angry because of me.
I'm sorry I didn't understand
you for such a long time.
It's okay.  It doesn't mean anything now.
That's Takumi's Eight-Six.
W...who's that girl?
Tsuchiya Keiichi's drift is incredible.
Look at these sequential photos, Takumi.
Takumi.
Hey, Takumi!
What is it, Itsuki?
Is it lunch time already?
You idiot!
It's nothing.
I'm just talking to myself.
Takumi's been acting strangely
for the past few days?
How strange is he?
He's out of it, and...
That's not unusual...
Well, true...
...but he wasn't that way
during summer break.
But since school started, he looks
even worse than before.
I wonder if it's fatigue
from constant battles.
It was his first experience, so he might've
lost tension after school started.
That's not quite right.
It's almost like he's brainless.
Hey, do you think he can race
against Takahashi Ryosuke?
Takumi has a girlfriend, doesn't he?
Why'd you ask that so suddenly?
Well, I thought he could be
lovesick over a girl.
Lovesick over a girl?
Yeah.
You were like that when you were
with Mako, remember?
Kenji, it's taboo to mention
her name here.
I...it's alright, Itsuki.
And I saw Takumi and
a girl in his Eight-Six.
IS THAT TRUE?!
I only glanced at her,
but she was cute...
Could Takumi's girlfriend be...?!
No wonder he stopped
going home with me...
That jerk...
I won't forgive you.
I haven't even been able
to touch her hand!
That's it!
That's the reason.
It must be!
Leave it to me!
I'll drag him out and ask him tonight!
Road Racers don't need
girls, right, Iketani?!
Right!
We're lonely drivers!
So pathetic...
What do you want to talk about?
You've been going out with Mogi
without telling me, haven't you?
Oh, that?
"That?!"
I didn't think it was something
I had to tell you.
No excuses!
Answer my question!
H...how far have
you gone?
How far have you gone
with Mogi?  Be honest.
"How far...?"
If you're my best friend,
tell me honestly!
Itsuki, look ahead, look ahead!
I'll tell you!
Go ahead.
Last Sunday...
"Last Sunday...?"
The two of us...
"T...Two of us..."
...went to Lake Akina.
Hey...Itsuki!
Look, look!
That's not what I'm asking.
It's about going from A to B to C!
You're really an idiot.
"A to B...?"
D...did you kiss?
Yeah.
SAY WHAT?!
Hey, Itsuki, stop!
STOP!!
It must be because of a girl.
What're you looking at?
You've been acting strange lately.
Have I?
It's not like you to think so much,
but you've been thinking a lot lately.
Yeah... you're right.
He must be preoccupied,
recalling the kiss with Mogi.
I'm wondering what'll happen in the future.
In the future?!
After a kiss means...
How dare you say such a dirty thing
in front of a lonely driver!
I know what happens after a kiss!
What do you mean?
There's only one thing!
What're you talking about?
We aren't talking about the same thing!
What I mean by the future...
Oh, whatever.
I don't like to think about
difficult matters.
I guess his lovesickness can't
be cured so easily.
Welcome to touge
1434m altitude
I was wondering who that was...
...but that's Keisuke's FD and Kenta's S14.
Kenta's fast on the downhill.
His car's grade is Q's with a non-turbo,
so his specialty is downhill.
He's been recognized by Keisuke,
and being trained by him.
If he's being personally taught
by our team's number two...
But there's a race against the
Night Kids the day after tomorrow.
I wonder if he should be
messing around with Kenta.
I guess he's got time to spare.
So Nakazato Takeshi is going
to be out of his league.
He's been in good
condition lately.
Hey, don't you think his driving style
has gotten similar to Ryosuke's?
Yes, it has.  I think so, too.
I guess Ryosuke trusts
Keisuke completely.
That's why he won't show up on Myogi.
Keisuke, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Why're you leaving Akina's
Eight-Six alone?
Why don't you drag him to
Akagi for a return match?
To Akagi?
That's right.
You're familiar with the course, so you couldn't
be defeated by a mere Eight-Six!
If you don't...
...I will!
You'd better not, Kenta.
Why not?
Do you think I'd lose?
If it's Akagi's downhill,
I'd be able to...
That's not the issue.
You're a member of the Redsuns,
so you should know better.
It's our policy to defeat opponents
on their home course.
It's true, but...
...Keisuke, I can't stand the fact
that we lost to the Eight-Six!
If it's neither of our home courses,
the conditions will be equal!
Let me...
Let me do it!
Don't be so hasty!
Don't worry.
When it's time to do it...
...there's a person who'll do it right.
So, Ryosuke will finally...
Don't be hasty.  We have a race
with the Night Kids first.
Leave it to us.
Something's wrong with him, after all.
See?  He confessed.
It's a girl after all.
We have to do something.
We only have one week before the battle
against Takahashi Ryosuke.
This is really bad.
Panda Trueno
September 15th, 10pm
At Mt. Akina's peak
Takahashi Ryosuke
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
(The body style is the same as the same year 240SX stateside,
although equipped with a much hiher output turbo engine.)
Nissan has revived the Silvia in the S14 series  (1994-1998)
Silvia has three grades: Jack, Queen, és King.
Kenta's S14 is one of those Q Silvia models.
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
...into the bright future.
Let's make it sure over and over.
This passion will be eternal.
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
The flower of miracles.
Bad, bad, really bad!
What's so bad, Itsuki?
The battle against Takahashi Ryosuke is soon...
No time to think about that!
Takumi is lovesick over a girl at
an important time like this!
Lovesick over a girl?
He must have done this and that
and something really (bleep)!
Oh, not that again.
Huh?
Next time on Initial D:
"Severe Hill Climb!"
Initial
Next Time:
Severe Hill Climb
Don't miss it!