This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shita kemuri...
...misugita yume no daisyou.
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi.
Accel funde gomakasu.
Yoru ni kowareta mama shisen tsuyoku togarasete.
Dareno kimagure kara sekai sae mo owarisoude.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Obieta me wo shite lost in the night.
Ochiteku yume ni dakareru.
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart.
Jibun sae mo kizu tsukete.
Taoreru kurai ni love me so much.
Subete wo suttee anata wo...
...ai suru koto sae dekitara...
...kitto sunao ni naresou.
Is there a good cure to save
Takumi from his lovesickness?
Today's Friday, so September 15th
is still a week away.
We're lucky that it's not tomorrow.
By the way, there's a race between the
Redsuns and the Myogi Night Kids.
That's it!
We'll drag Takumi out there,
and watch the battle!
He'll be stimulated and recover!
That's a good idea!
That's it!
We'll knock him out and save him
from his lovesickness.
Severe Hill Climb
Hey, Dad, I've been thinking...
What is it?
I... drove on Mt. Usui the other day.
At first, I thought Usui was
totally different from Akina.
But... I don't know
how to say this...
They seemed almost the same
after I started driving.
Well done.
"Well done?"
Akina and Usui are totally different...
...but you simply drove in the same manner.
You tried what you do on Akina
in a different place.
Well, take care of the delivery.
Yeah.
Try what I do on Akina
in other places...
I know what you meant to say...
...just a little.
I'd better take a nap when I get home.
Takumi looks totally bored.
Alright, it's the time to proceed
with the plan!
Hey, Takumi!
Takumi!
Hey, big news!
Don't be surprised!
The Redsuns and Night Kids are racing!
And it's tonight!
Wha...?
Don't give me "wha," will you?
You're racing against Takahashi
Ryosuke next week...
...so you shouldn't miss this.
Right?
Alright, we've decided!
And it'd be a waste of gas
to go in two cars...
...so we'll go in your Eight-Six?
My...
I'm so excited!
Aren't you excited?
I'll be at the usual place at
seven o'clock tonight...
...so make sure you borrow
the Eight-Six, okay?!
As I thought, there're so many people.
Have you seen Takumi and Itsuki?
No.  I guess they aren't here yet.
I let Itsuki handle it, but I'm worried
if they'll make it.
What're you doing, Takumi?
It's gonna start soon.
Since you didn't want to take
the highway, we got lost.
You're so stingy.
What're you talking about?
You wanted to save gas and
didn't drive your Eight-Five.
Man, I've never heard of a Road Racer
who's bad at directions.
It must be because of a girl.
Okay, I got it.
Hurry, we don't have much time!
I've been waiting.
The hero always arrives late.
Myogi's valley is deep.
You'd better be concerned
about your life.
Can it.  Aren't you shaking from fear?
I'll defeat you so easily.
No one in the Night Kids can match me.
I hope your overconfidence
doesn't kill you.
We'd better start before
the rain comes.
Right.
The Eight-Six!
It's Akina's Eight-Six!
The Eight-Six?
Wow, look at all the people
in the galleries...
First, let's find those two.
I know.  Since there are
so many people, it's tough.
Where should we park the car?
Should we go to the peak?
There's a big parking lot there.
Okay.  I'll head for the peak for now.
So he's come after all.
It excites me whether
I like it or not.
Eight-Six...
...I'll show you how much
I've improved.
It's the Eight-Six!
From Akina?
Yeah.
So, that's the one...
Hey, Takumi, I noticed earlier.
Don't you think they're watching us?
Dunno.
"Dunno...?"
We really stand out...
...because Akina's Eight-Six is famous.
Everyone thinks so highly of you.
I was right about coming
in the Eight-Six.
What're you talking about?
Alright.
Forward.
Alright, alright.
Okay.
No oncoming traffic.
Starting the countdown!
Five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one.
Go!
What an incredible rocket start!
Keisuke'll win.
I know it.
Don't lose.  We can't disgrace ourselves
by losing on our home course.
Takahashi
It's begun.
Rain...
The FD's greatest advantage
is its manueverability.
Don't forget that, Keisuke.
Hey, Takumi, don't you think Myogi's
passes are similar to Akina's?
Are they?
I'd say that they remind me of Usui.
What?!  They're nothing like it!
It's no use.  His sickness is deeper
than the Marianas Trench.
Alright, Takumi, look carefully!
It's not as narrow as Usui, and this dynamic
climbing path is very similar to Akina's.
That's not what I mean.
The rhythm is similar.
"R...rhythm?"
He's tough.
The FD's fast in the corners.
I didn't expect anyone to keep up
with my R and I on Myogi.
He's started steering hard.
Is he going to increase the pace
to try and outrun me?
If you do that on the downhill, the tires
will definitely lose grip.
This's the midpoint, and
they just went past.
The 32 is ahead, but
the gap is minimal.
I see.
Tell me one thing.
Is Nakazato pulling away from
Keisuke at the corner's exit?
Well, he's slightly slower at the exit,
but he's keeping up overall.
His driving is very smooth.
It's very different from
Nakazato's drastic driving.
Okay, I got it.
Thanks.
If you're doing that, you've
improved, Keisuke.
The R32 is ahead, but there's
no gap in between.
They just passed us.
The 32 is ahead, but the
FD is right behind it.
Takeshi seems to be doing alright.
He's been practicing so hard.
Yeah, he's been totally different since
he was defeated by Akina's Eight-Six.
I've considered him my enemy even though
we're on the same team, but now...
...when I think about him driving
for our pride, my chest aches.
I've never had a feeling like this.
Here comes the 32.
The FD's right behind it.
Please win, Takeshi!
I'm counting on you!
I can only hear the sounds...
They're taking so long to get up here.
What?
Rain...
This is bad.  It's in the middle
of an attack at max speed!
The beginning of a rainstorm
is the most dangerous.
The dust and sand on the asphalt
are stirred up by the rain...
...and the road'll be extremely slippery.
You can lose grip very suddenly.
It's started raining.
Damn, the goal is so close...
The beginning of the rain
is most dangerous.
When you skid, it happens
without any warning.
It's getting heavier.
I hope it won't be canceled.
Say, Itsuki...
...the goal is over there, which means
this is the last corner, right?
That's Myogi's peak, so this short section just
before the goal is slightly downhill, isn't it?
So, the last part is downhill...
Here they come!
Now it's time to settle this match!
Impossible!  You won't be able
to turn at that speed!
That idiot's gonna crash
into the cliff!
I can do it.
I have feedback.
My FD's telling me to go!
It's coming this way!  Run!
Goal!
The FD won!
Cool!  It's so awesome!
Takahashi Keisuke is incredible!
This is the first time...
I've never been excited by watching
someone else race before.
I can't stand still after watching
something as incredible as that.
You were lucky, Takahashi Keisuke.
No.  It was because of my skill.
Say what?
The last corner was downhill...
...so I knew that the key would
be the front tires' condition.
Didn't you wear down your tires, so the
feedback from the front felt sluggish?
I saved my tires while
I kept pace with you.
This is the difference in our abilities!
Keisuke, that's just like you!
What should we do about the downhill?
We'll have to cancel it because of
this heavy rain.
Yeah.
Then, Keisuke, let me race
against Akina's Eight-Six!
What?
It's okay since it's not
our home course...
...and this isn't his home course either,
so the conditions are equal.
Hey!
Ah, Senpai...
Who's he?
I don't know.
Kenta...!
You're Fujiwara Takumi, aren't you?
I'm Nakamura Kenta of the Redsuns.
What do you say?  Will you accept
my challenge to a rain battle?
Hey, Kenta, without checking
with my brother...
Let's ask the galleries, Keisuke.
Guys, do you want to see a rain battle
between me and the Eight-Six?!
Go for it!
Do it!
T...this is bad.
He can't say no in this situation.
B...but Takumi has a battle against
Takahashi Ryosuke next week!
I'll race you first.
If you lose to me, you don't deserve
to race against Ryosuke.
Don't just stand there.
Say something.
I'm confident driving in the rain.
Don't tell me you're scared
of the rain...
N...no, the timing's bad!
He's... not in the right mood...
Okay, I'll do it.
W...wait...
No one can stop them now.
But...
The Eight-Six isn't only our target.
All Road Racers want to race
against the Eight-Six.
You understand that, don't you?
That's what I want.
When it comes to the downhill in the rain,
we can compare our techniques.
Go get your Eight-Six,
and pull up next to me.
Come with me, Itsuki.
Am I riding with you?
If I leave you here, I'll have to
come back and pick you up.
I don't want to waste my time, so let's go
home after we get to the base.
Okay, I'm getting in.
Hold it.
Sorry, Itsuki, but would
you sit in the back?
In the back?
Okay.
Is there any reason for this?
Well, maybe there is and
maybe there isn't...
What do you mean?
Aren't you sure yourself?
How should I hold my
body during drift?
I'll... leave it up to you.
Up to me...?  Hey!
It's just a short ride to the base,
so hang in there, okay?
They're not gonna cancel!
There'll be another downhill race!
The Eight-Six...
Akina's Eight-Six is gonna race!
Okay, no oncoming traffic.
Let's start!
This is totally unexpected.
Yeah, but there was nothing we could do.
Please watch me, Keisuke.
I like rain.
Before I joined the team, when I practiced
drifting alone, I chose rainy days.
I was poor, so I liked driving in the rain because
the tires didn't wear out so quickly.
I like your confidence, but don't
underestimate the rain.
I have more experience in
the rain than anybody else.
Don't worry.  If it's raining,
I have the advantage.
I'll win.  The rain is on my side.
Hey, Takumi, you don't
look very nervous.
Are you alright with
this rain battle?
I don't know.
I can't go as fast in the rain, so I'll
just drive like I normally do.
I don't know if I can drive fast or not.
I'll try not to push myself too hard.
If I damage the car, Dad'll hit me.
I see.
But if he loses, what'll happen to the
battle with Takahashi Ryosuke?!
I'll start the countdown!
Five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one.
Go!
YOU CALL THIS NORMAL?!
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na
hitomi ni miserate yuku
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitsu da to ieru
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Kagayaku mirai e
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Kiseki no hana yo
A rain battle...
Will you be alright, Kenta?
Yes, I'm confident.
Besides, Keisuke's watching,
so I have to win!
But your opponent is the Eight-Six,
and even Keisuke couldn't beat him.
That's why I want to avenge him!
It's for Keisuke!
But it's a route you've never
raced on before.
I'll be alright.  I'll drive so that
I won't disgrace Keisuke!
Wait a minute.  Don't tell me
that Keisuke's your...
Well...
Next time on Initial D:
"Downhill Rain Battle!"
Initial
Next Time:
Downhill Rain Battle
Don't miss it.