This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
INITIAL
Silver smoke in a freezing city...
...that's the cost of having an unachievable dream.
A frozen body and unforgettable desire...
You deceive yourself by stepping
on the accelerator.
Although depressed in the night,
your eyes are kept sharply open.
You feel like someone's careless
act could end the world.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Lost in the night with frightened eyes...
Embraced by a ruined dream.
Scared of loneliness, I'm missing you in my heart.
I almost hurt myself.
Love me so much and knock me out.
If only I can give up everything...
...and love you...
...I can be my true self.
Hey, Takumi, you don't
look very nervous.
Are you alright with
this rain battle?
I don't know.
I can't go as fast in the rain, so I'll
just drive like I normally do.
I don't know if I can drive fast or not.
I'll try not to push myself too hard.
If I damage the car, Dad'll hit me.
I'll start the countdown!
Five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one.
Go!
Downhill Rain Battle
The S14 took the front at the start.
Although it's a non-turbo,
it's got a 2.0 liter engine.
It's not only because of engine size...
...but he engaged the clutch on
the slippery road very well.
He deserves what he said about
driving in the rain.
No, the Eight-Six was holding
back at the start.
It's like he could catch up anytime,
once they get moving.
He took the front easily.
This is bad.
He'll pull away by using
superior engine power!
The gap is wide...
I guess uphill is too tough for the Eight-Six.
But it'll be downhill corners continuously
from here to the base.
Once they're on the downhill, the unbeatable
downhill driver's super technique will shine.
Ishimon Entrance
I don't think he'll remain behind...
Hello?
Oh, Brother?
The Eight-Six and Kenta in a rain battle?
Yeah.
That Kenta is so confident
against the Eight-Six...
...but rain isn't that easy, Brother.
You're right.
When playing at drift at slower
speeds, he's alright...
...but it's totally different in a battle.
Yeah, it'll be extremely difficult to open
the throttle to the limit in the rain.
If it was dry, the grip of
the tires would help...
...but in the rain, a car's behavior
will be very severe.
They don't run as you like unless you
use the weight shift effectively.
A small mistake will
result in big trouble.
Whether those two know the true
terror of driving in the rain yet...
It'll be interesting.
"Those two?"
You liar.
You're only really interested
in HIM, aren't you?
H...help me!
I don't want to die yet!
Damn, it's getting heavier.
His opponent is an Akagi Road Racer.
This isn't their home course,
so the conditions are equal.
The problem is this rain.
I wonder if he drives well in the rain.
In the rain...
He delivers tofu everyday, doesn't he?
Therefore, many times in the rain...
That's right!  He must!
If so, his driving technique...
will work in the rain.
I won't let you gain on me,
I'll keep pulling away.
My Q's can outrun turbos
when it rains.
He let the rear slide!
That S14 is pretty good in the rain!
FRs have a very difficult
time in the rain.
Yeah, even if you step on the accelerator,
it simply changes the heading of the car.
Here comes the Eight-Six!
I don't believe it!
How can he drift like that in this rain?
What the hell was that...?
His entry gave me a chill.
I've got goose bumps.
I...is this the driving of a man who was lovesick
over a woman just a while ago?
He said he wouldn't push hard,
so is this normal for him?!
I can't see anything because of the rain
and darkness. How can he drive?
It's too dark, and I can't
see where the road is!
Don't make that sound!
This speed is insane!
H...he's not human.
He's a monster!
I'm in the groove.
I'm in my rhythm!
I'm in really good condition today!
The legend of Akina's unbeatable
Eight-Six ends today.
Not Keisuke or Ryosuke...
...but I'll defeat the Eight-Six!
What the...?!
The Eight-Six is right behind me...?!
When?
It can't be.
What happened?
We've only cleared a few corners
since the downhill began.
It's impossible.
How did I get caught so easily
on the downhill in the rain...?
No...
...this doesn't mean I've lost!
They're less than
five centimeters apart!
Look!  The Eight-Six's
about to overtake him!
The Eight-Six's about to overtake him!
He passed him so easily...
It's... unbelievable.
It was worth waiting, even though
we got soaked.
Yeah.
I can't keep up.
The gap widens every time
we clear a corner!
I can't enter the corners
at the same speed.
What's the difference
between me and him?
Isn't the rain supposed
to be my ally?
Okay, I got it.
A report from the midpoint says that
the Eight-Six has passed the S14.
I see.
As I thought, Kenta was
no match for him.
Well, he did pretty good.
Now we know that the Eight-Six
is fast, even in the rain.
We knew that before the race.
Weather isn't a factor in
defeating the Eight-Six.
So it's Takahashi Ryosuke's turn.
Welcome!
Welcome.
So it's proven that
Takumi's fast in the rain.
He's getting more like a Road Racer.
He accepted the challenge
from the S14 himself.
His lovesickness is cured.
I guess our plan worked.
Hey, Itsuki, you were damn lucky...
...getting to sit in the Eight-Six's passenger
seat during the rain race.
It was reeeally scary!
I almost died!
I wasn't sitting in the passenger seat,
though.  I was in the rear seat.
The rear seat?
Why?
Dunno.
Takumi said he didn't have
any particular reason.
Oh, I got it.
There's a reason, and
I think I know why.
Really, Kenji?
What is it?
It's...
It's...?!
Because he gets distracted.
Don't you think so?
What if someone as noisy as Itsuki
was in the passenger seat?
That's true.
Oh, I see!
Wrong answer!
They're so carefree...
The reason he put him in the rear
seat was as an instant setting...
...to increase the weight on the
rear axle as much as possible.
Takumi probably knew it by
feeling instead of thinking.
Thank you.
I wonder how much more he'll grow...
Takumi!
Who's she?
Could she be...?
Takumi's girlfriend.
I thought so...!
Say what?
I didn't have any reason for coming by...
...but I was wandering around
and ended up here.
I see.
Am I a bother?
No.
H...he looks confused.
This is bad.
I don't want to disturb you at work,
so I'll go home.
Oh no!  He finally got well, but
he might get lovesick again!
Do something, Itsuki!
Even if you say that, races just don't
happen when you want them!
Anyway, he has the race against
Takahashi Ryosuke next week...
...so he has no time for women!
Okay!
Hey, Takumi!
Let's go driving on Akina tonight!
It looks dirty.
Is it because of the battle last night?
kisetsu hazure no asa ni kisha ni notte hitori kita e
I head north on a morning train at the season's end.
odayaka na kaze ga fuki tori ga sora ni kumo wo egaku
A calm wind blows, and a bird leaves a trail in the sky.
mioboe no aru keshiki fui ni toori kakaru basho de
I happen to see a familiar sight while driving by.
omoigakezu mitsuketa mukashi sunda machi wo
I unexpectedly find the town where I used to live.
kakenukete iku mado goshi ni omoide tachi mo machi nami mo
Memories and the view of the town pass by beyond the window.
Hello?
What?  You're who?
It's me.  It's been
a while, Bunta.
Oh, you.
How unusual of you.
Did you get in an accident and are calling
from a hospital or something?
Knock it off.
Anyway, Bunta, a lot of people
are talking about your son.
They say he's pretty good.
What?  Next Saturday?
Takahashi Ryosuke?
Who's that?
You don't know him?
He's well known in our world.
I heard that he's the number
one street racer in Gunma.
My son's gonna race against him...?
Answer me straight.
Who do you think will win?
I don't know.
I won't know until they race.
Sounds just like you, Bunta.
I'm tempted to watch your son, whom you
taught from the beginning to drift.
Your drift scared the shit out of me,
and I still can't shake it off.
That was a long time ago.
Mr. Tsuchiya, you're next.
Okay.
Later, Bunta.
You've improved a lot compared
to when you started, Itsuki.
Really?  Do you really think so?
I'm glad to hear that from you!
I've been practicing
grip driving so often.
Okay, for a special presentation, I'll show you
a super technique, the result of long practice.
The fantastic heel and toe!
Something's wrong.
I did it yesterday.
Okay, in the next corner!
One more time, please!
W...wait.
Hold on, Itsuki!
I'm relieved.
I was worried that you
were lovesick again.
Lovesick?
What do you mean?
I wasn't lovesick.
But you've been acting strange.
Like I told you before,
I was thinking.
I'm wondering what'll happen after I win
or lose against Takahashi Ryosuke.
Don't you know what I mean?
I don't.
Don't play riddle games.
Should there be anything
after that battle?
It'll be okay if there's
nothing after that.
You drive fast already.
I don't.
What're you talking about?
You are fast!
You've been winning
one race after another!
Is that it...?
I don't know how I'd be...
For now, you'd better concentrate on the
battle against Takahashi Ryosuke!
You don't have much time.
Takahashi Ryosuke...
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
...into the bright future.
Let's make it sure over and over.
This passion will be eternal.
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
The flower of miracles.
Ryosuke, you'll finally be able to test
your hypothesis  in battle.
I'm looking forward to this opportunity
to present my hypothesis.
Could you tell us your
hypothesis  in detail?
Do you know the formula
E equal M C squared?
It's Einstein's famous
Theory of Relativity.
First, I apply my own logic to it.
Take E as the opponent's average speed.
As long as my average speed exceeds it...
Next time on Initial D:
Initial
Next Time:
The White Comet of Akagi!
"The White Comet of Akagi!"
Don't miss it!