This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shita kemuri...
...misugita yume no daisyou.
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi.
Accel funde gomakasu.
Yoru ni kowareta mama shisen tsuyoku togarasete.
Dareno kimagure kara sekai sae mo owarisoude.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Obieta me wo shite lost in the night.
Ochiteku yume ni dakareru.
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart.
Jibun sae mo kizu tsukete.
Taoreru kurai ni love me so much.
Subete wo suttee anata wo...
...ai suru koto sae dekitara...
...kitto sunao ni naresou.
Yo, Takumi!
You look sleepy.
It's my nature.
Hey, it's time...
For the battle against Takahashi Ryosuke!
I'm looking forward to it so much that
I can't concentrate on studying.
He's the fastest in Gunma.
And Takahashi Ryosuke's very
popular with the girls!
Hey, Takumi, do you have a plan?
Not really.
I'm not that smart that I can change strategies
according to my opponent.
It's the same every time.
I'll just drive the fastest
way I know how.
If he's faster than that, I lose...
...and if he's slower, I win.
That's true...
But I'm counting on you!
If you defeat Takahashi Ryosuke...
...you'll be great!
It's so cool...
I'm so lame.
The White Comet of Akagi!
Welcome!
Oh, Kenji.
I've got something interesting.
Interesting?
Could that be that rare
adult video you have?
Sorry, it's not.
It's even more exciting.
More exciting?
It's a battle.
It doesn't look like Akina.
Just keep watching.
Hey, let me see that part again, slower.
Ta...Takahashi Ryosuke?!
He looks a lot younger...
It's a battle from three years ago.
How did you get this?
An enthusiast took a few videos.
Incredible!
Look at that sharp turn-in.
It's the work of a god.
Awesome.
I was in the gallery at this battle!
It's so nostalgic...
Takahashi Ryosuke didn't belong to
any team then, and he drove alone.
He was called the White Comet of Akagi.
"The White Comet of Akagi...?"
Sounds so cool.
I'm getting excited.
Then, what about the Redsuns?
He formed the Akagi Redsuns later,
by gathering highly skilled drivers.
So they're all high level, and different
from a group of friends like us.
Today, after adding his brother, Keisuke, they
became known as the Takahashi Brothers.
But the "White Comet of Akagi"
still sounds right to me.
What're you guys watching?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Turn the video off!
No, it's alright.
Let's take a look.
It's incredible.
Takumi is racing against those guys?
Yes.
The galleries will be completely
packed at the next battle.
Naturally, because of Takahashi Ryosuke...
...but also because Takumi is famous
as the driver of Akina's Eight-Six.
Right.
He's the mysterious downhill specialist
who appeared so suddenly on Akina!
Something like that, and it's so exciting.
Who do you think will win?
Well?
I'm sorry to say this, but I honestly don't
think Takumi has a chance of winning.
He's got a tough opponent this time.
I think so too.
Takahashi Ryosuke is fast.
Ultra fast.
I...is he that fast?
Yeah, he was way out of our
league even three years ago.
And he's improved his skills since then.
Not only on the mountain passes...
...but he's also continuously winning
in autocross and circuit racing.
He's rewritten many course records,
and he hasn't been defeated.
His undefeated legend
hasn't been ruined yet.
And they say there hasn't been a race
that's made him drive seriously yet.
They say that he can defeat any
opponent with just half his skill.
So no one has seen him
driving at his limit.
Well, if Takumi can keep up
with him, that'll be enough.
B...but...
Here you go with the
pessimistic thoughts again.
Why can't you be more optimistic?
Then, who do you think will win?
Takumi defeated his brother, Keisuke,
and the Night Kids' Nakazato!
He defeated the Sil-Eighty on Usui!
He also won the gumtape death
match... and the rain battle!
I...I think he can compete.
Ryosuke even outclasses the rest
of the highly skilled Redsuns.
He's charismatic.
He's not on the same level
as Keisuke or Nakazato.
Well, if it were a boxing match, the betting
would be ten to one, I guess.
I want Takumi to win.
Not only because he's my friend...
...but also I want my dream car,
the Eight-Six, to outrun the FC!
Don't cry.
Guys like cars, don't they?
Yeah.
Are they that great?
They are.  I can go anywhere I want.
If you were told to choose between your girlfriend
and a car, which would you choose?
I can't compare them.
A girl is a girl, and cars are cars.
Driving a car is difficult.
Lately, I've been thinking more
about how to drive faster.
I feel good when I think about it.
Takumi, you're...
...perverted.
What do you mean, saying that
I'm perverted so suddenly?
Sorry, I just felt like it.
It's girl's intuition.
But now I know.
I feel like I know the
secret of your charm.
W...what're you talking about?
You're not making sense.
It's alright.  I don't think
you'd understand.
Geez.
When's the battle?
The night after tomorrow.
You're going to race against
a very fast person, right?
Yes.
I want to see you race.
But... I'd better not.
Just don't have an accident.
You can lose, but don't have an accident.
No matter what.
Promise me?
Hey, Ryosuke, there's another professional
team asking you to join.
They contacted me.
Another one?
Cool.
Which one?
That famous Hoshiya Racing Team.
They're looking for a promising
young driver.
They say they want to see you
as soon as possible...
...so they're asking you to
contact them soon.
You'd be very competitive
in professional racing!
I'm excited just imagining it!
What're you going to do, Brother?
Please decline.
As I said before, I have no intention
of becoming a professional driver.
How can you say that!
Why don't you at least listen to them?
He's right, Ryosuke!
I'm not interested in professional racing.
Street racing is more interesting
because anyone can race freely.
To me, autocross and circuit driving are
only processes for mastering the street.
All I care about now...
...is the Eight-Six this coming Saturday.
Hey, you're closed, right?
Why don't you come for a drive?
With you?
Yeah.
I changed the suspension settings, so
I'm going to take it for a test spin.
Take a test spin...?
I don't like the way you say that.
Hey, Bunta...
Yeah.
Did you change the suspension
settings to win the next battle?
Sort of.
Yuichi, I'm gonna push it a little.
W...wait!
Okay, but just for a little.
Here it is.
Here comes the corner.
Incredible entry speed.
Geez, I feel the side G
force from a little aft.
Hey, y...you idiot!
Bunta, what're you doing?
Well, I feel like a smoke.
S...stop!
How can you look away?!
No.
Not bad...
Okay, now I'm gonna drive seriously.
LET ME OUT!
The engine and suspension tune-ups for
winning the next battle are complete.
How much is it making, Brother?
Well, it's about 260 horsepower at max.
260 horsepower?!
That means it's been detuned!
I believe you had at least 350 HP!
Correct.
You lowered the power...
What's the point of making it slower?
You'd better remember this.
In order to drive fast, sometimes
you have to lower the power.
That's the difficulty of street racing.
The key to mastering the
downhill is total balance.
I tuned my FC to have total balance
for both downhill and uphill.
Because I had confidence in handling
big power on the downhill...
...I changed the turbine, and
increased the pressure.
But now, I have to lower the power.
For whatever the reason, this detune
is disgraceful for me.
Even if I lose my pride,
I still have to win.
Which means Akina's Eight-Six
is that fast, doesn't it?
I'm glad to have met someone who
can make me feel this way.
After such a long time, my
Road Racer blood is boiling.
Follow me.
He's fast.
Although he lowered the power...
...the exit speed is definitely faster.
He won't lose.
No way he will!
I'm not the Redsuns'
Takahashi Ryosuke now...
...I'm the solo driver, the
White Comet of Akagi...
...Takahashi Ryosuke.
I'll win the battle no matter what.
Takumi!
Hey!
Race day's here!
Yeah.
I'm frustrated, because everyone says
that Takahashi Ryosuke will win.
It's like a match between a champion
sumo wrestler and a neophyte.
Aren't you frustrated?
Don't you have a secret plan
to turn the situation around?
"Secret plan...?"
Nope.
Road Racers are heading for the mountain.
It's time...
Manager.
I've cleaned the outside,
so let me call it a day.
Okay, good work.  You're going
to see the battle tonight, right?
Yes.
Do you still think Takumi will lose?
Even if Takumi's a genius,
he's only a high school kid.
He hasn't experienced that many battles.
I wonder how long he can keep up
with Takahashi Ryosuke.
I disagree.
I think he might be able to win.
Why?
Because...
Yo.
We're in a hurry, so excuse us.
Okay.
I have only one reason for thinking
that he might be able to win.
Takumi is Bunta's son...
That crazy Bunta.
As I thought, the galleries are packed.
If I were Takumi, I'd run away.
I'd be so nervous if I had to race
in front of so many people.
That's Usui's Sil-Eighty.
As I thought...
They're both pretty nice...
Yeah.
Let's see... I think this is the place.
We should be able to see the battle
in a combination of corners.
By the way, Mako...
...which one are you rooting for?
Which one...?
The Eight-Six, isn't it?
Me too.
That Eight-Six has a mysterious charm.
The charm that can only be felt by
those who've raced with him.
Even if you lose, you still
want to support him.
Besides, he's...
...so cute, right?
Oh, Sayuki...
It's almost 9:30.
It's almost time.
I'm so excited!
Here come the Redsuns.
That's the Takahashi Brothers!
They're so cool!
Yeah, the king of the streets!
Ryosuke!
Finally, Takahashi Ryosuke has appeared.
When Takumi appears, the cast
will be complete.
The Eight-Six isn't here yet.
As usual.
He always shows up at the
very last moment.
Keisuke, I've been thinking
about this for a while.
If I lose on the street...
...I'll retire.
What're you talking about?
You won't lose!
Just listen.
That doesn't mean I'll stop driving.
I'll withdraw from being top driver.
I'll still be involved with the team
in a different way.
What about the Redsun's project
to be the fastest in Kanto?
If you don't drive, it'll be impossible!
Don't make such a pathetic face.
I haven't lost yet.
But I want you to know that there'll be a
time for a new generation to take over.
Someday, I'll lose to someone.
Now that I've said that...
...I can say that I've met two drivers
who might defeat me.
One of them is you, Keisuke.
Me?
Yes.  I can sense a promising
talent in you.
You will definitely get faster.
And the other is...
He's come!
Takumi's here!
Hey, Takumi!
Brother, could the other be
the Eight-Six driver?
I haven't lost to anyone yet.
Tonight, I'll drive,
drifting at full throttle.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na
hitomi ni miserate yuku
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitsu da to ieru
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Kagayaku mirai e
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Kiseki no hana yo
What's wrong, Takumi?
I've been racing because
the situation called for it.
This time, I feel like
it's a little different.
I'm so excited, but I don't know what to do.
It's fun and interesting to drive.
Anyway, I don't know how much I can do,
but I want to try my best...
He's different from the usual Takumi!
Takumi is hyped up!
Next time on Initial D:
"Last Great Battle!"
Initial
Next Time:
Last Great Battle
Don't miss it!