This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
INITIAL
Silver smoke in a freezing city...
...that's the cost of having an unachievable dream.
A frozen body and unforgettable desire...
You deceive yourself by stepping
on the accelerator.
Although depressed in the night,
your eyes are kept sharply open.
You feel like someone's careless
act could end the world.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Lost in the night with frightened eyes...
Embraced by a ruined dream.
Scared of loneliness, I'm missing you in my heart.
I almost hurt myself.
Love me so much and knock me out.
If only I can give up everything...
...and love you...
...I can be my true self.
Takumi, this is for you.
Who from?
From Takahashi Ryosuke.
Takahashi...
...Ryosuke.
He's fast.
Although he lowered his power...
...his exit speed is definitely faster.
He won't lose.
No way he will!
"Battle?"
Are you going to fight someone?
No.  We just call a car race a "battle."
If you don't like it,
why don't you ignore him?
It's not that I don't like it.
I'm not going to run away, although
I don't know if I can win.
Do you still think Takumi will lose?
Yes.
Even if Takumi's a genius,
he's only a high school kid.
I wonder how long he can keep up with
Takahashi Ryosuke.
I only have one reason for thinking
that he might be able to win.
Takumi is Bunta's son.
That crazy Bunta.
Keisuke, I've been thinking
about this for a while.
If I lose on the street...
...I'll retire.
Now that I've said that...
...I can say that I've met two drivers
who might defeat me.
One of them is you, Keisuke.
Me?
And the other is...
Last Great Battle
Cute.
Takumi!
Good luck, Takumi.
You know, I... I believe
that you'll win!
So outrun Takahashi Ryosuke and become
the greatest star in Gunma!
Takumi...
Itsuki, he understands,
so leave him alone.
You're late.
It's just before 10 o'clock.
You're as laidback as usual.
I've been waiting for you.
I don't know how someone as young
as you learned all these techniques...
...but you impress me.
I've driven Akina's mountain passes more than
anyone else, so I'm familiar with them.
I don't use any special techniques.
You must've misunderstood,
and think too highly of me.
That's interesting.
I guess you don't know
much about yourself.
You're interesting.
I want to spend more time
talking to you someday.
Brother...
Let's get started.
It's gonna be a fun night.
Alright, move your cars!
Okay!
The Redsuns'll manage the
race again.  Is that alright?
Yeah.
Please assign some people from
the Speedstars as officials.
Okay.
Iketani, I'll be at the finish.
We're counting on you.
Keisuke, I'll be at the five
sequential hairpins.
Ryosuke will win, right?
We'll have our revenge, won't we?
Of course.
No matter how fast he is,
my brother won't lose.
I think so, too.
Well, I'm going.
Hello, this is Fujiwara Tofu...
Oh, it's you.
Bunta, I just got to Akina.
The galleries are packed.
You'd be surprised.
So?
Do you think Takumi'll win?
His opponent is the street king,
the fastest in Gunma.
I don't know.
If you don't have anything else
to say, I'm hanging up.
Bun...Bunta.
Bunta, wait!
Don't hang up on me!
Alright.  Report on each corner's condition.
Okay.  This is the first corner.
We're ready.
This is from the skating rink.
The straightaway is clear.
This is the No. 17 hairpin.
We're ready.
This is the five sequential hairpins.
There's no traffic.
We're ready.
This is No. 6.  We're moving the
gallery's cars, but it'll be ready.
The tension's so high,
and my throat's dry!
My heart's pounding.
The entire mountain pass
is filled with tension.
Yeah.
I wonder if Takumi'll be alright...
Takumi, your opponent is one
of the best Road Racers.
It's alright to lose,
but drive your best!
Takumi, good luck!
I believe that you'll win!
There's no way my brother'll lose.
But when the Eight-Six races, unexpected
things happen on Mt. Akina...
Excuse me, but what about the battle?
It hasn't started yet.
Oh, I see.  Thank you.
This is the starting point.
How's the finish line?
Yes, it's ready.
Begin any time.
Okay, let's start.
Wait!
Let me count it down.
I want to do it for this
particular race.
All right?
I won't let anybody else do it for the race
between my brother and the Eight-Six.
I'm gonna count down!
Five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one.
GO!
Go, Takumi!
Good, good!
The start was even!
Oh, Takumi's taken the lead!
Takumi, go for it!
That's my brother's style.
For an important race...
...he lets his opponent go ahead and
then passes him at the critical point.
He's won that way before, and there's no
error in his logic for the fastest driving.
Both are incredible!
What a tight twin drift!
Takahashi Ryosuke usually
doesn't use drift that hard!
Both are showing off from the start!
It's drift versus drift!
Even Takahashi Ryosuke is using
drift from the very start.
He must be trying to win with
Takumi's specialty...
...to keep his status as the street king.
Takumi's doing great, it's
gonna be a great battle!
Takumi, please win, no matter what!
Right, Iketani?
Yeah... right.
I'm surprised.
The Eight-Six's motion is totally
different from before.
As I thought, he's improved.
He doesn't countersteer at the end
of his drift like before.
But the angle of the countersteer
right after the turn-in is also smaller.
I don't understand.  How did
he eliminate that weakness?
He hasn't raced very many times, but he's
improved, one race after another.
I'll have to change my simulation.
But that's all, and the result
will be the same.
My theory for the fastest
driving is correct.
Let me make this clear, Takeshi.
I didn't park here because
I saw your car.
So don't get the wrong idea.
I decided to come here
beforehand, so get lost.
No.
I decided to watch the race from here.
Why don't YOU get lost?
Well, the amateurs in the galleries
chose famous places...
...like the five sequential hairpins.
Right, but they can't settle
the match there.
This is the only place
they can make a go at it.
You thought so, too...
I have to say it's just what
I'd expect from you.
Same to you.
Besides, there's only
us two around here.
Those who don't know us might think
that we're close friends.
Disgusting.
Here they come...
Both cars are so close
to the guardrail!
Incredible.
It's so shocking.
No time to waste.
I'd better call him.
What a pain...
This is Fujiwara...
Hey, Bunta, can you hear me?!
Not you again...
Hey, listen.
They just passed in front of me.
Both cars passed by while
drifting really hard.
Takumi's Eight-Six has taken the lead...
...and the FC is right on his tail.
Takumi's in front?
That's bad.
Bad?
Why?
Think about it, Yuichi.
The chaser has an advantage over
the one who's driving in front.
It's just common sense.
He's right.
The one chasing can closely watch the line
and rhythm taken by his opponent.
Those who're skilled enough can
copy that easily.
But if he can pull away...
The one driving in front
feels a lot of pressure.
If your opponent follows you at the same
speed, you feel mentally cornered.
If you can't pull away while
you're driving your best...
...you start wondering if the opponent is
far more skilled than expected.
Especially since Takumi has no experience
in managing the pace.
He must be scared by now.
He is?
I'll call you once it's over.
Will he lose...?
Nah.
They're coming!
My god!
I can't believe it!
This is corner number 24!
The Eight-Six and Ryosuke's
FC have just passed by.
And I got the split time,
and it's incredible!
If they keep this pace...
...they'll shorten the Eight-Six's last
course record by 7 or 8 seconds!
Anyway, that's my report.
They're gonna be faster than
our race by 7 or 8 seconds?!
Gimme a break.
So this is what my brother
meant by driving his best.
It's almost scary.
Tonight's battle will become legendary.
Takumi's still in front.
Alright!
He'll do it, Senpai.
Yeah, but I wonder how
long he can hold on.
His opponent is Takahashi Ryosuke.
If Takumi finishes the race safely,
I'll be satisfied.
He's staying right on my tail even though
I'm driving at full throttle.
I can't shake him, no matter
how fast I drive.
It's no good, I might lose this battle.
Takahashi Ryosuke...
...he's not a driver someone
like me can defeat.
I don't want to lose...
...but I'm losing.
a remake standalone sub based on
fansubfilesanime's release
Original translations and
scripts by Central Anime
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
Repro sub by FXM-ID Project II
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
By Fans for the Fans!
Not for Sale or Rent!
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
...into the bright future.
Let's make it sure over and over.
This passion will be eternal.
Bloom red like a rose.
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
The flower of miracles.
I think Takumi'll win, as I expected...
I don't want to lose...
Hello, this is Fujiwara Tofu Shop...
I don't know if I'll be able to...
...with an Eight-Six...
...his sense of drift...
Ryousuke, I...!
...Takumi'll definitely win this race!
Go, Takumi!
That's it!
Takumi, keep up!
Go for the win!
So many opinions are crossing over,
but the race'll be settled.
Next time on Initial D, the last episode:
"New Downhill Legend!"
Initial
Next Time:
New Downhill Legend!
Don't miss it!