This story is fiction. The names of people,
places and groups are imaginary.
Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shita kemuri...
...misugita yume no daisyou.
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi.
Accel funde gomakasu.
Yoru ni kowareta mama shisen tsuyoku togarasete.
Dareno kimagure kara sekai sae mo owarisoude.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Obieta me wo shite lost in the night.
Ochiteku yume ni dakareru.
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart.
Jibun sae mo kizu tsukete.
Taoreru kurai ni love me so much.
Subete wo suttee anata wo...
...ai suru koto sae dekitara...
...kitto sunao ni naresou.
He's staying right on my tail even though
I'm driving at full throttle.
I can't shake him, no matter
how fast I drive.
It's no good, I might lose this battle.
Takahashi Ryosuke...
...he's not a driver someone
like me can defeat.
I'm losing.
New Downhill Legend!
Excellent.  It almost gives
me goose bumps.
He's taking an ideal line.
I can keep up with him because
I'm copying his line and rhythm.
But it'd be extremely difficult to do
the same if I was driving alone.
Those who can drive fast only on
straightaways are amateurs.
Those who've mastered the
corners are middle rank.
An advanced driver makes the difference not in the
straightaways or corners but in the third point.
To master the third point is my theory
for the fastest driving's main theme.
I've been looking for an ideal
sample for my theory.
I didn't expect to find it so nearby.
He's scary.
They're close!
Which is it?  Takahashi Ryosuke
...or the Eight-Six?
Man, how dynamic!
It's so impressive...
No good, I can't shake him!
They're coming!
I can hardly stand still,
hearing that sound!
The straightaway to the five sequential
hairpins is long, so they pick up speed.
It's gonna be a severe braking match...
There they are!
The Eight-Six is in front!
Ryosuke...
This is the entrance to the
five sequential hairpins.
Both cars just appeared.
The Eight-Six is in front!
Say what?  The Eight-Six...?
You're going too fast.
You've screwed up.
Dammit, turn!
How reckless.
A big power car can recover
by using its power...
...but you did it with an Eight-Six.
Ryosuke's FC has taken the lead!
Say what?
The Eight-Six understeered at the entrance...
...so Ryosuke's FC passed the Eight-Six!
The Eight-Six understeered...?
It's great!
Ryosuke outclasses him!
Ryosuke will definitely win!
He's strange.
He has some weak points
I'd never have expected.
I was going to stay behind a little
longer to hide my plan...
Now that I'm in front, I'll be in trouble
if he catches up with me.
Before he recovers, I'd better pull
away and settle this race.
The FC just passed by, and the
Eight-Six is a little behind.
R...Ryosuke's time is incredible!
At this pace, he'll break the course
record by twelve seconds!
Twelve seconds...?!
It's over.  My brother
will keep pulling away.
It gives me chills, hearing that.
Even if Takumi loses, this won't
hurt his reputation.
Takahashi Ryosuke is simply
overwhelming.
The battle isn't over yet!
I believe that Takumi'll overtake him!
But...
He's always been like that!
He's reversed every difficult
situation at the end.
I'm sure that Takumi'll
overtake him this time!
Please, get to the base safely.
Don't think of doing something
too reckless, Takumi.
The most appealing part of a rotary engine isn't
the power from the light and compact engine...
...but that it makes the car agile, by providing
an ideal front/rear weight balance.
I like the spirit of aiming higher, which
can be felt in rotary engine cars.
For my pride's sake, I won't let the Eight-Six
outperform my rotary engine car in corners.
Just like them.  Both Takahashi
Ryosuke and Takumi.
The speed is totally different
from those drift kids.
Sayuki, what's going to happen?
Now that Takahashi Ryosuke's in front,
he won't let his opponent pass him.
But... his opponent is Takumi.
Takumi hasn't given up, because he's taking
a more difficult line than the FC.
It's the line of one who
has mastered Akina.
I thought that he'd pull away, but surprisingly,
the gap hasn't widened much.
I still have a chance!
I'm gaining on him.
I'm slowly getting closer!
Damn.
The front tires have started
losing their grip suddenly.
Tire deterioration because of the heat...?
Because I copied the Eight-Six's
driving style in the first half...
...I put more stress on the front
tires than I expected.
The Eight-Six is slowly gaining on me.
I wonder if his tires are alright.
Well, even if the tires are a little worn,
it won't disturb my driving.
At this rate, I won't be
able to catch him.
I have to gain on him fast.
Damn, is this my limit?
Should I try it...?
Dad said there's another
way of using the gutter.
Oh, good work.
Dad, I found a good way to avoid
skidding on a snowy road.
I let the tire grab the gutter.
The car turns so easily.
Driving in the gutter...?
I've used that technique often.
Oh, so you've already used it...
Takumi, there are two ways
to use Akina's gutters.
The way you just found is an
entry oriented method...
...so that you don't understeer
at the entrance.
There's also exit oriented gutter driving.
The timing for dropping and
freeing the tires is different.
It's difficult.
Practice hard to learn it.
I've never tried it, but I have to
take the chance.
I'd better do it.
Alright, let's go!
What... did he do?!
What the hell did he do...?!
They're coming, Shingo.
Judging from the squeals, they're
really close to each other.
It's just as I expected.
This point is the only place
for settling the race.
Before a braking competition, there's
a straightaway to pick up speed.
The passes are narrow, but this corner has
three lanes, so they can choose any path.
Moreover, this is a complex corner
with two turning radiuses.
The goal's right after this, so there're
no other places to pass.
The one who's in front at
this corner's exit will win!
There they are!
The FC's ahead!
Alright, he's right behind!
What're you gonna do?
How're you going to attack?
You can't pass from outside,
so take the inside!
Inside or outside?!
From the outside?!
Takahashi Ryosuke didn't
open up the inside!
It was impossible to take the inside!
The FC's taken the front!
The inside has a definite advantage!
The FC's drifting outward!
Incredible!
His speed's too fast for the
sharper curve at the exit!
No way!
Their lines are gonna cross!
There!  They're coming!
What...?  No way!
Really?!
How could Ryosuke lose?!
It's Takumi's car.
Takumi...
It's the Eight-Six!
The Eight-Six won!
I don't believe it!
It's the Eight-Six!
With an incredible course record!
My brother... lost.
His undefeated legend has ended.
Banzai!
Takumi won!
The Eight-Six won!
Incredible!
He did it!
Banzai!  Banzai!  Banzai!
Hey, are you listening, Bunta?!
Takumi won!
Don't be so excited.
Of course he did.
It's an incredible course record!
I got it.  See you later.
Damn!
So, he won...
That Takumi...
We saw an incredible event.
It shocked me so much.
I don't believe it.
Shingo, stay away from me.
Those who don't know us might think
that we're close friends!
Same to you!
Takumi did it.  He defeated Takahashi
Ryosuke, isn't it cool?
I'd better ask him out...
Why don't you ask that guy?
What's his name...?
Iketani?
Yes, that guy!
You still have a chance.
Why don't we try a double date?
Uh, I have something
I'd like to ask you.
Would you tell me?
Why did you wait for me in
the middle of the battle?
You think that I slowed down in
the second half on purpose?
That's your misperception.
Then why...?
Because you increased your pace.
I tried to minimize the slowdown of my pace,
because the front tires were wearing down.
Tires...?
My tires aren't an excuse, because
we drove under equal conditions.
I lost.
I...
I don't think I'm faster.
I can't believe such a thing.
You're strange.  I've never met
someone like you.
Don't be satisfied with
Akina's small stage.
There's a bigger world out there.
Fujiwara Takumi, you were faster.
See you again.
yoake no sora e mado wo hiraite
I open the windows to see the night sky.
yawarakai kaze ni tokesou na kimi no suhada
Your body seems to be fading in the calm wind.
sotto dakiyosete kuchizukeru hodo
I gently bring you closer, and give you a kiss.
It's almost fall...
fushigi na kurai kokoro wa furueteru
I wonder why I feel so nervous.
Shall we head home, Takumi?
sabitsuita door wo tataku afuredashisou na atsui tokimeki
I'm almost knocking on a rusty door, and my passion is overflowing.
This car is small, but it's
very fast, isn't it?
It's pretty, so I like it.
sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo karada juu de tsutaetai
This feeling is all I want you to know with all of my body.
kono koini yowasetekure kiseki no hana yo
Let me be drowned in this love. The flower of miracles.
Ta...Takumi!
ai ni tsukarehate samayotteta koro
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
Y...you've gotten another challenge!
yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
It's hard this time!  It's gonna be
really hard this time!
kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitsu da to ieru
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
kagayaku mirai e
...into the bright future.
ah kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Let's make it sure over and over.
Okay, get going.
In about half a year or so, I might
even be faster than you, Dad.
jounetu yo eien e todoke
This passion will be eternal.
Don't be silly.
I wouldn't lose to a kid.
sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
tsuyoku tsuyoku azayaka ni
Strongly, strongly and brightly.
motto motto kono omoi wo karada juu de tsutaetai
I want you to know more about my feelings with all of my body.
sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
tsuyoku tsuyoku dakishimete
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
utsukushiku karen ni sake
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
kiseki no hana yo
The flower of miracles.
Original translations and subtitle
scripts by Central Anime
Repro sub v3 typeset based on fansubfilesanime's release
Timing, additional editing, typesetting & car notes
for the conversion by the FXM-ID Project II
A bigger world...?