Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves a lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
Are you serious ?
With that Mogi Natsuki ?
Everyone was after her.
She's got such
a hot body.
She'll listen to
anything I say.
I'll teach her slowly.
Teach what ?
You know.
All girls are the same.
Even if they resist,
they'll be obedient anyway.
I took her up to the
roof the other day...
Knock it off already !
What's the matter
with you, Takumi ?
Is that the way you're supposed to talk to your seniors ?
Don't, Takumi.
You're pissing me off,
you assholes !
Say what ?!
Stop, Takumi !
Stop !
A Road Racer's Pride
You're so mean, Takumi.
How can you leave such a cute girl alone and go to your own world ?
I asked you if you
have some girl you like.
I have someone I'm
interested in a little, too.
Iketani.
Hey, where did Iketani go ?
Iketani ?
I witnessed the incident !
On the frightening Mt. Akina downhill
where a scream echoes...
...of Iketani in the
third corner, passing out !
That Iketani went on
a delivery a while ago.
I see.
If Iketani isn't around,
I guess I have to ask Takumi.
I want you to take a sales
slip to Yamada Trading.
You can use my car.
Okay.
Manager.
You know, I have
a license, too.
Why do you only ask
Iketani or Takumi ?
Well, on that...
Put your hand on
your chest and think.
Do you get it ?
Nope.
In other words, I can trust Iketani and Takumi's driving...
...but if it's you...
...my precious car might
come back with a dent.
A dent ?!
That's why.
Shit, once I get an Eight-Six, I'll become a good driver quickly.
A~~32 !
Welcome !
Cool.
The 32 is so awesome.
N...Night Kids ?!
Hey, I'm Nakazato.
A local guy told me that I could speak to the Speedstars' members if I came here.
Can you tell me when I should visit Akina to see the Eight-Six ?
Don't you know what
I'm talking about ?
Aren't you a member
of the Speedstars ?
Member of the Speedstars ?
It sounds so wonderful.
I guess I came
to the wrong station.
No, you came to
the right place !
I'm the best friend of the driver of the Eight-Six.
Say what ?
We're called the fastest Eight-Six
downhill pair by our team.
Really ?
Well, he's a little
better than me.
I've never heard that the
Speedstars' skill level was so high.
Anyway, I can contact the Eight-Six driver you're looking for.
He's my best friend.
Then I'll count on
you to tell him.
Next Saturday
at 10:00 pm...
Next Saturday~~~
at 10:00 pm...?~~~
Nakazato of the Night Kids will be waiting at the peak of Mt. Akina.
``At the peak
of Mt. Akina.''
There'll only
be one race.
Wait...is that...?!
Wait a minute !
Hey...
I'm in big trouble.
Wasn't that a
challenge for Takumi ?
Holy shit !
How should I tell him ?!
Takumi !
What're you
doing there ?
Don't worry
about that, Takumi.
Anyway, if you're
free this Saturday...
...do you feel like
driving on Akina ?
Nope.
Why not ?
Sorry, but unless I have
a special reason...
...I won't go
out and drive.
Takumi, thanks.
Come on in and
have some coffee.
Okay.
Hey !
This is bad.
This is really bad.
Good work.
Hey, Takumi.
Let me ask
you something.
Hypothetically speaking, if a Road Racer challenged you...
...you'd race him,
wouldn't you ?
I don't like that,
so I wouldn't.
Then I'd be in trouble !
Why would you
be in trouble ?
Well, that's my problem...
...but a Road Racer has
to race when challenged.
That might be so if
you're a Road Racer...
...but I don't want
to be a Road Racer.
No way.
And I don't like the idea that I ``have to'' race when challenged.
This is bad.
Extremely bad.
What am I gonna do ?
Two more days
till the race.
I'll show that Eight-Six guy
and Takahashi Ryosuke...
...that I'm
number one.
Iketani !
You accepted the match against the Night Kids of Myogi, didn't you ?
If you did something that important,
you should've told the rest of us.
I don't know anything about that.
What're you talking about ?
What do you mean ?
Everyone's talking about it.
It's gonna be a single match on the downhill between the Eight-Six and a 32.
The Eight-Six and...?
Never heard of it.
But they say that Nakazato of the Night Kids came here himself and made the challenge.
Takumi, did you
accept his challenge ?
I don't know about it.
No one knows
about it ?
That's strange.
I'm sorry.
Itsuki, don't tell me...
I...I accepted it.
I'm sorry !
Nakazato of the Night Kids
came here yesterday.
Neither Iketani nor Takumi
were here at that moment.
I...
I was talking to him, pretending to be a member of the Speedstars...
...and it just happened.
Why'd you keep something so
important a secret until now ?!
I was going to tell you,
but I couldn't find a chance.
I'm sorry, Takumi.
Forgive me.
It was my fault.
Even if you say so...
Forgive me, forgive me.
Hey, that 32
is here again.
It's gonna race the Eight-Six of the Speedstars tomorrow night, right ?
I'll definitely
come and watch.
Yeah.
Nakazato will challenge the Eight-Six that Takahashi Keisuke couldn't beat.
We can't miss it.
It looks like a match between the Speedstars and the Night Kids...
...but in reality...
...it's a clash of pride between the Redsuns' Takahashi brothers and the Night Kids.
Whoever wins, Takahashi Ryosuke won't just stand by and watch.
Sleepless nights will come one
after another this summer.
Anyway, this isn't good.
What should we do ?
Since those rumors have spread so widely, we can't withdraw.
I'd better ask Takumi
to drive myself.
But even if it's Takumi, we're at a disadvantage because the opponent's a 32.
Nakazato of the Night Kids is as famous as the Takahashi brothers.
It's gonna be
a tough battle.
It might be a
hopeless battle...
...and if I think about it,
I just can't ask him.
We can't.
Here.
Hey, Dad...
How good is the 32 ?
The 32 ?
It's great.
Could you defeat the 32
on the downhill ?
I'd win.
Whether it's a 32 or
not makes no difference.
Do you think
I could win ?
I don't know.
But it'd be
a close match.
Why're you
asking me ?
Are you going to
race against a 32 ?
No reason.
I just wanted to ask.
I'm off.
So the next
one's a 32.
I guess I have to change the settings on the Eight-Six.
I don't know, but it'd
be a close match.
I had the feeling I'd see you
if I came here at this time.
It was about this time
when I first saw you.
I heard that you're gonna race against Nakazato of the Night Kids.
People are talking about
you all over the place.
Let me tell you that
I didn't agree to race him.
Say what ?
He challenged me while I was away,
and I'm not interested in racing.
What do you mean
you're not interested ?
Nakazato of the Night Kids personally challenged you, didn't he ?
Why don't you accept ?
And beat the
shit out of him.
You should be
able to do that.
Why are you saying that ?
It's none of your business.
It sure as hell is...
...because you
defeated me.
Only the Takahashi brothers of
the Redsuns will defeat you.
Until then, don't lose, even
if it's against the 32.
I said I'm
not doing it !
Besides, I don't
have any reason.
Reason ?
What do you mean ?
Why does a Road Racer
need a reason to race ?
I'm not a Road Racer.
Stop screwing
around with me !
Are you trying
to be sarcastic ?
You must've been driving a lot
to acquire such great technique.
Why would someone other than a Road Racer drive so much ?
I don't mean to drive that
way because I want to.
I have to drive
to help the shop.
Don't lie to me.
How can you learn such great technique if you drive unwillingly ?
That's not it.
You don't understand.
You're the one who
doesn't understand !
How could someone who
hates driving master drift ?
Only those who like to drive can master that kind of technique.
You might not
have noticed...
...but you like to
drive in your heart.
Listen, if you like to drive a car, that's enough to be called a Road Racer.
If you're a Road Racer, you should have pride in the techniques you've learned.
If someone challenges you,
you accept it.
That's the pride
of a Road Racer.
I'm disappointed
I came to see you.
I hadn't realized...
...that I like
to drive a car ?
But that doesn't mean I ``must'' accept someone's challenge.
I just don't get it.
Hey, Itsuki,
where's Takumi ?
He's on late
shift today.
I see.
Iketani.
I'll go to Mt. Akina tonight and apologize to Nakazato of the Night Kids.
Itsuki...
If I beg him, and explain what happened, he might understand.
Originally, it had nothing
to do with the Speedstars.
I wonder if there's
a way to convince Takumi.
I don't think it's possible.
I know him too well.
He really hates it when someone tries to force or order him around.
He looks quiet, but once he makes up his mind, he gets stubborn and won't change it.
That part of his personality
is identical to his father's.
He doesn't like the idea of accepting someone's challenge automatically.
That's why he's resisting.
If we force him,
he'll get mad.
When he was a sophomore, he got pissed, and beat up a senior in the soccer club.
Takumi did ?
Manager, I'm finished outside.
Good work.
Well then,
I'm heading home.
Takumi.
Sit down over here
for a sec.
I heard a rumor that you're
going to race a 32 tonight.
Well, I...
You'd better not, because
that's a tough opponent.
Well, about that...
Don't say anything.
I understand without
you telling me.
I know all about it.
I know that you didn't
accept the battle.
Itsuki accepted it without
asking, didn't he ?
Yeah.
But you're too nice.
You don't have to save
face for your friend.
I'm telling you. You'd better stay away from the 32.
You don't know
much about cars...
...so you don't know what kind
of car the 32 is, do you ?
Is a 32
that good ?
Good, he took the bait.
It's far
better than good.
It's totally overwhelming.
It's got a drive train that combines the advantages of both FR and 4WD.
It's so unfair.
The GT-R is totally different from the Eight-Six.
Maybe if the
driver wasn't good...
But your opponent is a
famous Road Racer, isn't he ?
It's different
from what Dad said.
He said it would
be a close match.
Hey...
Are you listening ?
You got famous by defeating
the team from Akagi.
You should keep it.
It's not wise to race against someone you have no chance of beating.
Right, Takumi ?
The opponent is a 32, so even if you don't race, no one will think you ran away.
Run away ?!
Manager...
...thanks for
your advice.
I don't think it's important to gain fame as a Road Racer at all.
So you're not
gonna quit.
I won't.
Having heard how
good it is...
...I want to see how
good it is myself.
I'm not afraid
of the 32.
Excuse me.
His reaction is surprisingly similar to his father's.
Temporarily closed due
to private reasons.
Fujiwara Tofu Shop
Temporarily closed ?
I hadn't heard anything.
We're poor, so he
should be working.
Damn, the car.
If he's gone out drinking,
it's hopeless.
That shitty old man won't
come home until morning.
If I don't have a car,
I can't go anywhere.
I should've asked
him this morning.
The galleries
are really packed.
There are more people this time than there were during the race against the Akagi team.
What did they
come to see ?
I'll bet it's
not the 32.
Of course, it's the drift
of the Eight-Six.
He keeps the gas pedal open one corner after another, and they say he's so fast.
I can't wait
to see it.
Oh, I see.
If he shows up, could you
tell him to call home ?
Thank you.
It's no use.
I can't find him.
Shit.
You stupid old man !
Bring back the Eight-Six !
My pride says "You gotta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make room.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
`Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin' my dream.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safety zone.
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change, even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
:Di-ding dang, another round, never slow down.
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down to the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logic...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
Itsuki spoke too freely, and accepted this battle.
The 32 or the Eight-Six, which one do you think will win, Kenji ?
Of course, I say
the Eight-Six...
...but it's impossible, even if it's Takumi, because the GT-R's the fastest car in Japan.
Besides, we don't know
if Takumi will arrive.
If not, once again,
you might have to...
Don't say that !
Next time on Initial D,
``Just Before the Time Attack.''
Takumi, please come !
Get here quickly !
Initial
Next Time:
Just Before the Time Attack!
Don't miss it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org