Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai{Information spread out in a matter of second.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai{but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love"...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
Show yourself,
ghost of Akina.
The Battle Begins!
How's the
booster pressure ?
It's okay.
Don't forget to check
the tire pressure.
Okay.
We'll win today's race.
It's a piece of cake.
Shut up and
keep on working.
Geez...
Hey, hand me
that cross wrench.
What're they doing ?
Changing the
tires of the FD.
They seem to have
a few sets in the van.
Changing the tires according
to the situation ?
They're serious.
Dammit.
It's ready anytime, Keisuke.
Arigato.
Hey, isn't
it 10:00 yet ?
It's still 9:40.
Shit.
Brother, that Eight-Six
hasn't showed up yet.
I'm getting pissed.
I was sure it
would represent Akina.
My prediction was wrong.
It's such a turn off.
Unless I humiliate them by winning the time attack by a big margin...
...I can't ease my anger.
Iketani, it's almost time.
Yeah, I know.
Who's that ?
Senpai !
Iketani !
Itsuki...
W...what about
the time attack ?
It's about to start.
Great, I made
it in time.
Who's gonna run
for the Speedstars ?
Kenji, you'd better
prepare yourself.
You're representing the team ?
Good luck,
I'm with you !
This is the starting point.
Are you ready ?
This is the finish.
Everyone's in position.
We can begin any time.
Okay.
You heard that.
Shall we begin ?
So he didn't
come after all.
I'm counting on you, Kenji.
Okay...
Gimme a break.
How can you be my opponent ?
Kenji, you don't look good.
You're sweating a lot.
It's painful looking at you.
Even if you say so...
Guts !~~Put your
guts into it !
Alright, let's begin
the countdown.
Ten seconds...
Hold a second !
This is the finish line !
A car just passed by.
It could interfere.
Should we wait until
it reaches the peak ?
This is a public street.  There might as well be oncoming traffic.
Don't worry,
let's begin !
Okay.
Wait.~~Can you ask him what kind of car it was ?
Can you tell what
kind of car it was ?
Let me see...
It's got retractable lights.
It's probably an
Eight-Six Trueno.
Give it to me.
What color was
that Eight-Six ?
Why're you asking
me such things ?
White and black.
A panda Trueno.
He's here.
Here comes my target.
What do I do ?
Continue counting down ?
Stop counting down, and wait until the Eight-Six arrives.
The One-Eighty beside me
isn't my true opponent.
Right ?
Yeah, you're right.
Kenji, you can relax.
I'm saved.
Your eyes are watery.
Same as yours.
That old man has come to save the pride of Akina's Road Racers.
That's more than enough.
It doesn't matter
if we win or lose.
What the hell...?
I feel awkward.
People are standing
at every corner.
What're they doing ?
I've come to
a strange place.
What the heck...
...if I win, the tank will be full, and I can go to the beach without hesitation.
What's wrong, Takeshi ?
He's good.
The rear of the car, just leaving the corner, looked very steady.
Didn't you see ?
Even if you say so...
It looked like any
other ordinary Eight-Six.
Cars driven by those who can control their car like their hands and legs give off auras.
A strong aura surrounds
Takahashi Ryosuke's driving.
It's still weak for
his brother, Keisuke.
But that Eight-Six
had a strong aura.
If he's representing Akina, we can't predict which one's gonna win.
Almost.
He's really here.
The fastest on
Akina's downhill.
A legendary
super technician.
We can show the Takahashi brothers the true potential of Akina.
Come on, Eight-Six.
I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of driver he is.
I haven't felt such
anticipation in a long time.
He put things off
till the last minute.
But that trick
won't work on me.
Let me watch carefully.
There it is !
Clear the street !
Guide it to the starting line !
What's that car for ?
They were waiting
for that car ?
But that's only
an Eight-Six.
Shit.~~Where did all
these people come from ?
Fujiwara Tofu Shop (Private Vehicle)
Excuse me...
Could that
Eight-Six be...?
Takumi...
T...that's...
So he's the one.
Takumi !
What's going on ?
What happened to your father ?
I came here because
Dad told me to.
Even if the car's here, it won't do anything unless your father is, too !
What should we do, Iketani ?
This wasn't supposed
to happen.
I shouldn't have
come after all.
That shitty old man
pisses me off.
Takumi, didn't your father say anything besides that ?
Dad only told me to go to the mountain peak and defeat the FD on Akina's downhill.
Your father told
you to drive ?
Yeah.
Can you defeat...
...Takahashi Keisuke ?
I won't know unless I try...
...but I defeated
him once.
Defeated him once...?
He'll give me a full
tank of gas if I win.
So, if you let me try,
I'll win, no matter what.
Excuse me...
Umm, excuse me, excuse me.
Takumi, you
complete moron !
Ouch !
What's wrong with you ?
Takumi, how can you
be so stupid ?
I'm so embarrassed
just looking at you !
Just move the car, and don't interfere with the time attack !
Get in the Eight-Six...
Hold on a sec, Itsuki.
Iketani, I'm very sorry !
He's so dumb, and he
doesn't know anything !
Please forgive him !
Takumi, your father isn't the only one delivering tofu, right ?
You do too, don't you ?
For the past five years,
I've been the only one.
For the past
five years ?
I finally get it, Takumi.
Okay, you'll drive the time attack on the downhill.
W...what're you
saying, Iketani ?
If an amateur like Takumi pushes too hard on Akina's downhill...
...he'll lose control
and die instantly !
Don't worry, just go
to the corner and watch.
I'm glad you're here, Takumi.
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
Sorry to keep
you waiting.
Dammit, I'm tired
of waiting.
He's so young.
Your name ?
Fujiwara Takumi.
I'll remember that.
I'm Takahashi Keisuke.
I won't make the
same mistake twice.
Is it alright ?
A race between an Eight-Six
and an FD is so unfair.
Its power is totally outclassed, and the FD is Japan's best cornering machine.
The Eight-Six is no match for it on the straightaways or corners.
All I can
do is believe.
I'm starting the
countdown.
Okay.
Ten seconds to start !
Nine...
...eight...
...seven...
...six...
...five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one...
Go !
Takahashi Keisuke's
FD is so fast !
350 horsepower isn't just for show, and his clutch meet was perfect.
This won't be a race.
The full acceleration of the Eight-Six almost looked like it wasn't moving.
Takumi...
Judging from the start dash, that Eight-Six has 150 horsepower at most.
It's far from the
monster Keisuke says it is.
The reason why the
shift timing is quick...
...is because it has a close transmission, just like a rally car.
That suits Akina's tight
hairpin curves perfectly.
Even so, I can't find any factor for that Eight-Six to defeat Keisuke's FD.
The monster
isn't the car.
Could it be
the driver ?
I won't hold back.
It's not my style to go full out on the straightaway, but this is a time attack...
I won't see the Eight-Six
in my rear view mirror again.
What the hell...?
This is the
first corner !
That Eight-Six took
an incredible line !
It was 5 cm from
the guardrail !
I've never seen any
car that turns so fast !
What ?!
He's gaining on me.
His car is
getting closer.
No, it's not.
Something so
absurd can't happen.
A...are you serious ?
Takumi's father is
a great Road Racer ?
Yeah.
I've seen him
a few times.
He looked like an
ordinary tofu shop guy.
You can't judge a
person by appearances.
The manager told me that he's still the fastest on Akina's downhill.
Anyway, that old man sent Takumi here instead...
...so we have
to believe in him.
Yeah, it's much better
than me driving.
But no matter how fast his dad is, if it's Takumi...
Actually, it seems that Takumi has defeated Takahashi Keisuke once.
Takumi has defeated
Takahashi Keisuke ?!
You must be kidding !
I can't believe it.
That stupid Takumi
actually did ?
He didn't even know
what Eight-Six meant.
W...what's going on
with that Eight-Six ?!
It entered the corner at incredible speed while skidding the rear...
...and exited at
very high speed !
I don't know if it lost control !
It's just so exciting to watch !
He caught me !
What's going on ?
It's driving me crazy !
Shit !
Initial acceleration in second gear is almost the same, but he can stretch it longer.
The gap widens
on the straightaway.
This is from the straightaway in front of the skating rink !~~They've just passed us !
Keisuke is being pushed.
Akina's Eight-Six
is damned fast.
Holy shit !
I've never seen anyone charging on Keisuke's FD so close !
I'm getting
goose bumps.
He's pulled away on the
long straightaway again...
...but the hairpins are coming up,
so he might be in trouble.
Did you hear, Ryosuke ?
We've made
a misjudgement.
We didn't expect Akina to
have such a skilled driver.
Incredible entry !
It was an entry
oriented kamikaze drive !
He lacks any fear
of the downhill !
I'm faster on the straightaway,
but he's still charging in.
He's better at
cornering work.
It's a Road Racer's worst disgrace to be tailed by an underpowered car.
I won't accept
that, no matter what !
That shitty old man won't call it a win unless I overtake that car.
It can't be helped, because the prize is a full tank of gas.
The attack point is the
five hairpin curves ahead.
My pride says "You gatta be wild and tough."
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make a room.
************************
Timing:
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Timing:
Tizya
Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin my dream.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Addition Timing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
************************
Timing:
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Addition Timing:
Tizya
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safe zone.
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
************************
Guys:
Hajime Hosoi
Shogo Sakamoto
Naoki Imamura
Masato Amano
Jun Suzuki
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down on the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logics...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
Tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
Finally, the race
has begun, Takumi !
Yeah.
Did you practice
for this battle ?
Not really.
It's just like
delivering tofu.
So your daily work is effective.
That's about right.
Do you have any secret
plan to overtake the FD ?
It's not really
a secret, but...
You have to win to use the Eight-Six with a full tank of gas to date Natsuki, don't you ?
Initial
Next Time:
End of the Dogfight!
Yeah.
Next time on Initial D...
...something's gonna happen
in the five hairpins.
Don't miss it !
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org