Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
INITIAL
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shita kemuri
Silver smoke in a freezing city...
misugita yume no daisyou
...that's the cost of having an unachievable dream.
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi
A frozen body and unforgettable desire...
accel funde gomakasu
You deceive yourself by stepping on the accelerator.
Yoru ni kowareta mama shisen tsuyoku togarasete
Although depressed in the night, your eyes are kept sharply open.
Dareno kimagure kara sekai sae mo owarisoude
You feel like someone's careless act could end the world.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Obieta me wo shite lost in the night
Lost in the night with frightened eyes...
ochiteku yume ni dakareru
Embraced by a ruined dream.
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart
Scared of loneliness, I'm missing you in my heart.
jibun sae mo kizu tsukete
I almost hurt myself.
Taoreru kurai ni love me so much
Love me so much and knock me out.
subete wo suttee anata wo
If only I can give up everything...
Ai suru koto sae dekitara
...and love you...
kitto sunao ni naresou
...I can be my true self.
Takumi, this is for you.
Who from ?
From Takahashi Ryosuke.
Takahashi...
...Ryosuke.
He's fast.
Although he lowered his power,
his exit speed is definitely faster.
He won't lose.
No way he will.
``Battle ?''
Are you going
to fight someone ?
No.~~We just call a
car race a ``battle.''
If you don't like it,
why don't you ignore him ?
It's not that
I don't like it.
I'm not going to run away, although I don't know if I can win.
Do you still think
Takumi will lose ?
Yes.
Even if Takumi's a genius,
he's only a high school kid.
I wonder how long he can keep up with Takahashi Ryosuke.
I only have one reason for thinking that he might be able to win.
Takumi is Bunta's son.
That crazy Bunta.
Keisuke, I've been thinking about this for a while.
If I lose
on the street...
...I'll retire.
Now that I've said that, I can say that I've met two drivers who might defeat me.
One of them
is you, Keisuke.
Me ?
And the other is...
Last Great Battle
Cute.
Takumi !
Good luck, Takumi.
I believe you'll win...
...so outrun Takahashi Ryosuke and become the greatest star in Gunma !
Takumi...
Itsuki, he understands,
so leave him alone.
You're late.
It's just before 10 o'clock.
You're as laidback as usual.
I've been waiting for you.
I don't know how someone as young as you learned all these techniques...
...but you impress me.
I've driven Akina's mountain passes more than anyone else, so I'm familiar with them.
I don't use any
special techniques.
You must've misunderstood,
and think too highly of me.
That's interesting.
I guess you don't know
much about yourself.
You're interesting.
I want to spend more time talking to you someday.
Brother...
Let's get started.
It's gonna be
a fun night.
Alright, move your cars !
Okay !
The Redsuns'll manage the race again.  Is that alright ?
Yeah.
Please assign some people from the Speedstars as officials.
Okay.
Iketani, I'll be
at the finish.
We're counting on you.
Keisuke, I'll be at the
five sequential hairpins.
Ryosuke will win, right ?
We'll have our
revenge, won't we ?
Of course.
No matter how fast he is,
my brother won't lose.
I think so, too.
Well, I'm going !
Hello, this is
Fujiwara Tofu...
Oh, it's you.
Bunta, I just got to Akina.
The galleries are packed.
You'd be surprised.
So ?
Do you think
Takumi'll win ?
His opponent is the street king, the fastest in Gunma.
I don't know.
If you don't have anything
else to say, I'm hanging up.
B...Bunta.
Bunta, wait !
Don't hang up on me !
Alright.~~Report on
each corner's condition.
Okay.~~This is
the first corner.
We're ready.
This is from the skating rink.
The straightaway is clear.
This is the No. 17 hairpin.
We're ready.
This is the five
sequential hairpins.
There's no traffic.
We're ready.
This is No. 6.  We're moving the gallery's cars, but it'll be ready.
The tension's so high,
and my throat's dry !
My heart's pounding !
The entire mountain pass
is filled with tension.
Yeah.
I wonder if
Takumi'll be alright.
Takumi, your opponent is one of the best Road Racers.
It's alright to lose,
but drive your best.
Takumi, good luck !
I believe
that you'll win !
There's no way
my brother'll lose.
But when the Eight-Six races,
unexpected things happen on Mt. Akina.
Excuse me, but what
about the battle ?
It hasn't started yet.
Oh, I see.
Thank you.
This is the starting point.
How's the finish line ?
Yes, it's ready.
Begin any time.
Okay, let's start.
Wait !
Let me count it down.
I want to do it for
this particular race.
All right ?
I won't let anybody else do it for the race between my brother and the Eight-Six.
I'm gonna count down !
Five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one.
Go !
Go, Takumi !
Good, good !
The start was even !
Oh, Takumi's taken the lead !
Takumi, go for it !
That's my brother's style.
For an important race...
...he lets his opponent go ahead and then passes him at the critical point.
He's won that way before, and there's no error in his logic for the fastest driving.
Both are incredible !
What a tight twin drift !
Takahashi Ryosuke usually doesn't use drift that hard !
Both are showing
off from the start !
It's drift versus drift !
Even Takahashi Ryosuke is using drift from the very start.
He must be trying to win
with Takumi's specialty.
To keep his status
as the street king.
Takumi's doing great, it's
gonna be a great battle !
Takumi, please win,
no matter what !
Right, Iketani ?!
Yeah, right.
I'm surprised.
The Eight-Six's motion is totally
different from before.
As I thought,
he's improved.
He doesn't countersteer at the end of his drift like before, but...
...the angle of the countersteer right after the turn-in is smaller.
I don't understand. How did
he eliminate that weakness ?
He hasn't raced very many times, but he's improved, one race after another.
I'll have to
change my simulation.
But that's all, and the
result will be the same.
My theory for the fastest
driving is correct.
Let me make
this clear, Takeshi.
I didn't park here
because I saw your car.
So don't get
the wrong idea.
I decided to come here
beforehand, so get lost.
No.
I decided to watch
the race from here.
Why don't YOU get lost ?
Well, the amateurs in the galleries chose famous places...
...like the five
sequential hairpins.
Right, but they can't
settle the match there.
This is the only place
they can make a go at it.
You thought so, too ?
I have to say it's just
what I'd expect from you.
Same to you.
Besides, there's only
us two around here.
Those who don't know us might think that we're close friends.
Disgusting.
Here they come.
Both cars are so close
to the guardrail !
Incredible.
It's so shocking.
No time to waste.
I'd better call him !
What a pain...
This is Fujiwara...
Hey, Bunta,
can you hear me ?!
Not you again...
Hey, listen.
They just passed
in front of me.
Both cars passed by while
drifting really hard.
Takumi's Eight-Six
has taken the lead...
...and the FC is
right on his tail.
Takumi's in front ?
That's bad.
Bad ?
Why ?
Think about it, Yuichi.
The chaser has an advantage over the one who's driving in front.
It's just common sense.
He's right.
The one chasing can closely watch the line and rhythm taken by his opponent.
Those who're skilled enough can copy that easily.
But if he
can pull away...
The one driving in front
feels a lot of pressure.
If your opponent follows you at the same speed, you feel mentally cornered.
If you can't pull away while you're driving your best...
...you start wondering if the opponent's far more skilled than expected.
Especially since Takumi has no experience in managing the pace.
He must be
scared by now.
He is ?
I'll call you
once it's over.
Will he lose...?
Nah.
They're coming !
My god !
I can't believe it !
This is corner number 24 !
The Eight-Six and Ryosuke's
FC have just passed by.
And I got the split time,
and it's incredible.
If they keep this pace...
...they'll shorten the Eight-Six's
last course record by 7 or 8 seconds.
They're gonna be faster than our race by 7 or 8 seconds ?!
Gimme a break.
So this is what my brother meant by driving his best.
It's almost scary.
Tonight's battle
will become legendary.
Takumi's still in front.
Alright.
He'll do it, Senpai.
Yeah, but I wonder how
long he can hold on.
His opponent is
Takahashi Ryosuke.
If Takumi finishes the race safely, I'll be satisfied.
He's staying right on my tail even though I'm driving at full throttle.
I can't shake him, no
matter how fast I drive.
It's no good,
I might lose this battle.
Takahashi Ryosuke...
...he's not a driver someone
like me can defeat.
I don't want to lose...
...but I'm losing.
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
Kagayaku mirai e
...into the bright future.
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Let's make it sure over and over.
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
This passion will be eternal.
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku dakishimete
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
Kiseki no hana yo
The flower of miracles.
I think Takumi'll win, as I expected.
I don't want to lose...
I don't want to lose this race.
Hello, this is Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Wha ? Ganmo and Atsuage...?
Takumi'll win this race.
Takumi, go, keep up.
So many opinions are crossing over, but the race'll be settled.
Next time on Initial D,
the last episode:
Initial
Next Time:
New Downhill Legend !
Don't miss it !
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org