Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
INITIAL
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves a lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
That was dangerous !
How dare you
drive like that !
Hey, you...
Hang on !
Are you alright ?
Sorry about my
carelessness.
I'm sorry...really...
Hey, hold on, I'll
call an ambulance !
Downhill Specialist Arrives
What ?!
Iketani had an accident ?!
When ?!
Last night he hit the guardrail driving the downhill on Akina.
How is he ?
Thank you very much.
His injury isn't too serious.
Just minor whiplash.
But he's really
torn up about it.
His car was heavily
damaged, too.
Then what about
the race on Saturday ?
It's hopeless...
Anyway, we have to find a
substitute for Iketani somehow.
Welcome...
Oh, Iketani...
Is it alright to
be walking around ?
Yeah, it's okay.
Where's my car ?
In the back garage.
Nothing's been done yet.
We can't start until
we get all the parts.
Excuse me.
I want fried tofu.
Coming.
Thanks...
You had an accident ?
Yeah...
There isn't much
time till the race.
What're you
going to do ?
I came to ask you a favor
about that, Mr. Fujiwara.
Favor ?
Yes.
Can you drive in the race instead of me the day after tomorrow ?
I beg you, Mr. Fujiwara.
My neck...
Don't die.
You can understand how
a Road Racer feels, right ?
The local drivers
can't be defeated !
Hey, even if I do, I'd just be an old man in the wrong place.
I grew up driving Akina...
...so I can tell that those Redsuns guys are looking down on all of Akina's Road Racers.
That's why I'm
so frustrated !
I want to show them there's a skilled Road Racer on Akina.
Mr. Fujiwara, you can
do that because...
...you've defeated Takahashi,
the fastest of Akagi, once already.
Please, Mr. Fujiwara !
What is it ?
We're closed for today.
Don't be so rigid.
Fill it up with high octane.
How cheeky...
High octane for the
Eight-Six, you said ?
It was you who told Iketani
that ridiculous rumor.
Yeah, I didn't mean
to tell a lie.
So, what about it...?
He came over today with
bandages and neck brace on.
He asked me to drive
instead of him.
I can't hate that
kind of guy, though.
If you don't, then
why not drive instead ?
Iketani's a nice guy.
Forget it.
It's like an adult poking
his nose in a kids' fight.
That's not my style.
Then why don't you send
a kid to a kids' fight ?
Are you talking
about Takumi ?
Yeah.
He's really good,
isn't he ?
Not yet...
...but if it's Akina's downhill,
he's good enough not to lose to anyone.
Well, he can't
defeat me, though.
Here comes your
fighting instinct.
I wonder what made
him so stubborn.
Even if he's asked, he's not the kind who'll accept so easily and drive...
Well, I'll come up with a plan for the sake of the bandaged Iketani.
Don't break your promise.
I hate people who smoke
and break promises.
Let me use the
car on Sunday, okay ?
Sunday...?
You can't.
Why not ?
I'll do the delivery
in the morning as usual.
That's not it.
I have a meeting of the Society of Commerce on Sunday, so I need it.
Really ?
This is bad.
I really need the
car this Sunday.
It must be a girl.
None of your business.
Don't be so stubborn,
and let me use it...
...because the car isn't
that great for your use.
I'll go without
asking, okay ?
The car won't
run without a key.
I'll put it on a string
and wear it around my neck.
That's mean.
If you're so desperate,
I can consider it.
Really ?
But I have
one condition.
Condition ?
Saturday night, beat the pants off a smartass kid who claims to be the fastest on Akagi...
...on Akina's downhill.
H...how come ?
Then I'll let
you use the car.
Plus, you get a
full tank of gas.
Full tank of gas...
That's so irresistible...
...'cause I'm
almost broke.
What're you going to do ?
L...let me think about
it for a while.
Fine, think as
much as you want.
Takahashi
I'm coming in.
Oh, Keisuke,
good timing.
I wanted to ask
you something.
What is it, Brother ?
It's about the Eight-Six
you saw on Akina.
Can you logically explain
why it was so fast ?
Oh, gimme a break.
I'm not good at that kind
of thing like you are.
Like I always say, the most important thing in driving technique is ``this.''
You can figure out anything
by driving behind your opponent.
From the opponent's habits and weaknesses, to how well the suspension is set up.
Your analysis skill is
almost monstrous.
To me, you're incredible because you can keep up with me without thinking.
If you can apply theories to your driving skill, it's ideal.
I was defeated the other day because of unfamiliarity and carelessness.
I've never had such
a disgrace before.
The inside of that Eight-Six
must be monstrous.
Monstrous, huh ?
I'm getting interested.
Maybe I should watch
the race tomorrow.
Takumi !
Saturday has
finally come !
So what ?
What do you mean,
``So what ?''
The race !
The race against
the Akagi Redsuns !
You promised me you'd borrow the Eight-Six and we'd go see it together.
Oh, speaking of which...
Things are getting
complicated.
What is it ?
Don't even say
that you can't go.
Well, it's not that, but...
If you cancel, I won't be seeing you anymore, no matter what the reason is.
I've kept counting the
days to go until today.
I know.
Excuse me.
I want fried tofu.
Oh, you again.
You're so persistent.
Mr. Fujiwara, please come
to the race today.
I might be
able to go.
I said, I might be able to go to tonight's race on Mt. Akina.
Really ?!
My neck...
Hey, are you alright ?
Are you really coming ?
I can't say
it's definite...
...but the chance
is fifty-fifty.
When's it gonna start ?
The friendship rally
begins at 9:00...
...and the time attack
begins at 10:00.
Ten o'clock...
If the Eight-Six doesn't
appear by ten, give up on me.
Then you'll have to
do something yourself.
I'll be waiting,
Mr. Fujiwara.
I believe that
you'll definitely come.
I'm not sure.
I said fifty percent.
No, you've already
decided to come.
I'll be waiting for you,
along with all the team members.
Well then, Mr. Fujiwara, I'll be waiting at Akina's peak at 10:00.
I can't help myself when it comes to an eager guy like him.
If Takumi refuses,
should I drive myself ?
Boy, I'm getting excited.
Something good happened ?
You're acting a little
different than usual.
Am I ?
I'm always like this.
You look happy
for some reason.
Actually, I'm going to the beach with my friend tomorrow.
I'm really looking
forward to it.
Friend, you mean a guy ?
No, it's a
girl of course.
If that's what it is, I can buy you a new bathing suit at the department store.
It's alright.
I bought myself one already.
I don't need two.
I want to see you
in the bathing suit.
That's strange.
You've seen
everything.
You're a pervert.
I wonder if it'll
be sunny tomorrow.
Don't ask such
a dumb question.
It'll be sunny all
over the country.
Are you going somewhere ?
I'm going
to the beach.
Beach ?
Say what ?!
I'm so envious !
I wanna go to the beach, too !
Don't tell me...
...you're going with a girl !
Is a girl going with you ?!
Yeah.
Who is it ?!
Do I know her ?!
Is she cute ?!
Does she have big boobs ?!
Really cute.
Mogi Natsuki...?
Yeah.
You're so cruel,
going ahead of me.
Sorry, but the situation didn't give me a chance to ask.
Some other time, okay ?
Don't cry.
What's gonna happen
during the race today ?
I heard that the Redsuns have won every race they've challenged.
The outcome is
so obvious.
The Akina team will
be totally nailed.
But the fastest in
Gunma aren't the Redsuns...
...but us, the
Night Kids of Myogi.
Takeshi, it's about time.
Alright, let's go.
The R32 is a pure thoroughbred,
born to run fast.
It'll never be defeated by the rotary potatoes of Akagi.
Incredible.
There's gonna be a little
party on the mountain.
The story about the race
between Iketani's team...
...and the fastest team on Akagi,
has been talked about everywhere.
I wonder which
side's gonna win.
Well, Takumi's Eight-Six is Bunta's car as well...
...so it won't
be defeated.
I'm getting excited
after such a long time.
There're so many people !
I've never seen such big
galleries on Akina before.
The Redsuns drew them here
to show off their speed.
It'll be so disgraceful
if we lose.
By the way, about the Eight-Six you talked about earlier...
Is that really true, Iketani ?
Yeah.
It's so hard for me
to believe in that Eight-Six.
I heard that Takahashi's FD3S~~is moderately tuned for the mountain path.
Still, they say it
produces at least 350 HP.
It's got so much power.
Even if it's downhill, the
Eight-Six will be no match for it !
Iketani, did you get hit
somewhere really bad ?
Even if it's the Eight-Six,
it's not a normal Eight-Six.
Takahashi Keisuke himself said that it looked like a normal panda Trueno...
...but it's a monster
machine under the skin.
Trust me.
He'll come for us.
If he doesn't...?
The galleries
are so big...
...and I don't want them to say the Speedstars ran away...
In that case...
Kenji, for the sake of the team, you drive like hell to win !
Y...you must be kidding...
Many cars are coming up.
I hear the rotary
sound also.
The Redsuns !
There they are !
They've finally arrived.
The Takahashi brothers are
incredibly popular.
They're the sons of a doctor who runs a big clinic in Takasaki.
We can't compete
with the rich.
Driving skill depends on how much gas and tires are wasted.
What the hell
is Takumi doing ?
The race is gonna begin !
Even though I made sure,
that stupid Takumi...!
Idiot, jerk !
You're not my friend !
Ouch !
I won't be able to make it in time.
I'd better go on my scooter.
Let's start the time
attack at 10:00 as planned.
If it's late, there'll be no other traffic, making it easier.
We'll use radios at the start and finish to time them.
We'll put officials at the blind corners, so the drivers can go as fast as they want.
If there's oncoming traffic, we'll
use lights to signal the drivers.
I see.
They seem so experienced.
Yeah, I guess they do time attacks in many places.
Well then, it's gonna be a free run till 10:00, so let's have fun.
The galleries
are packed.
The Eight-Six isn't here.
What's going on ?
Are they going to hide their secret weapon until the last moment ?
It's the bottom of the ninth, one out,
with the bases loaded.
What is it ?
Have you decided to go ?
I don't feel
like it though...
Why not ?~~Don't you have the confidence to win ?
If you drive like you
always do, you won't lose.
There it is !
It's Keisuke's FD3S~~!
Incredible !
The entry speed was so fast !
That's Takahashi
Ryosuke this time !
Watch out !
Move !
Just like Takahashi Ryosuke.
His skill is the real thing.
Incredible !~~They don't
hit at that distance ?
That's the famous
parallel drift !
It's a difficult
one to approach.
It can't be done without the skill to control your speed and line during a drift.
But that's only
a performance.
They drive differently
when they race.
The ghost of Akina
hasn't arrived.
You're my only opponent.
Come out, Eight-Six !
Aren't you giving
me a paper cup ?
You don't need one, because you're not carrying tofu.
It's not for a
delivery, so have fun.
Full tank of gas.
Don't forget.
I know.
I'm going then.
Okay.
My pride says "You gotta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Information byousoku
Bunta: Unshou Ishizuka
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Natsuki: Ayako Kawasumi
Yuichi: omomichi Nishimura
Iketani: azuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru  Takagi
Papa: Tohru Furusawa
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Information byousoku
Bunta: Unshou Ishizuka
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Natsuki: Ayako Kawasumi
Yuichi: omomichi Nishimura
Iketani: azuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru  Takagi
Papa: Tohru Furusawa
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Ryosuke: Koyasu Takehito
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
~~ Hajime Hosoi
Jun Suzuki
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Yumi Kakazu
Makiko Miyagi
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Ryosuke: Koyasu Takehito
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
~~ Hajime Hosoi
Jun Suzuki
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Yumi Kakazu
Makiko Miyagi
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make room.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Timing:
Tizya
`Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin' my dream.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Timing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Timing:
Tizya
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safety zone.
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change, even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang, another round, never slow down.
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down to the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logic...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
Today's guest is famous for aggressive driving, from the Redsuns, Takahashi...
Give that to me !
Show yourself,
ghost of Akina !
Don't tell me you're
scared and ran away ?!
Do you think you
can win this time ?
Shut up !
There's no doubt !
I'll get revenge
no matter what !
Next time on Initial D,
finally, ``The Battle Begins.''
Which will win in the high tension battle between the Eight-Six and FD ?
Initial
Next Time:
The Battle Begins!
Don't miss it !
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org