Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information spread out in a matter of second.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love"...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
I made it.
FR Killing Death Match !
That sonuvabitch hit
me on purpose !
I won't let
you get away !
Akina's potato is
keeping up with me ?
That little...
Don't screw
around with me.
His turn-in is
unbelievably fast.
Brake lights...?
His brake lights are on
during high speed cornering !
Damn, I can't
keep up with him.
He's got
incredible technique.
The turn-in of that EG6 might
be faster than Takumi's.
Who the hell is he ?
Thank you very much.
And he really
pissed me off.
Braking while cornering ?
And at high speed ?
Yes.
I've never seen anything
like it before.
Really ?
It happens often.
I brake in
corners so often.
Oh shit,
I'm too fast.
I'm scared, tap, tap.
We aren't having such
a low level conversation.
That EG6 cleared the corner
at a very high speed.
EG6 ?
It's the Civic.
A Civic.
Then why don't you
simply say Civic ?
Although the Civic is FF,
it's popular among Road Racers.
It's got a 1.6 liter, non-turbo engine like the Eight-Six...
...but it's very powerful thanks to its VTEC engine.
Civics and Levin/Truenos have
been rivals for a long time.
You can't neglect the Civic because you're driving an Eight-Six.
I can't yield to the Civic
because I drive the Levin !
Anyway, I can't believe how he braked after a high speed entry into a corner.
He's using a left
foot braking technique.
Left foot braking ?
You don't use that technique
with FR cars very often.
But you can use your left foot for braking for sensitive control at the limit.
FF cars like the EG6 experience understeering when you step on the gas pedal.
They use left foot braking while depressing the gas pedal...
...to lessen the rear load to stay on the ideal path.
It's an advanced technique.
If he used that, he must be
a really good FF driver.
He must be very fast.
He's fast,
but that sonuva...
I managed to avoid an accident because
I practiced spinning using the parking brake.
My S13 could've been
``hospitalized'' again.
He won't get away the
next time I see that EG6.
I'm home.
Hey.
Oh, you had a phone
call a while ago.
From who ?
I don't know.
It was a girl.
She was cute.
She said she'd call back.
How do you know if she's cute or not by talking on the phone ?
Being a man for a long time,
my instincts can tell.
Experience counts in
both women and cars.
Well, good luck.
Shut up.
I'd better go
to the meeting.
Hello, this is
Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Hello, Takumi...?
Mogi...?
Sorry.
Were you sleeping ?
It's about our plans...
Hey, this had better
not be a joke, Takumi.
If it turns out to be,
it'll end our friendship !
So she's coming
with another girl.
It'll be alright.
Mogi definitely said
she'd bring her friend.
I wonder if
she'll be cute ?
Nice body or maybe
incredibly beautiful ?!
Well, well ?!
I don't know.
She's Mogi's junior high friend.
Actually, I'm not so
picky about her looks.
If I keep my hopes too high,
I might be disappointed.
So you kept your
promise, Takumi !
I'm so happy to have
a good friend like you !
You're overreacting.
Just watch.
With a girl by my side,
I'll be the fastest on Akina !
How dare you !
Shit !
My Levin, my...!
They should be
here by now.
Takumi, did you wait long ?
Mogi, don't surprise
me like that.
I'll introduce you.
This is friend Saori.
This is Takumi
and Itsuki.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
Cute babe.
So you're
a Road Racer ?
Yeah.
I'm on the team called
the Akina Speedstars...
...and I'm number
three or four.
Well, Akina's Levin is
well known in Gunma.
How cool.
What's a Road Racer ?
Oh, come on.
Don't you know, Natsuki ?
Road Racers are...
Way to go, Saori.
She's better than I hoped for.
Hey, Itsuki, watch out !
Should I drive ?
No, it's okay.
Sorry about that.
It's a bad Road Racer habit.
How do you feel ?
I'm fine now.
His driving is so rough.
Hey, Takumi and Natsuki !
This is great !
Why don't you
guys take a ride ?
They're getting
along well.
You know, I could
take you guys home.
Oh, it's okay.
We haven't seen each other for a while, so we want to talk more.
Itsuki, thank you.
It was fun.
See you again.
See ya.
S...Saori...
Saori, see you again !
Great, great, great !
She's the best !
I'm talking about Saori.
I feel so alive !
Saori !
Hey, drive carefully.
Don't worry.
Thank you so much, Takumi.
She said ``again.''
I'll ask her to go driving.
Hey, look ahead.
Sorry, sorry.
Thank you very much !
Alright, is there
anything else to do ?
Work, work...
Itsuki's so excited.
I wonder if he found a girl...
I don't know.
If so, I won't forgive him
for getting ahead of me !
By the way, Takumi...
...do you feel like
driving my S13 ?
It's refreshing to drive a
different car once in a while.
No, thanks.
I'll pass.
Besides, it's your precious...
I'm begging you, Takumi.
I want to learn
from your driving.
Please !
Are you serious about
racing Akina's Eight-Six ?
You'll see.
Well, let's go.
C'mon, Akina's Eight-Six.
I'm looking forward
to seeing you.
Are you sure about this ?
I'm begging you, Takumi.
Just drive normally
and I'll be satisfied.
It'll be very helpful.
Come on,
just this once.
I don't know...
I haven't driven other cars,
so I don't think I can drive it fast.
Iketani's only
asking this much.
Why don't you drive ?
That's right, Takumi !
Give him a
little respect !
Alright then,
just this once.
Don't expect
too much, okay ?
Oh, you will ?
Yahoo !
Lucky you, Iketani.
Don't pass out, okay ?
Don't worry, don't worry.
This is the second time.
Push it hard, Takumi.
Okay, we're going.
Right.
What should I do ?
Well, how about
braking drift ?
Okay.
Hey.
You're gonna do
it right away ?
Aren't we going too fast ?
I wonder if Iketani
will be alright.
Once again...
I hear the echoes of a death cry in the Akina mountains !
The scary downhill...
....where Iketani,
in the third corner...
...p...p...p...passes out !
Will it happen again ?
Incredible.
He's drifting a car he's
driving for the first time.
My S13 is
actually fast.
It's different
from my car...
...but I've got the hang of
how to drive this car.
B...but you only cleared
the third corner...?
Here comes the drift.
Drift...?
Then what was that in
the last three corners ?
I think I turned the
corner as I imagined.
Incredible...
He's so incredible.
I don't know
what's going on.
They're back.
Hey, you're
still conscious.
You've improved a bit.
So, Iketani, did you get
any hints for braking drift ?
Not a one.
I don't know
what happened.
Say what ?
What was the point of asking
Takumi for the favor then ?
Even if you
say so, Kenji...
...Takumi performs incredible
techniques so easily.
I ``learned'' that his level is totally different, and I can't learn from him yet.
That's a big
improvement.
An EG6 !
I'm sure it's the
one from last night.
Sonuva...
Hey, you're the one !
You hit my car from
behind, didn't you ?!
Who are you ?
Don't play innocent !
You remember this
two-tone S13, don't you ?
Oh, that one.
Don't give me
that crap !
Apologize !
You could've caused
a big accident !
Gimme a break.
It was your fault.
Say what ?
You were so slow I couldn't
predict your actions.
I didn't expect you to
enter the corner so slowly.
I couldn't brake in time,
and I touched your tail.
How dare you !
Stop, Iketani !
What an asshole.
Iketani's pride
is torn to pieces.
If you want me to apologize,
we'll race by our rules...
...and if you win, I'll
kneel down to the ground.
By your rules ?
What do you mean ?
It's not so difficult.
We call it a
gumtape death match.
Gumtape death match ?
Just bind your right hand to the steering wheel with gumtape.
That's the only rule.
We race under
those conditions.
Bind the right hand to the
steering wheel with gumtape ?
The left hand is free
for shifting, right ?
The right hand to
the steering wheel...
You can't pass the steering wheel from one hand to another !
You can't steer !
It's too risky !
I don't want
to race you.
Oh, yeah.
I heard that there's a fast Eight-Six downhill driver in the Speedstars.
I don't know who the brat is,
so why don't you send him out ?
Tell the Eight-Six brat that I'll be waiting here at 10:00pm next Saturday.
We'll settle everything with
a gumtape death match.
Catch ya later.
My pride says "You gatta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make a room.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin my dream.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
************************
FF = Front Engine Front Wheel Drive
Gumtape = Duct tape
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safe zone.
************************
FF = Front Engine Front Wheel Drive
Gumtape = Duct tape
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
************************
FF = Front Engine Front Wheel Drive
Gumtape = Duct tape
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down on the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logics...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
Tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
Love fortune:  ``Your relationship will develop further next week.''
Oh, Itsuki,
something good happened ?
Finally, I'll have
a girl friend !
Really ?
Omedetou !
So, who is it ?
The girl we
double dated...
Oh, Saori.
Right.
There's more
to this fortune.
``Don't be persistent or you might be in trouble, so be careful.''
Huh ?
Initial
Next Time:
Itsuki's First Date
Don't miss it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org