Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shita kemuri
Silver smoke in a freezing city...
misugita yume no daisyou
...that's the cost of having an unachievable dream.
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi
A frozen body and unforgettable desire...
accel funde gomakasu
You deceive yourself by stepping on the accelerator.
Yoru ni kowareta mama shisen tsuyoku togarasete
Although depressed in the night, your eyes are kept sharply open.
Dareno kimagure kara sekai sae mo owarisoude
You feel like someone's careless act could end the world.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Obieta me wo shite lost in the night
Lost in the night with frightened eyes...
ochiteku yume ni dakareru
Embraced by a ruined dream.
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart
Scared of loneliness, I'm missing you in my heart.
jibun sae mo kizu tsukete
I almost hurt myself.
Taoreru kurai ni love me so much
Love me so much and knock me out.
subete wo suttee anata wo
If only I can give up everything...
Ai suru koto sae dekitara
...and love you...
kitto sunao ni naresou
...I can be my true self.
Then I cleared
the corner like...
I was almost like the
wind at that moment.
I like the
mountain passes.
When you buy a car,
you should try `em.
My car ?
It's a Road Racer's dream,
the Eight-Five. The Eight-Five.
Well, ordinary people wouldn't know about it though...
The Challenge from the Superstar
This year's summer
was so exciting.
Why ?
``Why ?''
Because I bought a car, and you swept through the Road Racing world like a comet.
Stop calling me
things like that.
One, two, three, four...
What're you counting ?
Four, four.
It's the number of battles
you won this summer.
First there was the Redsuns'
Takahashi Keisuke and his FD.
Then, the Night Kids'
Nakazato and his 32.
And the gumtape death match
against Shoji Shingo's EG6.
Finally, Mako and Sayuki in the Sil-Eighty on Usui.
Four wins in a row.
The legend of the unbeatable Fujiwara Takumi began this summer.
You're no longer just
an airheaded kid.
It's not
a big deal.
Don't be so shy.
Keep winning, Takumi...
...until I defeat you and
become the fastest in Gunma...
...no, I mean on
the Kanto Plain.
The Comet of Akina,
Itsuki, so to speak !
Takumi, we only have an opening ceremony today...
...so why don't we go
somewhere this afternoon ?
But I have to
work this afternoon.
You have to work ?
I want to ride
in your car again...
...because it's
so cute.
Even if it's cute,
it's still my dad's car.
You said you want
to buy your own car.
Have you
saved enough ?
I'm saving almost all my money from work, but there's a long way to go.
How much do you
think you will need ?
About one million yen.
\C5(~$9500~)
One million, huh ?
How much have you
saved so far ?
Still way too low.
Say, Takumi...
...if I gave you 1 million yen,
what would you do ?
I wonder what
would happen.
You'd appreciate it a lot and think that I'm very important to you.
Then you couldn't
oppose me.
You'd quit working and
love me so much everyday.
No, no, Takumi...
Stop kidding around.
One million isn't the kind of money kids like us can earn easily.
So what ?
It's just an idea.
Can't you even dream ?
It's so unrealistic.
So we know that Takumi's technique works wherever he goes.
It's not
just technique...
...but if he's fast on a
course he's never driven...
...he's got good
natural senses.
He's a genius.
He defeated all those modern high performance machines...
...with a 10 year
old Eight-Six.
It's awesome.
How can you say that ?
Just a while ago...
...you said Takumi would be slow because he had never driven anywhere else.
W...well, if you say that...
Everyone thought that.
Takumi is unusual.
I thought he'd lose when I heard that he was going to race on Usui...
...against ``Mako's'' Sil-Eighty.
Sorry, Iketani.
My apologies...
Don't worry.
I go by lonely
driver, Iketani.
That's Itsuki's line.
Welcome.
Flowers ?
You must be mistaken.
This is a
gas station...
Takumi, these are for you.
Who from ?
From Takahashi Ryosuke.
Takahashi...
...Ryosuke.
From Gunma's number one
superstar to Takumi...?!
What does it say ?
Let me read it.
September 15, 10:00pm.
At Mt. Akina's peak.
Hey, that's all it says ?
B...but that's...
Finally, Takahashi Ryosuke has sent him a challenge for a downhill battle.
Takumi, what'll you do ?
Whatever the outcome might be,
he should accept it !
Speaking of the Redsuns, his brother, Takahashi Keisuke, was defeated by Takumi !
Right.
If you refuse this rematch,
it'll be more disgraceful than losing.
What's wrong, Takumi ?
Aren't you having
fun with me ?
I...it's not that.
But you don't
look very interested.
You look out of it.
Well, that's
nothing new, but...
You look like your
mind isn't here.
If you aren't having fun,
I'm going home.
I am having fun.
Sorry, I apologize.
Then tell me what
you were thinking.
I won't forgive
you unless you do.
It would be difficult for you to understand even if I told you.
I'm going home !
Okay, okay.
I'll tell you.
``Battle ?''
Are you going
to fight someone ?
No.  We just call
a car race a ``battle.''
Car race ?
I didn't know you
liked that kind of thing.
I didn't intend liking it.
I was kinda dragged into it.
And my next opponent's
very good and famous.
I haven't been able to help thinking about it since this morning.
I guess this
is pressure.
You're good at driving,
so you'll be okay.
It's not that easy.
If you don't like it,
why don't you ignore him ?
It's not that
I don't like it.
I'm not going to run away, although
I don't know if I can win.
That's just like you.
You want to race deep in
your heart, don't you ?
You look calm, but at the bottom of your heart, you absolutely hate to lose.
I don't dislike that
type of personality.
Let's go home.
Hey, a little longer...
Why don't we talk
a little longer ?
Umm, I know why...
...you fought the soccer club senior classman in the locker room.
After you quit the club, one of the members quietly told me.
You got angry
because of me.
I'm sorry I didn't understand you for such a long time.
It's okay.~~It doesn't
mean anything now.
That's Takumi's Eight-Six.
W...who's that girl ?
Wha...?
Tsuchiya Keiichi's
drift is incredible.
Look at these
sequential photos, Takumi.
Takumi.
Hey, Takumi.
What is it, Itsuki ?
Is it lunch time already ?
You idiot !
It's nothing.
I'm just talking to myself.
Takumi's been acting strangely for the past few days ?
How strange is he ?
He's out of it, and...
That's not unusual.
Well, true...
...but he wasn't that way
during summer break.
But since school started, he looks even worse than before.
I wonder if it's fatigue
from constant battles.
It was his first experience, so he might've lost tension after school started.
That's not quite right.
It's almost like
he's brainless.
Hey, do you think he can race against Takahashi Ryosuke ?
Takumi has a girlfriend,
doesn't he ?
Why'd you ask
that so suddenly ?
Well, I thought he could
be lovesick over a girl.
Lovesick over a girl ?
Yeah.
You were like that when you were with Mako, remember ?
Kenji, it's taboo to
mention her name here.
It's alright, Itsuki.
And I saw Takumi and a
girl in his Eight-Six.
IS THAT TRUE ?!
I only glanced at her,
but she was cute.
Could Takumi's
girlfriend be...?!
No wonder he stopped
going home with me.
That jerk...
I won't forgive you.
I haven't even been
able to touch her hand !
That's it.
That's the reason.
It must be !
Leave it to me !
I'll drag him out
and ask him tonight !
Road Racers don't need
girls, right, Iketani ?
Right !
We're lonely drivers !
So pathetic...
What do you want
to talk about ?
You've been going out with Mogi without telling me, haven't you ?
Oh, that ?
``That ?!''
I didn't think it was
something I had to tell you.
No excuses !
Answer my question !
H...how far have
you gone ?
How far have you gone
with Mogi ?~~Be honest.
``How far...?''
If you're my best friend,
tell me honestly !
Itsuki, look ahead,
look ahead !
I'll tell you !
Go ahead.
Last Sunday...
``Last Sunday.''
The two of us...
``T...Two of us...''
...went to Lake Akina.
Hey...Itsuki !
Look, look !
That's not what
I'm asking.
It's about going from A to B to C !
You're really an idiot.
``A to B...?''
D...did you kiss ?
Yeah.
Say what ?!
Hey, Itsuki, stop !
Stop !
It must be
because of a girl.
What're you looking at ?
You've been acting
strange lately.
Have I ?
It's not like you to think so much,
but you've been thinking a lot lately.
Yeah, you're right.
He must be preoccupied,
recalling the kiss with Mogi.
I'm wondering what'll
happen in the future.
In the future ?!
After a kiss means...
How dare you say such a dirty thing in front of a lonely driver !
I know what happens
after a kiss !
What ?
What do you mean ?
There's only one thing !
What're you talking about ?
We aren't talking
about the same thing.
What I mean
by the future...
Oh, whatever.
I don't like to think
about difficult matters.
I guess his lovesickness can't
be cured so easily.
I was wondering
who that was...
...but that's Keisuke's FD
and Kenta's S14.
Kenta's fast
on the downhill.
His car's grade is Q's with a non-turbo,
so his specialty is downhill.
He's been recognized by Keisuke,
and being trained by him.
If he's being personally taught
by our team's number two...
But there's a race against the
Night Kids the day after tomorrow.
I wonder if he should be
messing around with Kenta.
I guess he's got
time to spare.
So Nakazato Takeshi is going
to be out of his league.
He's been in good
condition lately.
Hey, don't you think his driving style has gotten similar to Ryosuke's ?
Yes, it has.
I think so, too.
I guess Ryosuke trusts
Keisuke completely.
That's why he won't
show up on Myogi.
Keisuke, can I ask
you something ?
What is it ?
Why're you leaving
Akina's Eight-Six alone ?
Why don't you drag him to
Akagi for a return match ?
To Akagi ?
That's right.
You're familiar with the course, so you couldn't be defeated by a mere Eight-Six !
If you don't...
...I will !
You'd better not, Kenta.
Why not ?
Do you think I'd lose ?
If it's Akagi's downhill,
I'd be able to...
That's not the issue.
You're a member of the Redsuns,
so you should know better.
It's our policy to defeat opponents on their home course.
It's true, but...
...Keisuke, I can't stand the fact that we lost to the Eight-Six !
If it's neither of our home courses,
the conditions will be equal !
Let me...
Let me do it !
Don't be so hasty !
Don't worry.
When it's time
to do it...
...there's a person
who'll do it right.
So, Ryosuke
will finally...
Don't be hasty.~~We have a race with the Night Kids first.
Leave it to us.
Something's wrong
with him, after all.
See ?
He confessed.
It's a girl
after all.
We have to do something.
We only have one week before the battle against Takahashi Ryosuke.
This is really bad.
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
************************
Car note:
Q's = The Nissan Silvia has three grades.
Jack, Queen and King.
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
Kagayaku mirai e
...into the bright future.
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Let's make it sure over and over.
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
This passion will be eternal.
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku dakishimete
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
Kiseki no hana yo
The flower of miracles.
Bad, bad, really bad !
What's so bad, Itsuki ?
The battle against
Takahashi Ryosuke is soon...
No time to
think about that.
Takumi is lovesick over a girl at an important time like this.
Lovesick over a girl.
He must have done this and that and something really (bleep) !
Oh, not that again.
Huh ?
Next time on Initial D:
Severe Hill Climb
Don't miss it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org