Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information spread out in a matter of second.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love"...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
You're hopeless !
So lame !
Your driving sucks !
Wataru hasn't
improved at all.
Yeah.
Hey, here it comes !
Oh no.
Hey, clear the road !
Hurry, it's almost here !
Watch the best
driver carefully.
Wow, it's awesome.
No one can copy that.
Don't worry.
Overtake it.
We're gonna pass an oncoming car at the exit of the corner.
Open the inside !
Next, no oncoming car.
Get 5 cm closer
to the inside.
It's sandy.
Just right, and you're in
a good mood and driving well.
No one can
defeat you now.
The Angels of Usui Mountain
N...no way !
A girl you met for the first time
gave you her phone number ?!
I can't believe that !
Something's definitely wrong.
That's right, Iketani !
Life isn't that easy !
I...I...
A Road Racer doesn't
need a girl.
Besides, it doesn't sound like you if there's nothing wrong with this kind of situation.
What do you mean it doesn't sound like me, Kenji ?
Are you making
fun of me ?
I don't mean
it like that.
It just sounds too
good to be true.
I hate it.
I don't like your
envious thoughts.
Her long brown hair
that waved in the wind...
Her charming eyes when
she turned to me...
God must have sent an angel
to a guy who works hard !
I'll go to Karuizawa
to see Mako tomorrow.
Alright, back to work.
Hey, why don't we follow him
to see how cute she is ?
Yeah, let's go.
We've got to see this girl.
But what if
Iketani notices us ?
Don't worry.
Iketani can't focus on
anything else right now.
Welcome.
I've got to check out
this girl called Mako.
Hey, don't get
in Iketani's way.
We won't bother him.
When he gets dumped,
we'll cry together.
For the sake
of our friendship.
Gets dumped, you say...?
She can't be as
good looking as he says.
He tends to exaggerate, and
he easily convinces himself.
You're right.
I think it was when we
were in middle school...
We went to
Akina Lake to fish.
We didn't catch anything until I caught a small one just before we went home.
He was so excited,
and said...
...``It's so big !''
out loud.
It was this small.
Strangers came to see it.
I was so embarrassed
at that time.
Iketani can really
exaggerate things.
Kenji, take a look.
Damn, I was so absorbed in talking,
I wasn't paying attention to my right foot.
I was supposed to follow him,
but I caught up with him.
Sorry, Iketani !
Forgive me.
We just wanted to see
what Mako looks like.
It's true.
We have no intention of bothering you on your date.
Don't be mad.
We'll turn around at
the next interchange.
It can't be helped.
You don't
have to leave.
I don't mind
introducing you to her.
Really ?
Great.
But...
...don't follow us after
that, or I will get mad.
Okay.
So...
...they're my friends.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Sato Mako.
H...hi.
H...hello.
Well, Mako...
Okay.
Are we dogs
or something ?
It's not a dream.
I don't believe it.
I'm so shocked.
How could Iketani
find such a cute girl ?
Road Racers don't
need a girl.
Kenji, why don't
we cry together ?
What do you mean ?
Are you saying I'll
never find a girl ?
It was just a joke.
What should
we do now ?
Well...
Karuizawa isn't the place for three guys to hang out this time of year.
Why don't we go to
Usui's mountain pass ?
S...sorry.
Do you have a
favorite car, Mako ?
It's not quite
my favorite...
...but I used to dream
of the previous model RX-7.
The FC ?
You have
good taste.
You're a Road
Racer, aren't you ?
Well...can you tell ?
I usually try to drive
like everyone else.
What do you think
of Road Racers ?
I think it's alright,
because I also like cars.
Really ?
Road Racers are better at driving than ordinary people.
If you have money, you
can buy a good car...
...but you can't
buy technique.
I prefer someone who can use
technique when needed...
...to someone who has
an expensive imported car.
She's great.
She's my ideal girl.
So this is
Usui's mountain pass...
This is the first time I've seen it, and it's a much harder winding road than I imagined.
It's incredible.
It's one corner after another,
and the road is narrow.
It's nothing like Akina.
I wonder who's the
fastest on Usui.
Umm...you are...
Y...yes...?
From a man's
point of view...
...if there's a girl who likes mountain passes, and tries to be a Road Racer...
...what would you
think about that ?
Sil-Eighty ?
Yeah, the blue Sil-Eighty is said to be the fastest.
Don't be surprised
by this, though.
The driver
is a woman.
A woman ?!
Female Road Racer ?
Y...yeah.
I like it.
I think it's okay.
It's great.
A female Road Racer would
be wonderful to talk to.
Is that so ?
Yeah.
I see.
I get it.
She wants to be a Road Racer.
And her dream
car is the FC.
A girl driving
a Sil-Eighty...?
What's a Sil-Eighty ?
Is it an import ?
No.
The Sil-Eighty is a 180
with a Silvia front  on it.
A Silvia and a 180 are combined,
so it's called a Sil-Eighty.
And the driver is a girl, and she's the fastest on Usui's mountain pass.
I want to see this.
If you wait until nightfall, you'll be able to see it on Usui's mountain pass.
But don't even think about challenging her, because none of the locals can defeat her.
It's called the
Akina Speedstars.
I assembled the team, and we have the fastest driver on Akina.
He's my junior worker.
Speaking of the skill,
I guess I'd be second.
What's wrong, Mako ?
Oh, nothing at all.
Sorry.
I must be boring you with
all this talk about cars.
No, not at all.
I like cars a lot,
so it's fun.
Really ?
That's good.
Ah, do you think
drift is cool, too ?
A little...
You have to drive hard
like me to master that.
It's a dangerous technique.
Are you good
at drifting ?
A little...
I'm happy for some reason.
You are...?
Thank you.
It was fun today.
Ah, Mako...
Yes ?
Are you...
Well...
Is there someone you're
going out with now...?
Well...
Do you have anyone ?
I don't have a boyfriend.
So, please call
me again, Iketani.
Hey, Iketani...
Can you hear me ?
Iketani, get a grip.
I'm...
Why're you
guys still here ?
We were concerned about you,
so we couldn't go home.
So how was it ?
Did it go well ?
Today is such
a wonderful day.
Let's go eat.
It doesn't happen very often,
but it's gonna be my treat.
And it's not a bad idea to take a look at the Usui guys' driving, too.
I guess it
went well.
So miracles do happen.
Pretty good.
Everyone on Usui
is highly skilled.
Hey, Takumi...
...you'd never seen a mountain pass other than Akina, right ?
How was it ?
``How was it ?''
I wasn't driving,
so I don't know.
Are you sure ?
You looked so serious.
I did ?
Your eyes looked totally
different from now.
I can't believe they're
of the same person.
What do you say ?
Do you think you can drive it ?
I can't tell
unless I try.
Here it comes !
The Sil-Eighty ?
Nonstop counter drift ?
What the hell ?
She's really good.
See that ?
The road is narrow,
so it looked so exciting.
I talked big and told Mako
that I'm good at drifting...
...but in reality, I panic
when the rear starts to skid.
This is bad.
I've gotta practice hard,
or my angel will be gone.
Let's go down.
Okay.
Every mountain pass has
an incredible driver.
Hey, look...Iketani
is driving so fast.
There are three in here,
so I can't keep up.
You'd better
keep your distance.
The rhythm is bad.
Something's wrong with his car.
Do you think
something's gonna happen ?
I don't mean that something
will happen, but probably...
Probably ?
He screwed up, just
like you said.
Just like Takumi said.
Oh shit, a car is coming !
That was close.
Who's that idiot ?
The rear skidded, he got scared, released the gas pedal, and oversteered.
That's the most uncool spin
only an amateur would do.
Hey, 13 dude !
If you don't move your car quickly,
you'll endanger other cars !
I'm moving it now.
It's so embarrassing !
How uncool.
Let's pretend to be strangers.
I'm really sor...
What's wrong ?
It's nothing.
Usui Mountain's fastest
driver is Mako in her Sil-Eighty.
I feel like
I could die.
He took the day off ?
He didn't even call.
That workaholic, Iketani ?
I don't believe it.
He must've been
really shocked.
He didn't talk
at all afterwards.
When we stopped at a service
area to use the restroom...
...he looked out of it,
and his eyes weren't focusing.
We were so sorry for him,
we didn't know what to say.
I had a bad feeling.
She's too cute to
be Iketani's girl.
After all, Road Racers
don't need a girl.
Lonely driver, Itsuki.
That's my motto.
I hope the shock
doesn't last too long.
Kouichiro, phone call !
I don't want to take it.
Tell him I'm sleeping.
It must be Kenji anyway.
It's a girl !
Sato Mako !
You said you
wanted to talk.
If you're making
fun of me, please stop.
No, I'm not
making fun of you.
I never thought that you'd be the driver of that incredible car.
I saw your Sil-Eighty
drifting at full speed.
They say you're
the fastest on Usui.
If so, you could
have told me.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean
to lie to you.
It was shocking
for me, too.
And I thought I should
tell you the truth.
Truth ?
I'm actually
the quiet type.
Quiet...?
That's hard to believe, because you can perform such a dynamic drift.
You know how some people's personalities change once they get behind the wheel ?
I'm that type.
When I drive fast,
guys don't see me as a girl.
So I thought
I should quit.
I've made up my mind.
I'm quitting road
racing this summer.
For my last memory
of this summer...
...would you let me race against Akina's Eight-Six on Usui's mountain pass ?
That's my wish.
If you make my
wish come true...
...you can have
my virginity.
Wait a minute.
Don't say such a thing.
Am I not enough ?
It's not that.
He's my friend, so I can't
make a deal like that.
I understand.
Her target was never me,
it was always Takumi.
It's obvious.
Otherwise, a cute girl like her would never be interested in me.
Okay, I'll see
what I can do.
Really ?
Don't misunderstand me.
I'll cooperate, but not because
I want something from you.
Iketani...
I just want to make
your wish come true.
It's alright.
Although it was only a short time,
I was seriously in love with Mako.
As long as she's happy,
I'll be satisfied.
People would call me a fool,
but I really loved her.
Even though it was my misunderstanding, I really loved her.
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sake bara no youni akaku
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku kimo wo daite
************************
Car Notes:
Two faces were given to the Nissan 240SX
(Called 180SX in Japan for its smaller engine)
The coupe body with fixed headlights was called the Silvia, and the hatchback body with pop up headlights was called the 180SX
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
************************
A shop came up with an idea to replace the front end of the 180SX with the Silvia one for the heck of it
It was sold under the name Sil-Eighty
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
************************
Imagine the Camaro front end on the Firebird. Lame, isn't it ?
Kagayaku mirai e
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Kiseki no hana yo
Mako, how could a cute girl
like you go after Iketani ?
Even if you
ask me why...
And that
shocking comment.
I guess it
was too bold.
There are so
many handsome guys.
But why ?~~How can
Iketani be the one ?
Even if you ask me...
After all, Iketani is...
I don't understand, no
matter how hard I try...
Next time on Initial D:
``Sudden Death Death Match.''
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org