Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves a lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
Sonuva...
Hey, you're the one !
You hit my car from
behind, didn't you ?!
Gimme a break.
It was your fault.
Say what ?
You were so slow, I couldn't
predict your actions.
I didn't expect you to
enter the corner so slowly.
I couldn't brake in time,
and I touched your tail.
How dare you !
Stop, Iketani !
If you want me to apologize,
we'll race by our rules...
...and if you win, I'll
kneel down to the ground.
By your rules ?
What do you mean ?
It's not so difficult.
We call it a
gumtape death match.
Gumtape death match ?
I heard that there's a fast Eight-Six downhill driver in the Speedstars.
Tell the Eight-Six brat that I'll be waiting here at 10:00pm next Saturday.
Catch ya later.
What's with him ?
He challenged Takumi.
But he doesn't
know Takumi's face.
Takumi, take his challenge, whether it's a gumtape death match or not !
Defeat the guy,
and make him kneel down !
Don't be stupid.
It's too risky, Itsuki.
He won't be able to
steer during the race.
But, Iketani, Takumi has defeated the FD and 32 !
He won't lose just because
of some customized rule !
Idiot, that guy must've practiced a lot under that rule.
Takumi, don't race at such
a disadvantage, no matter what.
I don't have any
intention of racing.
Yeah, that's good.
Just ignore him.
Itsuki's First Date
What ?
A gumtape death match ?
Yes.
That's ridiculous.
And what about Takumi ?
He's calm and
uninterested like usual.
He doesn't
feel like racing.
I want Takumi to race.
He'll outrun that jerk, make him kneel down, and we'll feel great !
He's driving a Civic, the
archrival of Levins and Truenos !
Yeah, when we were young,
we used gears and rules...
...but the gumtape death match was one of the most dangerous battles.
Is a gumtape death match really that dangerous ?
I don't quite get it.
Itsuki, get in your
car and give it a try.
Then you'll see.
Well...
Okay, steer full to either left or right, while keeping your right hand on the steering wheel.
O...okay.
I can't turn
any farther.
Okay, leave the steering wheel as it is and get out of the car.
Okay.
Now see how
far you steered.
O...okay.
It only turned that much ?!
I thought I steered a lot.
See ?
How would you turn
in the corners ?
You couldn't drive
in the mountain passes.
You can only use steering
to initiate the turn.
You must slide the rear
tires to clear the corners.
All of them.
But Takumi's good at drifting,
so he'll be able to pull it off.
It's not that easy.
He can't countersteer, which
makes drift control difficult.
If he oversteers a bit,
he'll go into a spin.
But if he understeers at the entrance, it'll be over.
This rule gives
FF cars an advantage.
The opponent is
an EG6, right ?
Yes.
Since the EG6 has an FF layout...
...he can cope with oversteering using the gas pedal, so he can enter corners fast...
...and he can also minimize the ``under'' by using the parking brake.
In order for an FR like
the Eight-Six to race safely...
...just like a circus
tightrope walker...
...he has to drift throughout the race and maintain extreme control.
He'd better not do it.
Damn, if he heard that,
he might become interested.
Umm, Manager...
Hey, it's Kenji.
Iketani, it's about that
jerk from the other day.
I did a little
investigating.
He's Shoji Shingo of
the Myogi Night Kids.
Shoji Shingo of
the Night Kids...?
He's supposed to
be their number two...
...but he claims to be the fastest of the Night Kids on the downhill.
But he doesn't choose normal means to accomplish his goal...
...so the other members
don't trust him.
He especially doesn't get along with their leader, Nakazato Takeshi.
I see.
So he wants to defeat Takumi to gain influence in the Night Kids.
He's going around
spreading a nasty rumor.
What ?
A rumor...?
Yeah.
``The Speedstars are scared, and we won't accept his challenge.''
It doesn't say anything about it being a gumtape death match.
So we're the only
ones who'll look bad.
What an asshole.
Yeah.
He's trying to drag Takumi
into racing him, no matter what.
Takumi...
Me...?
Means nothing to me.
I won't accept his challenge.
That's good.
Even if you've been challenged, it's too ridiculous to accept.
Don't sweat it.
O...okay.
So, what about the battle
with the Eight-Six ?
I'm ready any time.
It's their move now.
Wait and see.
I'll drag that
Eight-Six brat out.
It'll be an
interesting battle.
Takeshi...
Shingo, you seem to
be planning something.
I don't care
what you do...
...just don't disgrace the name of the Night Kids, okay ?
What's so funny ?
Aren't you the one who's disgraced our name already ?
Say what ?
Who was the one who was totally outrun by a brat in a dated Eight-Six ?
And in a high
powered 32, at that ?
Shingo...
A loser should go
bark somewhere else.
I don't want you preaching to me as if you'll be our leader forever.
Nakazato, I'll avenge you.
You should
thank me.
Shingo, you'll eventually see how great the Eight-Six is.
Man, Takeshi is
on the way out.
Really, he was so lame.
From now on, the leader of the Night Kids is you, Shingo.
Before that, I'll send Akina's
Eight-Six to the junkyard.
Hello, this
is Takeuchi...
Is this Saori ?
Oh, Itsuki...?
Sure, I remember you.
Go driving to
Akina Lake ?
Okay.
I'll be waiting at
the bus stop at 1:00pm.
Yeah.~~Bye.
Alright !
My 18 years of life without
a girlfriend is finally over !
I'll do it !
Here.
Oh, Dad...
What ?
Is a gumtape
death match...
Nothing.
Never mind.
Gumtape death match, huh ?
You're so...
...good at driving.
I don't mind staying
overnight if it's with you.
I think of her a lot.
Thank you very much !
Where's Itsuki ?
He was washing
a car a while ago.
I wonder
where he went.
I see, I see.
So...
...you're neglecting work
in a place like this.
I...I'm just
taking a break.
It's unusual to
see you reading.
T...that's...
Let's see...
Love manual ?
How to romance a girl ?
Well, that's...
Reading a book
like this means...
...you've got a date ?
Y...yes.
With that babe, Saori,
you talked about ?
How dare you
get ahead of me !
I bought the book on the way home yesterday, and I've been studying hard.
When it comes to things like this, I don't think I can depend on you.
You're straightforward. It can't be helped because it's true.
Things are so
convenient these days.
We had to find out everything
by ourselves in my time.
Let me see...
``It's an established fact, to get close to a girl by the third date...''
``...create a romantic mood
for the first kiss...''
I'm perfectly
prepared, Manager.
So I'm taking a day off,
like I told you earlier.
So that's what it's all about.
I guess it's alright.
I'm envious of you !
This is it.
Saori...?
Over here, Itsuki !
Gorgeous.
Welcome...
I don't need any gas.
I want to hear your answer
about the gumtape death match.
You told the Eight-Six
guy about it, didn't you ?
Yeah.
He has no intention
of racing you.
That's what he said.
That's funny.
Akina's Eight-Six
driver is a coward.
The gumtape death match
scared him off, huh ?
That doesn't matter.
I'll do anything
to make him race.
So cute.
We Road Racers don't say, ``turn into the curve,'' we say, ``tackle the corner.''
I want to
get a license.
Why don't you ?
I'll teach you how.
Okay, I'll think about it.
Akina Fuji.
It's so beautiful.
``Girls react to the mood.
Do the first kiss in a romantic setting.''
First kiss...
It's the right chance.
Go for it, Itsuki !
Itsuki !
I'm sorry.
The mood is heavy.
I'm in trouble.
Found you.
An EG6...
He tapped my bumper.
Does it mean I should
get out of the way ?
He's right on my butt.
Shit, I have to be decisive
in front of Saori.
Saori, I'm gonna
speed up a little bit.
Please bear with it
for a while, okay ?
Itsuki, stop !
It's a battle
between Road Racers !
I can't stop !
At...at least Saori...
Hey, we have
a problem !
Itsuki had
an accident !
Where ?
On Akina's mountain pass !
He was taken to the city hospital !
You two go
check on him !
Right.
Are you alright, Itsuki ?
Senpai, Takumi.
What happened ?
They're overreacting.
It's not as
bad as it looks...
...but they're keeping
me here to be sure.
What about Saori ?
She was with you, wasn't she ?
She only got a scratch,
so she went home already.
I steered hard so I wouldn't
crush the passenger side.
What happened
to the car...
...your Eight-Five ?
It spun just right, so it only
suffered minor damage to the trunk.
It's done.
Take care.
Thank you.
I was going downhill on Akina,
and an EG6 tailgated me.
An EG6 ?
Him again ?
Probably, because
it was a red EG6.
I was suddenly bumped
from behind in a corner.
That asshole
did it again.
Shit.
I'll do it !
Whether it's a gumtape death
match or not, I'll do it !
Takumi, wait !
Takumi...
Sorry.
Don't be taken in
by his strategy !
A gumtape death match
is too dangerous !
Don't do it, Takumi !
I won't lose,
no matter what.
My pride says "You gotta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make room.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
`Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin' my dream.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation}Your motivation is easy.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safety zone.
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change, even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang, another round, never slow down.
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down to the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logic...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
You've caused Itsuki
to have an accident.
You're playing dirty,
aren't you, Shingo ?
I don't care, as long as
Akina's Eight-Six shows up.
Come on...
I know my chances of winning
the gumtape death match are 100%.
It won't be fun to simply defeat him, so I'll arrange an interesting show.
N...next time on Initial D:
``Improving Genius of Drift !''
I'll make him experience
true fear in the downhill.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org