Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information spread out in a matter of second.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love"...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
Five seconds !
Four !
Three !
Two !
One !
Go !
I've been steering hard,
keeping the ABS on !
So the load to the front tires is greater than I expected !
It's getting tough !
The five hairpins
are ahead...
What ?
The place where you were overtaken will be the key point.
Dangerous Five Hairpins
The Eight-Six is
right on his tail !
I don't believe it !
Nakazato is fighting
so desperately !
What's going on ?!
Look !~~That's the braking
drift of the Eight-Six !
Awesome.
The FC...?
Takahashi Ryosuke.
I watched Keisuke being overtaken by the Eight-Six in these five hairpins.
That Eight-Six used
the gutter to turn.
He blocked the inside.
He's trying not to let him squeeze in.
That Nakazato...
What're you going
to do, Eight-Six ?
What ?
From the outside ?!
Watch out !
It's gonna crash !
Don't screw around with me !
I won't let you pass from the outside !
Just like the 32.
Sharp acceleration at
the exit is great.
Besides, that Eight-Six...
He kept skidding in
such a narrow curve.
Three more corners...
...and this battle
will be settled.
He's going to overtake
from the outside again !
So frustrating !
It pisses me off when
he gets outside of me !
The 32 is
acting strange.
Nakazato has lost
his concentration.
Keep your eyes
on them, Keisuke.
The Eight-Six's
gonna overtake him.
Overtake him...?
But the inside
is blocked.
How ?
Takumi's trying
to overtake him ?
Really ?
Great.
Way to go, Takumi !
I'm humiliated in front of so many galleries, almost being overtaken from the outside !
Because I get too
close to the inside...
...the car misses the ideal line,
and the entry speed has to be slower !
That's right.~~I only have to make a space slightly narrower than a car !
That way, my entry
speed can be faster !
Good, he's not gonna
take the inside !
The Eight-Six disappeared !
It can't be...!
Dammit, it understeered
at a critical moment !
He tried to go outside, and then he changed the line while braking !
The Eight-Six is capable
of doing that ?
But don't think that
you're going to win !
If we accelerate side by side, I'll be able to pull ahead at full throttle in 2nd gear !
I'll show you the true
potential of the 32 !
I lost.
The 32 and
I have lost.
No, that's not right.
Only I lost.
The car didn't lose
to the Eight-Six.
An incredible Road
Racer like him exists.
It's shocking,
but I feel refreshed.
Although I lost,
I tried my best.
What a pain.
The bodywork will
cost 70,000 yen ($700).
I'll train myself and
challenge him again.
He did it !
Takumi won !
He did it !~~He did it !
He did it !
Takumi did...
Takumi did it !
N...no way.
The Eight-Six overtook the 32 in
the fourth corner of the five hairpins !
How could the Eight-Six
defeat the 32 ?
The Eight-Six did ?
Really ?
I don't believe it !
It's just like you said, Bunta.
Just like him.
It's fun to watch interesting
things, isn't it, Keisuke ?
Yeah, the attack of the
Eight-Six was incredible.
He pretended to go outside, but changed the line during full braking.
It's got wonderful ABS.
What are you saying ?
Don't be dumb, Keisuke.
How could an Eight-Six
be equipped with ABS ?
Because...
That was human ABS.
Those Road Racers who've gotten used to modern cars equipped with ABS...
...would never be able to master severe pedal control just before locking their tires.
ABS is computer controlled, so it can't surpass the right foot of a well-trained driver.
I'm finally excited
after such a long time.
That Eight-Six is definitely
worth defeating.
Why're you
standing there ?
No reason.
Hey, Dad...
...about this car...
What ?
It's alright.
It's nothing.
I'm going to bed.
I bought an Eight-Six !
I kept it secret, but
it was delivered today !
It's still clean !
So you begged your dad,
and made him a guarantor.
The shop was nice, and I got a good price for the condition of the car.
Looks really good.
It could be a find.
I'm surprised.
You really
bought one, Itsuki.
Of course, Takumi.
I can't let you get
too far ahead of me.
From now on, I'll try to be one of the two fastest Eight-Six downhill Road Racers.
Such a big talker.
I couldn't sleep last night
because I was so happy.
I know what you mean.
I couldn't sleep the night
before my S13 was delivered.
That's right.
It's really my car.
My car.
I feel like I'm
having a dream.
Normal wheels and 70 aspect ratio tires look pathetic but adequate.
Hey, start up
the engine, Itsuki.
Sure.
No problem.
It doesn't
sound so good.
I guess it's because
the muffler is normal.
Don't worry.
I'll change the muffler.
I want to make it sound
as good as Takumi's Trueno.
I have a bad feeling.
Pop the hood, Itsuki.
I thought so.
Manager.
You're mistaken, Itsuki.
Mistaken...?
This isn't
an Eight-Six.
It's an Eight-Five.
Eight-Five...
You mean an AE85 ?
Comparing the Eight-Six and Eight-Five,
the body is the same...
...but the performance differences are like chocolate and shit, a goddess and an old maid !
The Eight-Six has a double overhead cam engine, and the Eight-Five has a single one !
DOHC and SOHC are
totally different !
You bought a car
without knowing that ?!
How lame !
Sorry, sorry, Itsuki,
but it's so funny !
Wait, Itsuki !
You guys laughed too much.
Think how
Itsuki feels.
Sorry...
Itsuki !
Leave me alone !
Don't bother me !
Even if you say so...
It was my fault for looking for a car by myself to surprise everyone.
That explains why it was
so cheap for an Eight-Six.
I got so excited
without knowing it.
I'm so embarrassed
I could die.
You're laughing inside,
aren't you ?
No.
I'm envious of you.
Envious ?
Don't give
me that BS !
It's not BS.
You're still in high school
and you have your own car.
My own car ?
Yeah.~~What's wrong
with an Eight-Five ?
It's got an engine,
tires and it runs.
Even if it doesn't have power,
it can pick up speed on the downhill.
Why don't you practice hard
and learn some techniques ?
Cars are interesting.
You know,
you've changed.
Have I ?
Yeah, you were uninterested
in cars before.
Takumi, I feel like I could
like my Eight-Five.
I'm not that
good anyway.
Right.
Don't agree
so easily.
I'd better drive on
Mt. Akina tonight.
Takumi, come with me.
Sure.
With your Eight-Five.
Takumi...
I'll pick you
up around 10:00pm !
Promise me, okay ?
Okay.
Don't go to bed,
just wait for me !
Didn't see
the Eight-Six.
I wanted to see it.
It's hard to imagine that an Eight-Six defeated a 32.
Isn't that
an Eight-Six ?
Could it be...?
Man, it's so fun driving
the mountain pass !
It's slow on
the straightaways...
...but it runs well in the
corners, doesn't it, Takumi ?
Yeah, more or less.
What're you doing ?
Well, if I look at
it from a distance...
...my Levin looks cool.
Why're you so
cool, my Levin ?!
I'm glad I bought
this Levin !
How optimistic you are.
They're just brats.
They couldn't be.
The technician who defeated
the 32 couldn't be one of them.
Right.
How old are you ?
Do you have a license ?
If you don't,
you'll be in trouble.
I do.
I look young, but
I'm eighteen years old.
What's with them ?
They're so rude.
What's the point of
picking on a child ?
I don't like young Road Racer
wannabes driving Eight-Sixes.
You're a local,
aren't you ?
We came here to see
the famous Eight-Six.
Do you know about it ?
Don't you have a mouth ?
You know about it, don't you ?
Well...I know
about it...
But I don't think
it'll show up tonight.
That sucks.~~And after we
came all the way up here.
Let's go home.
If you're trying to be a Road Racer,
try not to be so pathetic.
What's wrong with
this Eight-Six ?
These normal wheels make
me sick just looking at them.
It's so lame.
At least change
the muffler.
It sounds so uncool.
Do you know anything
about an Eight-Six ?
Well, it's not an Eight-Six,
it's an Eight-Five.
So even if I changed the muffler,
it won't sound good.
I still want to
change it though.
Eight-Five ?
Even if you want
to change the muffler...
...you won't find one anywhere
that fits the Eight-Five !
None, anywhere.
My eyes are watering !
I've never seen anyone
driving an Eight-Five !
A brat deserves
an Eight-Five !
Let's go home.
I laughed so
hard I cried.
Try hard and don't let
a scooter tailgate you.
I'm pissed. I can't let
them get away with that.
Itsuki, let me use
your car for a while.
Takumi !
Get in the
car quickly.
What're you gonna do,
chase them ?
The suspension on the Eight-Five
is so weak, and the tires are normal !
I don't care.
Hey, Takumi, don't !
It doesn't have the limited
slip differential, and...
Who cares.
Put your seatbelt on.
It might be a little scary, but just trust me and bear with it.
I won't wreck
your precious car.
Here we go.
T...Takumi !
Taku...Taku...Taku...
My...my...
my Eight-Five...
Please drive gently
with my Eight-Five !
My pride says "You gatta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make a room.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin my dream.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
************************
SOHC = Single Overhead Cam
DOHC = Dual Overhead Cam
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safe zone.
************************
SOHC = Single Overhead Cam
DOHC = Dual Overhead Cam
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
************************
SOHC = Single Overhead Cam
DOHC = Dual Overhead Cam
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down on the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logics...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
Tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
Are you crying, Iketani ?
I'm so happy !
My S13 will finally be back !
Oh, that ill-fated specialty car, the S13, which crashed in episode two.
Hey, Iketani,
what's wrong ?
By the way...
...I heard a red EG6 showed up on the mountain pass aiming for Takumi's Eight-Six.
Do you know
anything about it ?
Nope.
Next time on Initial D,
``Dangerous Shingo Appears.''
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org