Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information spread out in a matter of second.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love"...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashittó
Get things done right only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
A Hot Wind and Violent Drive on Usui's Mountain Pass
They're fast.
Looks really bad.
Can I make it ?
If they can do it,
there's no reason I can't.
Go.
Next, almost rub the inside.
Grip the road.
Very good, Mako.
Obstacles.
Move outward.
Not bad.  He isn't
an ordinary Road Racer.
He's on our tail.
Otherwise we wouldn't
have any fun.
I wonder how much longer he can keep up with us.
We haven't gotten
serious yet.
This's tough. I'm not
driving in my own style.
I'm just copying
their style.
This isn't any different
than a roller coaster.
Because I'm not in
my rhythm, this is scary.
But if I get outrun now, I won't be able to catch up later.
I've got to keep up.
Not knowing the course is a much tougher handicap than I thought.
If I lose my concentration, I'll crash into the mountainside or fall off the cliff.
Just like Akina's
famous Eight-Six.
He won't let us
outrun him so easily.
The terror of Usui, where the corners appear one after another, begins now.
A right-hander's, next.
It's narrow.
Okay.
She's fast.
Damn, but I can't
let it pull away.
If they can turn,
I should be able to.
Takumi said, if they can turn, he should be able to, didn't he ?
Yes, that's what he said.
I don't believe it.
What a simple idea.
What's his brain
made of ?
But it's a great
thing, in a sense.
Only a skilled driver like him
would think about that.
Unless he loses control at a corner's entrance, he can control the car...
He should be able to.
But his opponent is...
...Mako and her Sil-Eighty, who knows everything about this mountain's passes.
She must be pushing her
car to the limit...
...so Takumi'll have to enter
corners at the same speed.
His first time on Usui's
unfamiliar passes...
That gives me a chill.
It's scary to
even think about.
Yeah.~~He'll need plenty of guts, not just technique.
One mistake
will be deadly.
He said his opponent
is a Sil-Eighty.
What's a Sil-Eighty ?
He's on my tail.
Why ?~~I'm driving
fast enough, aren't I ?
Yes, you are.
You're in a good mood.
But he's right
on my tail.
Stop looking into the mirror.
It'll disturb your rhythm.
I'm checking what's happening behind us, so don't worry.
It's just begun.
We have to enjoy this.
It's a great battle.
Okay, I'll leave
it to you.
Right, trust your partner.
You and I are the
best team on Usui.
If the frontrunner runs away from the chaser, the front wins.
If not, switch positions and try again until the game is settled.
It's a sudden death
death match.
With this rule, you should take the front for the first heat.
Yeah, there'll be a second heat,
so you'll have a chance to practice.
Even if you lose in the second heat,
you won't look too bad.
I'll take the rear
for the first heat.
Think it over, Takumi.
Okay ?
This is my battle, isn't it ?
Let me decide.
Damn, I chose the rear because
I hate having somebody on my tail...
...but I didn't expect
it to be this hard.
Takahashi
The most difficult part of attacking an unfamiliar course is...
...the ability to decide
a corner's entry speed.
The reason why
Keisuke was defeated...
...and the reason Nakazato was
passed are essentially the same.
No matter how skilled a driver is, he can't match one who drives hard every day.
If so, to defeat the
Eight-Six on Akina...
I can win.
With my hypothesis, I'll be able to defeat him, even on Akina.
Damn, I guess
I was wrong.
I took a big gamble.
Just a few centimeters difference at the entrance...
...and the speed difference causes a big gap at the exit.
Damn, too fast...
I scratched the bumper.
Damn, I won't
let it pull away.
A Road Racer grows by experiencing many terrifying moments.
With extraordinary concentration and trained driving technique...
...and with my perfect
suspension setting...
...he won't lose.
I wonder
what's happening.
Is the race
already settled ?
We won't know
until they return.
It's impossible.
No matter how you look
at it, it's too unfair.
B...but, Iketani...
...so far, none of the races have been easy for Takumi.
Nakazato's 32
was monstrous.
And the gumtape death match with that Shoji guy was his first try at that.
But one thing was
always on his side.
They all happened on Akina...
...where Takumi has driven every day
for the last five years.
Senpai, is the course
difference that important ?
It'd be different if he had
driven here a few times...
...but this is his
very first time.
Well...let me see...
Come to think
of it, Iketani...
...I've been wondering.
Who's the girl sitting
next to Mako ?
Who ?~~
Even if you ask me...
She caught my attention, too.
She got in the car so naturally, even though they were going to race.
I don't really know her well, but she's been her best friend since childhood...
...and they've driven together since they were beginners...
...and they perfected
their driving skill.
So she's like
a rally navigator.
If so, Takumi's in an even
more difficult situation.
Don't worry.
Takumi shouldn't lose.
But with a good navigator sitting next to Mako, she can concentrate on driving.
Obstacle before
the corner.
Avoid it and
close the inside.
He's still keeping
up with us.
How can he follow us
at this high pace ?
Mako is in the best condition, but he's still on our tail.
What a guy...
Mako, C-121 is near.
Let's settle this race.
You can skid from the
entry of the corner.
Let's show him what we can do at the most difficult corner on Mt. Usui.
Okay, I got it.
I'll show him my car skid from the entry to the exit.
No one has cleared the
corner at my entry speed.
Haven't Mako and Sayuki
come tonight ?
I don't know.
I haven't seen them.
I want to see
the Sil-Eighty's drift.
This C-121 corner
is the highlight.
It's really difficult.
It's more than
just difficult.
If you can skid from the entry to the exit, you're considered highly skilled on Usui.
If you're good on Usui,
you're the best wherever you go.
Yeah.
You have to enter the corner at high speed with lots of guts...
...or you'll lose speed, and your drift won't last until the exit.
Everyone fails on
their first try.
But if you get used to it,
you can do it, right ?
Only a few can.
Only Mako's Sil-Eighty enters the corner at full throttle.
I don't know how fast she goes,
but no one can copy her.
Someone's coming down.
The squeals are so loud.
Someone's really pushing it hard.
There it is.
It's the Sil-Eighty !
Mako and Sayuki.
There's a car behind it.
Who is it ?
Are they racing ?
Isn't that an Eight-Six ?
No oncoming traffic.
Let's show off, Mako !
Okay.
Go !
They dove into
the corner !
I don't know
who he is...
...but he must be stupid, entering the corner at the same speed as Mako !
He doesn't know
how difficult C-121 is !
You can't clear the
corner with only courage !
He's got nerve entering the
corner right behind Mako.
Once you enter this corner at that speed, you can't use any tricks.
The middle section of the C-121 is wide, but the exit is extremely narrow.
There appear to be many lines you can take, but there's only one.
Will you be able to stay on that line on your first try ?
Im...impossible.
He cleared it.
I don't believe it.
Who's driving
that Eight-Six ?
Could that be...?
Could that be Akina's Eight-Six
they've been talking about lately ?
I've got goose bumps.
How ?
The difficulty of four-wheel drift at very high speed is ultra D.
Even with all her experience, Mako missed the entry by five centimeters.
But he controlled the car to follow the ideal line.
We can't win.
We chose a totally outclassing
monster as our opponent.
No, you shouldn't skid
so much in this corner !
You should have told me that before we entered the corner, Sayuki !
What's wrong with you ?
Snap out of it.
It's not like you.
Don't you get
it yet, Mako ?
The Eight-Six behind
us is a monster.
We won't be able to
win with our skill.
Say what ?
You always talk big.
The race isn't over, but
you're ready to give up ?
I don't like that.
Of course not, but...
I don't care.
I didn't know you
were such a coward.
I won't depend
on you anymore.
We knew that the Eight-Six was extraordinary from the beginning.
I decided this race
would be my last !
So unless we try our best,
I won't be satisfied !
How can you have
gotten so timid ?
You're the worst !~~You're like baggage in the passenger seat !
Baggage ?
Yes, you're only ballast, worsening the power to weight ratio !
She's one of those people who changes personality behind the wheel.
How can you
call me ballast ?
I've got a nice body,
and I'm not chubby or fat !
But you're a
49 kg\C5(107.8 lbs)\C3 handicap !
47 kg !
\C5(103.4 lbs)
Now that you've said that,
I can't stay quiet.
Let's do it, Mako !
Drive like hell !
That's more like it.
Turn hard, as if you were going to hit the cliff in the next corner.
Okay, Sayuki.
Wings of fire, tsubasa ni koi no honoo nosete Higher
Wings of fire. We let our wings carry our passion for love.
Higher !
Wings of fire jiyuu ni hateshinaku takaku tobu
Wings of fire. We fly high so freely.
Wing of fire, futari wa speed ageteyuku Higher
Wings of fire. The two of us pick up speed.
I can do it.
Wings of fire, hirogaru kono oozora wo kakemeguru
Wings of fire. We fly around in the open sky.
*********************
I'm getting better, even while I'm desperately following them.
I can feel the rhythm
of this mountain pass.
I can drive
in my own rhythm.
There are a few
corners to go.
But I won't
drop my guard.
I'll push harder and
harder till the end.
For the pride of the best on Usui,
I won't let this be regrettable.
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sake bara no youni akaku
************************
Song: ``Wings of Fire''
A duet by Mako and Sayuki
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Kagayaku mirai e
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Kiseki no hana yo
Bunta, does Takumi have a chance of winning the battle against the Sil-Eighty ?
Who knows.
``Who knows...?''
I'm a tofu shop owner,
not a fortuneteller.
Oh, can I have
Gammo and fried tofu ?
It's the Eight-Six
I've thoroughly tuned.
No car can outrun
my car on the downhill.
So, it's up
to the driver.
Well, wait and you'll
see next week.
You're mean.
I'll buy both
soft and hard tofu.
Next time on Initial D,
``Race-Settling Super Drift.''
Make sure you see it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org