Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shita kemuri...
...misugita yume no daisyou.
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi.
Accel funde gomakasu.
Yoru ni kowareta mama shisen tsuyoku togarasete.
Dareno kimagure kara sekai sae mo owarisoude.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Obieta me wo shite lost in the night.
Ochiteku yume ni dakareru.
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart.
Jibun sae mo kizu tsukete.
Taoreru kurai ni love me so much.
Subete wo suttee anata wo...
...ai suru koto sae dekitara...
...kitto sunao ni naresou.
Yo, Takumi !
You look sleepy.
It's my nature.
Hey, it's time.
For the battle against
Takahashi Ryosuke.
I'm looking forward to it so much that I can't concentrate on studying.
He's the fastest in Gunma.
And Takahashi Ryosuke's very
popular with the girls !
Hey, Takumi, do you
have a plan ?
Not really.
I'm not that smart that I can change strategies according to my opponent.
It's the same every time.
I'll just drive the
fastest way I know how.
If he's faster
than that, I lose...
...and if he's
slower, I win.
That's true.
But I'm counting on you.
If you defeat
Takahashi Ryosuke...
...you'll be great !
It's so cool, isn't it ?!
I'm so lame.
The White Comet of Akagi !
Welcome !
Oh, Kenji.
I've got something
interesting.
Interesting ?
Could that be that rare
adult video you have ?
Sorry, it's not.
It's even more exciting.
More exciting ?
It's a battle.
It doesn't look like Akina.
Just keep watching.
Hey, let me see
that part again, slower.
I...it's Takahashi Ryosuke !
He looks
a lot younger.
It's a battle from
three years ago.
How did you get this ?
An enthusiast took
a few videos.
Incredible !
Look at that sharp turn-in.
It's the work of a god.
Awesome.
I was in the
gallery at this battle.
It's so nostalgic.
Takahashi Ryosuke didn't belong to any team then, and he drove alone.
He was called the
White Comet of Akagi.
``The White Comet of Akagi...?''
Sounds so cool.
I'm getting excited.
Then, what about the Redsuns ?
He formed the Akagi Redsuns later,
by gathering highly skilled drivers.
So they're all high level, and different from a group of friends like us.
Today, after adding his brother, Keisuke, they became known as the Takahashi Brothers.
But the ``White Comet of Akagi''
still sounds right to me.
What're you guys watching ?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Turn the video off.
No, it's alright.
Let's take a look.
It's incredible.
Takumi is racing
against those guys ?
Yes.
The galleries will be completely packed at the next battle.
Naturally, because
of Takahashi Ryosuke...
...but also because Takumi is famous as the driver of Akina's Eight-Six.
Right.
He's the mysterious downhill specialist
who appeared so suddenly on Akina.
Something like that,
and it's so exciting.
Who do you
think will win ?
Well ?
I'm sorry to say this, but I honestly don't think Takumi has a chance of winning.
He's got a tough
opponent this time.
I think so too.
Takahashi Ryosuke is fast.
Ultra fast.
Is he that fast ?
Yeah, he was way out of our
league even three years ago.
And he's improved his
skills since then.
Not only on
the mountain passes...
...but he's also continuously winning in autocross and circuit racing.
He's rewritten many course records,
and he hasn't been defeated.
His undefeated legend
hasn't been ruined yet.
And they say there hasn't been a race that's made him drive seriously yet.
They say that he can defeat any opponent with just half his skill.
So no one has seen
him driving at his limit.
Well, if Takumi can keep up
with him, that'll be enough.
No...
Here you go with the
pessimistic thoughts again.
Why can't you
be more optimistic ?
Then, who do you
think will win ?
T...Takumi defeated his brother, Keisuke,
and the Night Kids' Nakazato !
He defeated the
Sil-Eighty on Usui !
He also won the gumtape death
match and the rain battle !
I...I think
he can compete.
Ryosuke even outclasses the rest of the highly skilled Redsuns.
He's charismatic.
He's not on the same level
as Keisuke or Nakazato.
Well, if it were a boxing match, the betting would be ten to one, I guess.
I want Takumi to win.
Not only because
he's my friend...
...but also I want my dream car,
the Eight-Six, to outrun the FC !
Don't cry.
Guys like cars,
don't they ?
Yeah.
Are they that great ?
They are. I can
go anywhere I want.
If you were told to choose between your girlfriend and a car, which would you choose ?
I can't compare them.
A girl is a girl,
and cars are cars.
Driving a car
is difficult.
Lately, I've been thinking more about how to drive faster.
I feel good when
I think about it.
Takumi, you're...
...perverted.
What do you mean, saying that I'm perverted so suddenly ?
Sorry, I just felt like it.
It's girl's intuition.
But now I know.
I feel like I know the
secret of your charm.
W...what're you talking about ?
You're not making sense.
It's alright. I don't
think you'd understand.
Geez.
When's the battle ?
The night after tomorrow.
You're going to race against
a very fast person, right ?
Yes.
I want to
see you race.
But I'd better not.
Just don't have an accident.
You can lose, but
don't have an accident.
No matter what.
Promise me ?
Hey, Ryosuke, there's another professional team asking you to join.
They contacted me.
Another one ?
Cool.
Which one ?
That famous
Hoshiya Racing Team.
They're looking for a
promising young driver.
They say they want to see you as soon as possible...
...so they're asking you
to contact them soon.
You'd be very competitive
in professional racing.
I'm excited
just imagining it.
What're you going
to do, Brother ?
Please decline.
As I said before, I have no intention of becoming a professional driver.
You deserve it.
Why don't you at
least listen to them ?
He's right, Ryosuke.
I'm not interested
in professional racing.
Street racing is more interesting because anyone can race freely.
To me, autocross and circuit driving are only processes for mastering the street.
All I care about now is the
Eight-Six this coming Saturday.
Hey, you're closed, right ?
Why don't you come for a drive ?
With you ?
Yeah.
I changed the suspension settings, so I'm going to take it for a test spin.
Take a test spin...?
I don't like the
way you say that.
Hey, Bunta...
Yeah.
Did you change the suspension settings to win the next battle ?
Sort of.
Yuichi, I'm gonna
push it a little.
W...wait.
Okay, but just
for a little.
Here it is.
Here comes the corner.
Incredible entry speed.
Geez, I feel the side G
force from a little aft.
Hey, y...you idiot !
Bunta, what're you doing ?
Well, I feel
like a smoke.
S...stop !
How can you look away ?!
No.
Not bad...
Okay, now I'm gonna
drive seriously.
Let me out !
The engine and suspension tune-ups for winning the next battle are complete.
How much is
it making, Brother ?
Well, it's about
260 horsepower at max.
260 horsepower ?
That means it's
been detuned.
I believe you
had at least 350 hp.
Correct.
You lowered the power.
What's the point
of making it slower ?
You'd better
remember this.
In order to drive fast, sometimes you have to lower the power.
That's the difficulty
of street racing.
The key to mastering the
downhill is total balance.
I tuned my FC to have total balance for both downhill and uphill.
Because I had confidence in handling big power on the downhill...
...I changed the turbine,
and increased the pressure.
But now, I have
to lower the power.
For whatever the reason, this detune is disgraceful for me.
Even if I lose my pride,
I still have to win.
Which means Akina's Eight-Six is that fast, doesn't it ?
I'm glad to have met someone who can make me feel this way.
After such a long time, my
Road Racer blood is boiling.
Follow me.
He's fast.
Although he lowered the power, the exit speed is definitely faster.
He won't lose.
No way he will.
I'm not the Redsuns'
Takahashi Ryosuke now...
...I'm the solo driver, the
White Comet of Akagi...
...Takahashi Ryosuke.
I'll win the battle
no matter what.
Takumi !
Hey !
Race day's here.
Yeah.
I'm frustrated, because everyone says that Takahashi Ryosuke will win.
It's like a match between a champion sumo wrestler and a neophyte.
Aren't you frustrated ?
Don't you have a secret plan
to turn the situation around ?
``Secret plan...?''
Nope.
Road Racers are heading
for the mountain.
It's time.
Manager.
I've cleaned the outside,
so let me call it a day.
Okay, good work. You're going to see the battle tonight, right ?
Yes.
Do you still think
Takumi will lose ?
Yes.
Even if Takumi's a genius,
he's only a high school kid.
He hasn't experienced
that many battles.
I wonder how long he can keep up with Takahashi Ryosuke.
I disagree.
I think he might
be able to win.
Why ?
Because...
Yo.
We're in a hurry,
so excuse us.
Okay.
I have only one reason for thinking that he might be able to win.
Takumi is Bunta's son.
That crazy Bunta.
As I thought, the
galleries are packed.
If I were Takumi,
I'd run away.
I'd be so nervous if I had to race in front of so many people.
That's Usui's Sil-Eighty.
As I thought...
They're both
pretty nice...
Yeah.
Let's see...
I think this is the place.
We should be able to see the battle in a combination of corners.
By the way, Mako...
...which one are
you rooting for ?
Which one...?
The Eight-Six, isn't it ?
Me too.
That Eight-Six has
a mysterious charm.
The charm that can only be felt by those who've raced with him.
Even if you lose, you still
want to support him.
Besides, he's...
...so cute, right ?
Oh, Sayuki.
It's almost 9:30.
It's almost time.
I'm so excited !
Here come the Redsuns.
That's the Takahashi Brothers !
They're so cool !
Yeah, the king
of the streets !
Ryosuke !
Finally, Takahashi
Ryosuke has appeared.
When Takumi appears,
the cast will be complete.
The Eight-Six
isn't here yet.
As usual.
He always shows up at
the very last moment.
Keisuke, I've been thinking
about this for a while.
If I lose on
the street...
...I'll retire.
What're you talking about ?
You won't lose.
Just listen.
That doesn't mean
I'll stop driving.
I'll withdraw from
being top driver.
I'll still be involved with the team in a different way.
What about the Redsun's project
to be the fastest in Kanto ?
If you don't drive,
it'll be impossible.
Don't make such
a pathetic face.
I haven't lost yet.
But I want you to know that there'll be a time for a new generation to take over.
Someday, I'll lose
to someone.
Now that I've said that...
...I can say that I've met two drivers who might defeat me.
One of them
is you, Keisuke.
Me ?
Yes.~~I can sense a
promising talent in you.
You will definitely get faster.
And the other is...
He's come !
Takumi's here !
Hey, Takumi !
Brother, could the other be
the Eight-Six driver ?
I haven't lost
to anyone yet.
Tonight, I'll drive,
drifting at full throttle.
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sake bara no youni akaku
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Kagayaku mirai e
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Kiseki no hana yo
What's wrong, Takumi ?
I've been racing because
the situation called for it.
This time, I feel like
it's a little different.
I'm so excited, but
I don't know what to do.
It's fun and
interesting to drive.
Anyway, I don't know how much I can do, but I want to try my best.
He's different from the usual Takumi.
Takumi is hyped up !
Anyway, I don't know how much I can do, but I want to try my best.
Next time on Initial D:
Initial
Next Time:
Last Great Battle
Don't miss it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org