Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves a lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
No oncoming traffic.
Let's show off, Mako !
Go !
Im...impossible.
We knew that the Eight-Six was extraordinary from the beginning.
I decided this race
would be the last.
So unless we try our best,
I won't be satisfied !
How can you have
gotten so timid ?
You're the worst !~~You're like baggage in the passenger seat !
Baggage ?
Yes, you're only ballast, worsening the power to weight ratio.
She's one of those who changes their personality behind the wheel.
How can you
call me ballast ?
I've got a nice body,
and I'm not chubby or fat !
But you're a
49 kg handicap !
47 kg !
Now that you've said that,
I can't stay quiet.
Let's do it, Mako !
Drive like hell !
That's more like it.
Turn hard, as if you were going to hit the cliff in the next corner.
Okay, Sayuki.
Race-Settling Super Drift
Well, good night, Papa.
Yeah.
Natsuki...
...when will
I see you again ?
I don't know, since school
starts again soon.
Natsuki...
Next corner is sandy,
so stay on the inner edge.
Okay, Sayuki.
No oncoming car.
Drift in the
next corner.
I was distracted by the car behind me and I couldn't drive at my own pace.
Somewhere in my mind, I thought no one could keep up with us.
But I realize now...
There's no way I can drive fast if I watch my rear.
I won't look in the mirror again.
Skid here.
There shouldn't be
many more corners.
I wonder if Takumi
is keeping up with her.
Honestly speaking, I thought
they'd come back right away.
It'll be okay.
Even if he can't overtake them,
he'll outrun them in the second heat.
How could he possibly
overtake them ?
I don't know how
he can keep up.
He chose to be the pursuer on
a course he's never driven.
It started. Great.
I'm Sato Mako.
Call me.
I'm very sorry.
For my memory
of this summer...
...would you let me race against Akina's Eight-Six on the Usui mountain pass ?
That's my wish.
If you make my
wish come true...
...you can have
my virginity.
Iketani...
What ?
How come you
look out of it ?
You must be
thinking about Mako.
It shows on your face.
I...I'm not...
You don't have to lie.
Mako is a nice girl.
I agree with you.
Kenji...
I don't know what happened, but you should go after her again after this battle.
She's too good to
give up on so easily.
It's okay.
Drift here.
A car's coming, but you'll pass it in the third corner...
...so don't worry now
and go full throttle.
Okay, Sayuki.
Next one,
the car'll appear.
Some people are racing.
I want to see.
You can tell how good they are by watching how they drive the downhill.
I...incredible...
Bingo.
Sayuki never misses
oncoming cars.
She never misses the headlights, which reflect off the leaves several corners away.
Grip !~~Get close
to the inside !
Great, Mako.
This is more like you.
Drift all the
way and clear it.
No oncoming car,
so drift.
Incredible.
She's dangerously good.
Skilled Road Racers always keep a slight margin of safety.
They appear to be
driving at the limit...
...but they use the full gripping potential of the tires only at the exits.
They save the tires when braking and at the turn-in.
Because one mistake means crashing on the street with no escape zone.
But...
...she doesn't have
that margin right now.
Her tension is so high
that she hasn't noticed it.
I wonder if I should tell
her about it or not.
It's my role
to tell her, but...
I've decided...
I shouldn't disturb her while she's driving so well.
I've made up my mind.
We're the best partners, so I'll believe in your skill, Mako.
You're driving better
than ever before.
Damn, what an entry.
She increased her pace.
If she goes any faster,
I'll reach my limit first.
Even now, I'm using the
full potential of the tires.
Damn, I can't...?
Wings of fire, tsubasa ni koi no honoo nosete
Wings of fire. We let our wings carry our passion for love.
Higher.
Wings of fire jiyuu ni hateshinaku takaku tobu
Wings of fire. We fly high so freely.
Koe wo kiku dakede kimochi ga ochitsuku
I feel relieved just by hearing your voice.
Fudangi no futari ga naniyori mo uresii yo
We appreciate each other for unchanged behavior.
Togireta rail no ue samayoi tsuzuketeta hibi mo
There were days we wandered on a broken rail.
Kotae wa mabusikatta kesshite te wo hanasanai
The answer seemed so bright, and we'll never let our holding hands go.
Wings of fire, tsubasa ni koi no honoo nosete
Wings of fire. We let our wings carry our passion for love.
Higher.
Wings of fire, jyuu ni hateshinaku takaku tobu
Wings of fire. We fly high so freely.
Wings of fire, futari wa speed ageteyuku
Wings of fire. The two of us pick up speed.
**************
If you can't outrun him, there'll be no place to settle the race.
I know.
Wings of fire, hirogaru kono sora wo kakemeguru
Wings of fire. We fly around in the open sky.
**************
No oncoming car, so take
it at your best pace.
The Eight-Six slowed down.
Why ?
No, Mako !
Your entry speed's too fast !
No, you can't recover !
Just spin to stop !
This is bad !
Please, get by !
We're safe.
Splendid.
I admit our
total defeat.
He's incredible.
He's got much better range.
How do you feel ?
Even though we lost...
...I'm completely satisfied.
I recalled those exciting feelings from when we started racing.
We were obsessed with
driving until daybreak.
The pure feeling
from those days...
We crossed the limit, but you
were wonderful till that moment.
It's the best driving
I've ever seen from you.
Sayuki...
So, I'll leave
it up to you, Mako.
You can do
as you like.
Thanks, Sayuki.
No, no tears.~~I'm so happy to have had a great race.
They're back !
I...I wonder how the
first heat turned out.
Are they going to
start the second run ?
Takumi !
Takumi, I can't believe
this myself, but...
There won't be a second
heat, will there, Takumi ?
No second run.
Once was enough.
I thought so.
Even though
it was Takumi...
No, I didn't want
to see Takumi lose.
We lost.
W...what did you say ?
What did you just say ?
Don't make me say
that we lost again.
He won.
He did it !
Honestly speaking, we didn't think we could lose on our home course.
I just kept following you
so I wouldn't get outrun...
...so I don't
think I won.
You don't have
to be so modest.
You should be proud of yourself, because you have such wonderful skill.
But...
We've driven here so often,
we were very confident.
But we couldn't
outrun a visitor.
So that means we
lost, right, Mako ?
Mako...
It was a wonderful race.
Thank you.
He's so shy.
He's strange.
He's totally superior in controlling a car,
but he's so reserved in other things.
He's like this all the time.
He acts so stupid.
Almost like he's always asleep,
except for driving a car.
How can you say that ?
It's true.
But how can you be
so good at your age ?
Why don't you go after her again, after the race ?~~She's too good to give up on so easily.
Iketani.
T...thanks for tonight.
Mako, I...I...
Iketani, don't
be depressed.
Road Racers don't
need a girl, right ?
R...right.
When I look closely, he's got
my favorite kind of cute face.
Hey, what's your name ?
Fujiwara Takumi...
Takumi and I'm Itsuki.
Eighteen years old.
My sign is Leo, and my blood type is O.  My favorite car is...
I'm not asking you.
By the way, why don't we go to the pool together for friendship ?
Sounds good, sounds good.
Kenji...?
You'll go, right, Takumi ?!
And you of
course, Iketani ?!
Great !
Thank you
so much, Sayuki !
It's a promise !
This is great !
I'll go in my Eight-Five !
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
************************
Song: ``Wings of Fire''
A duet by Mako and Sayuki
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
Kagayaku mirai e
...into the bright future.
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Let's make it sure over and over.
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
This passion will be eternal.
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku dakishimete
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
Kiseki no hana yo
The flower of miracles.
Iketani, you have to
be true to yourself.
Otherwise, humanity would've
been extinct by now.
You're right, Manager.
But the first time is very important.
For the first time, don't...
Oh...dear ?
I'm just leaving.
Are you going home, Manager ?
What did you mean by
``For the first time, don't...?''
Next time on Initial D:
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org