Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information spread out in a matter of second.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love"...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
The galleries are packed.
It looks like there're more people here than during the match against the FD.
That means the battle between Takumi and Nakazato of the Night Kids...
...has attracted
a lot of attention.
What should I do ?
I'm feeling even more depressed.
The mood won't allow us to simply say it was a mistake.
Takumi...
...please come !
Just Before the Time Attack!
Shit.
Where did that
stupid old man go ?
Do you think
you could win ?
I'd win. Whether it's a 32
or not makes no difference.
Do you think
I could win ?
I know that you didn't
accept the battle.
I'm telling you. You'd better stay away from the 32.
Takumi, the opponent is a 32, so even if you don't race, no one will think you ran away.
Run away ?!
The Night Kids are here !
It's Nakazato
with his 32.
It looks so powerful.
That black 32 deserves to
be the king of the street.
So they're
the Night Kids.
There're so
many of them.
S...Senpai, if we're going to apologize, the sooner the better !
Yeah, but...
We still have time.
Let's go
and ask him.
I don't think it's a good idea to drag him to a hopeless battle.
We won't know
unless we try.
It's impossible. You'll understand if you cool down and think.
The opponent
is a 32.
The power is totally different, and it's got 4WD ATTESA E-TS.
I thought so at
the beginning...
...but since I got here,
I started to believe.
The Eight-Six would have no
chance on the circuit...
...but this is
a mountain pass.
Since Takumi has been driving here for five years, we don't know what'll happen.
When Takumi drives, the
Eight-Six becomes extraordinary.
It turns into a super machine
with infinite potential.
Because I rode next
to him, I can tell.
His driving is
beyond our imagination.
Oh, the incident of that frightening downhill with you screaming.
And you passed out
in the third corner.
His downhill driving
is that different.
And there's one more person
who feels the same way.
W...who's that ?
There's one more person who
has seen his driving up close.
That's...
Yes...
It's Takahashi Keisuke
of the Redsuns.
The Takahashi
brothers are here !
Now that the stars are on stage, I'm getting so excited !
Keisuke !
Ryosuke !
You're so cool !
They're good looking,
so they attract girls.
Damn, only skill should make
a Road Racer popular.
We can't defeat
them in any way.
And they're rich.
I knew they'd show up.
I'm looking forward
to the battle.
I'll prove who's the best
in the Gunma Prefecture.
It's not the Eight-Six
or the Takahashi brothers...
...it's me, Nakazato Takeshi
of the Night Kids.
Asshole...
The Eight-Six hasn't
shown up yet.
I'll have to go
and convince Takumi.
Get in.
What's wrong, Itsuki ?
I'll stay, Iketani.
I can't face Takumi.
I see.
Wait until the
last moment, okay ?
I'll bring Takumi,
no matter what.
He will...
Takumi will come.
Besides...
...I like this place.
I'm getting
used to this.
Oh, dear Ryosuke.
Why...
I'm frustrated to death.
I want to go to
Mt. Akina so much.
I don't know if I like
to drive that much or not.
But I've been driving alone for five years, whether it was snowing or raining.
I've driven Akina
more than anyone.
I want to test
how good I am.
I want to challenge the
GT-R with all my skill.
I've never felt
this way before.
I'm not giving up, even
though I don't have a car.
Instead, my desire to
drive is getting stronger.
Dammit, Dad.
Where're you
wandering around ?
Takumi.
Iketani...
Say what ?
Your dad left with the car,
and hasn't come back ?
Yeah.
Don't you know
where he is ?
I thought he'd be at a bar, so I called all the places I could think of.
And you couldn't
get a hold of him.
The Eight-Six isn't here and
we can't even persuade you !
This is unexpected.
Senpai, you came
to persuade me ?
Yeah.
The mountain
is in an uproar.
Nakazato of the Night Kids and the Takahashi brothers are entertaining the galleries.
But you're
today's main attraction.
Wait a minute.
Please, don't.
No matter what you say,
I can't do anything.
You won't change
your mind, will you.
I don't mean that.
Actually, I was
going to go.
What ?!
But without a car,
I can't do anything.
I've been so depressed,
sitting here alone.
How could this be...?!
It's so frustrating.
Without a car...
That's it.
Hey, Takumi, what about
borrowing Kenji's 180 ?
That's a good idea !
It's got the same FR layout, and it has a turbo, so it's more powerful !
If you drive it,
it'll run fast !
I don't think so.
Why not ?
I don't want to drive
someone else's car.
It has to be a car
I'm familiar with.
That's true.
It's not a good thing among Road Racers to drive someone else's car.
I'll wait as long as I can.
That's all I can do.
It's 9:45.
I guess they
didn't make it.
He's late.
What time is it ?
Almost 10:00.
We aren't
gonna make it.
Where are you, Dad ?
Please, come home.
We don't have time.
He's back.
That rhythm of revving up twice when turning from the interstate...
...that sound...
Dad's coming home.
You can tell by just listening to the exhaust sound ?
Is that really your car ?
I can tell.
I'm positive.
The Takahashi
brothers are here.
Yeah, they can't
ignore this.
He told me that
I'd be defeated.
That Takahashi Ryosuke is known for logical thinking, but he doesn't seem that good.
I'll defeat the Eight-Six in front of him, and humiliate him.
Let's do it.
If you're faster than the Eight-Six, which defeated Takahashi Keisuke...
We're faster
than the Redsuns.
It's a good opportunity to let those galleries know one thing.
Drift driving can't
defeat grip driving.
It's your favorite phrase.
Of course.
Drift is just a performance to excite the galleries.
It's not a technique
to race with.
That sounds just
like you, Takeshi.
When I was driving the 13,
I learned drift, so I can tell.
When the master of drift uses a grip technique, he can drive even faster.
It was shocking when you
were defeated by that 32.
Sorry, I wasn't
supposed to say that.
I was changed
at that moment.
I switched to the 32, the monster that defeated me, and my skill improved.
Who can call a person a Road Racer if he doesn't pursue better driving ?
All everyone talks about is drift, drift, and thinks highly of those drivers.
I can't stand that.
Come on, Eight-Six.
Drifting with the FR layout
is old hat. I'll prove that.
As usual, he isn't showing
up until the last minute.
Do you think he'll
really show up ?
He said he wasn't
interested, didn't he ?
No, he'll be here.
I'm sure of it.
He'll definitely
be here.
Well, that's what this is all about, so let me use the car, Dad.
You'd better hurry, Takumi.
It's almost time.
Sorry, but I'm
borrowing Takumi.
When we return,
I'll buy ten fried tofu.
I'll buy ganmodoki, too.
W...wait.
Takumi's eyes
looked different.
What's going on ?
Oh well, he'll be able to race evenly with that setting.
The mountain pass is close. I wonder if you can keep up with him, Kenji.
Oh, come on, Iketani.
That's a 1.6 liter non-turbo.
I've got a
2.0 liter turbo.
I'm not sure about the downhill, but if he pulls away on the uphill, I'll lose face.
I'm one of the top
three of the Speedstars.
He's so fast.
Me too !
Exit the corner,
then full acceleration !
He's gone.
The Eight-Six has vanished.
Takumi was also looking away in the entrance ceremony picture.
Two more minutes
till 10:00 pm.
I guess they
didn't make it.
I'd better give
up and apologize.
No, Iketani told me to wait.
If I go off on my own again...
But it was my fault, and it has nothing to do with the Speedstars.
I'd better prepare for
one or two punches...
There are so
many of them !
I don't think I'll be forgiven
with only a punch or two !
No way.
I want to run away.
They won't forgive me easily
if the Eight-Six doesn't show up.
Even if I kneel to the ground, they won't forgive me. I might be killed.
Father, Mother, help me.
Please, God.
I've never slept with a girl,
and I don't wanna die !
There !
There he is !
No.
They found me.
I can't even run away.
I'll be killed.
What're you doing, Itsuki,
sitting in the middle of the road ?
T...T...T...
You're in my way.
I'm gonna run over you.
Takumi, you came !
Yeah.
Sorry I'm late, Itsuki.
Takumi...
Road Racers have to accept
challenges, don't they ?
Takumi...
Stop it !
Hey, Itsuki !
That's more like it.
This is Fujiwara
Tofu Shop.
Oh, it's you, Yuichi.
You're there ?
I don't know
what's going on.
He wanted to go to
the mountain himself.
Like father, like son.
Besides, Bunta, tonight's
opponent is a GT-R.
Honestly speaking, do you think he has a chance of winning ?
The Eight-Six finally showed up.
Keisuke, he came as you predicted.
Yeah.
Weren't you going to tell him the weakness of the 32 ?
I was going to,
but I decided not to.
After seeing his face,
I started hating him.
He's my enemy,
after all.
Besides...
...even if he doesn't know
its weakness, he won't lose.
Did you give
him any advice ?
Not really.
Even if it's the GT-R,
it has its weakness.
The weakness of
the 32 is...
...the weight
of the body.
Understeering due to the
super heavy front load.
Suspension tuning and driving technique can't change its fundamental characteristics.
After pushing hard on the downhill, the front tires and brakes will weaken.
Even if the
brakes are tuned...
...by the time he reaches the base of the mountain...
...he has to cope with understeering at the corners' entrances.
His chance of winning lies at the entrance of the corners in the second half.
The key point
of this battle...
...is whether the Eight-Six can keep up with the 32 until then or not.
I changed the suspension setting of the Eight-Six a little.
The suspension ?
How ?
Heavy understeering when
the gas pedal is open.
What ?!
Heavy understeering ?!
Drift is Takumi's style.
What's on your mind, Bunta ?
Will he be able to keep up with the GT-R with that setting ?
Don't you get it, Yuichi ?
If the driver is skilled...
...he can depress the accelerator harder when it comes to the FR layout.
He has to deliver tofu, so the setting is usually compromised a little bit.
He can open the throttle
longer with the current setting.
If the driver
is skilled...
...I'm sure he
can handle it.
My pride says "You gatta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make a room.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin my dream.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safe zone.
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
:Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
{Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down on the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logics...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
Tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
Nakazato, how's your chance of winning against the Eight-Six ?
Psheesh.
It's so obvious.
So, the 32 will win.
But Takahashi Ryosuke...
He's hesitant because his brother was defeated.
I'll show them that I'm
the fastest in Gunma...
...and grip driving is superior.
He'll just be eating my dust.
What's that ``psheesh ?''
It's only action, action !
Next time on Initial D,
``The Battle to the Limit.''
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org