Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information spread out in a matter of second.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love"...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
I was suddenly bumped
from behind in a corner.
That asshole
did it again.
Shit.
I'll do it !
Whether it's a gumtape death match or not, I'll do it !
Takumi, wait !
Takumi...
Sorry.
Don't be taken
in by his strategy !
A gumtape death match
is too dangerous !
Don't do it, Takumi !
I won't lose,
no matter what.
Improving Genius of Drift !
Welcome.
Welcome.~~Please move
the car over here.
High octane or regular ?
Welcome.
Need your
ashtray cleaned ?
Takumi's going to accept
the gumtape death match ?
That's bad,
extremely bad.
He got pissed because
Itsuki was hospitalized.
I understand how he feels,
but it's still too reckless.
It's Saturday.
Where's Takumi ?
He took the day off.
With Itsuki in the hospital,
we're super busy.
No matter how good Takumi is, accepting a gumtape death match without practice...
I'll talk to
Takumi after work.
I have to
stop him somehow.
Sorry, but can you help
us out for a while ?
Welcome !
``If you lose your sense of duty to a friend, our society will come to an end.''
It's natural for
Takumi to feel that way.
I don't think
he'll listen.
Maybe we should
let him try.
No, he's at too much of a
disadvantage against an FF car.
I'm so surprised you called.
It's the first time you've called me.
A lot of things
made me mad.
After thinking about so many things,
I started thinking of you.
I felt like
I could relax.
I'm glad you did.
How are Itsuki's injuries ?
He was wearing
his seat belt.
It's not as bad
as it looks...
...but he has to go through a lot of checkups, so he has to stay in the hospital.
I'd better
go see him.
Yeah, he'll
appreciate that.
You look a little scary today.
Sorry.
You're not yourself.
But I like
you this way, too.
Takahashi
Brother !
What's up ?
Akina's Eight-Six...
...is going to have a gumtape death match against the Night Kids number two driver !
What ?
Moreover, the
opponent is an EG6.
What the hell
is he thinking ?
The gumtape death match is
a trap to kill FR cars.
It's only common sense that
an FR won't defeat an FF.
Common sense, yes...
But he's the driver.
If he drives, he'll blow mere common sense out the window.
What should we do ?
Should we go ?
Excuse me.
I'm closing the store.
I already sold out of
fried tofu and ``ganmo.''
We didn't come
for that today.
Do you know
where Takumi is ?
Takumi ?
No idea.
He took the Eight-Six this afternoon,
and he hasn't come home.
I don't know
where he went.
Sir, have you ever tried a gumtape death match before ?
Yeah, a long time ago.
What if Takumi tried it ?
Takumi...?
I don't know.
He's not very good, so he might end up at the bottom of the valley.
Iketani, let's go
look somewhere else.
Okay.
Sir, if he returns, tell him not to do the gumtape death match.
Excuse me.
Gumtape death match, huh ?
Shingo, let's get going.
Yeah.
Wait for me,
Eight-Six of Akina.
There's no way
I can lose.
Your Eight-Six will be
smashed into Akina's cliff.
Well, see you.
Call me again, okay ?
Sure.
Now then...
So many people
are here already.
I don't like
them around here.
We came here
to stop Takumi.
Here come the Night Kids !
Oh, only the
slow S13 dude ?
What happened to
the Eight-Six ?
Ignore him.
I wonder when
Takumi will get here.
Shit.
He's gonna be here soon,
it's almost time.
Here comes
Akina's Eight-Six !
Fujiwara Tofu Shop...?
Is this some
kind of joke ?
Takumi, it's not too late.
Don't race in such a
ridiculous battle as this.
Why not ?
I won't lose to
a guy like him.
He's driving an FF car.
Don't you get it ?
Oh, the kid from
the other day...
You're wasting my time.
What're you
talking about ?
Don't tell me you're
thinking about pulling out.
Iketani, I won't
quit, no matter what.
It's almost ten.
It's about time to begin.
Takumi, I believe in you.
You will win.
Please win !
I wonder if
he'll be okay.
Maybe we should've
forced him to stop.
All we can do now
is trust him.
It's okay.
The finish is ready.
Shall we start ?
Okay.
I'm counting down.
Ten seconds.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go !
It's begun.
Don't push too hard, Takumi.
Shingo intentionally laid off the accelerator and stayed behind.
So that he can watch the Eight-Six fall from a cliff, right ?
Only a genius can avoid an accident in an FR under these rules.
That Eight-Six won't
reach the third corner.
Don't get
too confident.
The B16A engine
is a masterpiece.
If I'd been serious, that dated 4AG engine couldn't have outrun me during the start dash.
Let me see how many
corners you can clear.
But is it really possible to turn with one hand taped to the steering wheel ?
There they are !
Hey, the Eight-Six looks
like it's going too fast !
This is bad !
He seems slower than usual.
You seem quite eager, but aren't you forgetting something ?
There you go.
You're finished.
I made it.~~How lucky.
I thought the tendon in
my arm was about to snap.
H...he recovered.
Incredible !~~I thought
he was done for !
I can't watch.
Hey, hey, hey, where
did all your pep go ?
I can't just stand here.
Let's follow them.
T...there's no way, Iketani !
We can't catch them with our skill !
I'm not thinking
about catching them.
If Takumi is involved in
an accident and gets hurt...
...we have to help him
as quickly as possible !
Hey, I'm coming with you !
I see.~~I've got this
battle figured out.
Shit, how can he...?
He's clearing corners with
minimum countersteering...
I don't believe it.
The gumtape death match can't be mastered on the first try.
The more conservative you drive, the greater the chance you'll fall into a pit.
I practiced so many times keeping my hand on the steering wheel...
...before I could turn into the corner with tape on.
In a long straightaway,
engine power is more significant.
When it comes to a normally aspirated 1.6-liter DOHC engine...
...no engine in the world
can surpass the B16A.
The ecstasy at the sound of the engine revving up rapidly into the red zone...
I'd die for it.
It's awesome.
Do you get it ?~~If I feel like it, I can pass you anytime I want.
Hey, hey, you'd
better hurry.
Why don't you
drive harder ?
My heart pounds every
time I clear a corner.
I'm afraid I'll see
a wrecked Eight-Six.
Quit saying that,
it'll bring bad luck.
As long as
nothing happens...
Yeah.
Besides, Takumi's
potential is surprising.
I can clear corners
at my desired speed.
The car can go faster
if I don't steer too much.
Shit, why doesn't my
pressure disturb him ?
At the beginning,
he was driving unsteadily...
...but his driving is getting sharper and sharper, as if he's a different driver.
Here they come.
They're close.
I guess they've
both survived so far.
If he couldn't get this far,
my expectations were too high.
Then the Eight-Six wouldn't
deserve to be my target.
There !
Oh shit, someone's
coming up !
Four wheel drift within the lane without crossing the centerline...?!
What incredible technique !
And he pulled
it off so easily.
He wasn't even fazed
by the oncoming car.
Is his hand still taped ?
Has it come off already ?
I think he figured out
this death match very early.
Which means...
You don't have to
depend on steering...
...you can also clear a corner
by shifting the weight.
He learned it quickly.
Man, what a guy !
He's definitely improved.
Shit, this is
totally unexpected.
Now that he's made it this far, I have to accept that it's not just luck.
But I'm not as
easy as Takeshi.
As long as I win,
I don't care how.
Don't blame me.
The Eight-Six of Akina will simply turn to scraps of metal in a junkyard.
Unbelievable !
After he spun out, he turned 360 degrees, and kept going as if nothing happened !
Damn, it's gotta be luck.
It must be coincidence.
Shit.
If it were a high speed corner,
it would've been finished.
It doesn't matter.
I'll win this battle.
It's a bummer that
I couldn't trash it...
...but I won't lose if it's a speed match, because I'm familiar with this rule.
I'll just outrun you.
Now I'm pissed.
He did that on purpose.
I won't lose to a lowlife like you, no matter what !
My pride says "You gatta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make a room.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin my dream.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safe zone.
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
:49:07.15 0:49:10.09 CF1 Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down on the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logics...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
Tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
I won't forgive him,
no matter what.
I won't lose,
Who is it ?
Takumi ?
I won't forgive him,
no matter what.
I won't lose,
no matter what !
Now, to continue.
Next time on Initial D:
``Angry Takumi's Maniacal Drive !''
I won't lose.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org