Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shita kemuri
Silver smoke in a freezing city...
misugita yume no daisyou
...that's the cost of having an unachievable dream.
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi
A frozen body and unforgettable desire...
accel funde gomakasu
You deceive yourself by stepping on the accelerator.
Yoru ni kowareta mama shisen tsuyoku togarasete
Although depressed in the night, your eyes are kept sharply open.
Dareno kimagure kara sekai sae mo owarisoude
You feel like someone's careless act could end the world.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Obieta me wo shite lost in the night
Lost in the night with frightened eyes...
ochiteku yume ni dakareru
Embraced by a ruined dream.
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart
Scared of loneliness, I'm missing you in my heart.
jibun sae mo kizu tsukete
I almost hurt myself.
Taoreru kurai ni love me so much
Love me so much and knock me out.
subete wo suttee anata wo
If only I can give up everything...
Ai suru koto sae dekitara
...and love you...
kitto sunao ni naresou
...I can be my true self.
Kenji, I'm so
happy to be here.
Itsuki...
...it's wonderful
and gorgeous.
Takumi !
Come over here, and
let's go swimming together.
Well, I...
Okay, we're coming !
What's wrong ?
Hurry !
We're coming !
I'm so happy to
be here, Itsuki !
Senpai...
The End of Summer
You're coming,
right, Iketani ?!
What's wrong ?
Isn't this fun ?
S...sure it is.
Hey, Takumi, let's
go try the Slider.
I...I'll just stay and relax...
Well, he's always out of it.
If you don't mind
us going too...
Okay, let's all
go together.
Together, together !
Alright, let's go.
Okay, Takumi, let's go !
Well, I don't
like the Slider...
How can someone who can do such a super drift say that ?
Sayuki's so forceful,
and she's always like that.
I guess it's okay.
Is it okay for everyone
to take the day off ?
We begged to take
a paid vacation day.
The manager didn't
look too happy though.
She's so bright.
My heart is
almost bursting.
At least I've gotten to see
her in a bathing suit...
...so this'll be the greatest memory of my 21st summer of life.
I'll never forget it.
After all, Mako
is beyond my reach.
Iketani...
Thank you for
many things.
I need to thank
you for a lot.
I learned a lot
from that race.
Mako...
I caused you a lot of trouble, but I won't quit racing.
Really ?
That's great.
I didn't want
you to quit.
After all, I got conceited because they put the label of Usui's fastest on us.
No, you can't recover !
Just spin to stop !
I realized that I needed to learn a lot more about controlling a car.
If I quit racing now,
I'd leave something unfinished.
I'm glad
to hear that.
So something good came
out of what I did.
Iketani...
Do you remember the promise we made by the lake ?
You might have misunderstood because of the way I put it...
...but I wasn't trying
to make a deal.
I want you to
be my first man.
I'll be waiting for you in front of the signboard where we first met around 8:00 pm.
Slow down.
So cute !
I feel her breasts
on my back.
I...I feel something
on my back...
So pathetic.
Mako, get the ball !
Please !
Takahashi Ryosuke !
Ready, Sayuki ?
Here.
Where're you throwing it ?
Sorry, sorry.
I missed.
Why does she have a picture of Takahashi Ryosuke ?
Something wrong ?
No.
Umm...
Can I ask
you something ?
Sure.
You said you've
never had a boyfriend.
Right.
Even if you haven't...
...you've had a crush
or something, right ?
Y...yeah...
I wonder why you can't
go out with that guy.
Most guys would be attracted
to you because of your looks.
Impossible.
That'll never happen.
What kind of
man is he ?
He's a Road Racer.
It was when I was still in high school, so it was about three years ago...
Some senior schoolmates took me to watch a race.
I didn't know anything
at that time...
...but the way one car
went by shocked me.
His driving looked clearly different from the others, even to my amateur eyes.
I was shocked by this unknown world, and I was fascinated by the world of Road Racers.
I got my license right after that,
and then I worked hard to buy a car.
I practiced so hard...
...so that I would be
able to get close to him.
My motivation sounds silly.
I've gone to see his
driving quite often.
But I've never
talked to him.
So, I don't know if
I can call it love.
I don't know whether
I liked him or his driving.
But you liked him.
Yes...
...I liked him so much.
What is this pain ?
Damn, I shouldn't
have asked.
She seems
so far away.
So her crush was on the
superstar of the Gunma area...
...Takahashi Ryosuke.
Now I know why
she likes FCs.
I can't.
I'm no match for him.
Finally, my brother has decided to race against Akina's Eight-Six.
Are you coming
with me, Keisuke ?
I'll show you my hypothesis
for the fastest driving.
Brother...
I enjoyed it so much !
I never knew going to the pool with girls was this fun !
Right, Takumi ?
But you were with Kenji
almost all the time.
Mako and Sayuki are
great, aren't they ?
Your recovery is quick.
You used to say that Road Racers don't need girls.
They're different.
Itsuki !
I can still see those
two in their bikinis !
It was awesome !
Sayuki's bouncy boobs are amazing,
but it's Mako after all...
She's got a knockout bod,
don't you think, Iketani ?
Yeah, true.
Something's wrong
with your reaction.
You look blue.
Did you fight
with Mako ?
No, I didn't.
I'm just tired.
Oh, what's the matter
at this time of night ?
Sorry about today.
I asked too much of you.
Oh, it's okay.
You're young, so you
need to have some fun.
I'd be worried if you were only into cars and didn't have a girlfriend.
Good luck, okay ?
Mako is your angel, right ?
Is it going well ?
I guess not.
She's beyond my
reach after all.
Don't be so discouraged.
Listen, Iketani,
girls are...
It's okay, Manager.
I've already given up.
I'm no match for
Takahashi Ryosuke.
What do you mean ?
What's happened ?~~I'm barely
keeping up with him.
His FC hasn't
been changed, so why ?
My hypothesis for the fastest driving is refined every time I get new data.
Wait for me,
Eight-Six of Akina.
As soon as I've completed it, I'll put your name on the list of losers.
I arrived before he did.
My chest feels tight.
My heart is pounding.
If I'm like this now, I don't know what I'll do when Iketani shows up.
What did you say ?
Are you stupid
or what, Iketani ?
You don't know
anything about girls.
Eh ?
Don't give me ``Eh !''
Think !
If she was actually going out with Takahashi Ryosuke, you'd be out of luck...
...but young girls have those kinds of feelings, you know ?
It's no different than
dreaming about TV stars.
Cool down, and think.
Because she chose you
over Takahashi Ryosuke...
...she took courage and
made up her mind.
Because she believes in you,
she told you how she feels.
Don't you get it ?
Don't let your inferiority
complex hold you back !
To love someone means to
accept everything about her !
That's what loving and caring
is all about, isn't it ?
What ?!
Eight o'clock ?!
Idiot, you're thirty
minutes late already !
It's impossible.
It'll take at least one hour to get to Yokokawa no matter how fast I drive.
I don't think
she'll be waiting.
Shut up and go !
You won't know
unless you go !
If you don't go,
I'll fire you !
Drive like hell.
If you're a Road Racer, this is the time to drive like hell.
But having said that, I don't
think he can make it.
Well, I guess that's
part of being young.
The manager is right.
How could I be so stupid ?
I'll never have another chance to meet someone like Mako.
Why couldn't
I be honest ?
I'm Sato Mako.~~Call me.
I'll give you
my virginity.
I'll be waiting for you in front of the signboard where we first met around 8:00 pm.
Mako is always
serious, but I...I...
I'm so stupid !
My feet hurt.
I hate sandals.
Mako, I'm not expecting to go to a hotel or anything.
Well, actually...
No. I just want
to see her face.
Please, God, give me
one more chance.
Don't take my angel
away from my world.
Traffic jam ?
An accident in a
place like this ?
No, God, this
is so cruel !
Sorry, Mako.
I got no impression.
This town's made by imitation.
Wanting your sensation.
I'll never wear sandals again.
In this silly simulation...
I wanna rage my dream.
I got no impression grey no kanjo
I got no motivation. Grey feeling.
bokashi mo iresugi machijyuu wa imitation
Shaded off too much, the city is an imitation.
real wo motomete takaburu anata ga
You are desperate in seeking for reality.
chikaku ni yorenai hodo atsukunaru
You get so excited that I can't come close.
Feel your frustration anata no sakebi wo
I feel your frustration and hear your shout.
Taste your vibration furueru hodo ni kanjiteru
I sense your vibration. I feel it so strongly that it shakes me.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang another round, never slow down.
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down on the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logics...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream. tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
Rage your dream. In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream. Ima wo ikiteiru
Rage your dream. You live in the present.
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sake bara no youni akaku
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Kagayaku mirai e
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Kiseki no hana yo
What's up with
that bouquet, Takumi ?!
Well...
Oh, they're
from Natsuki !
No...
I know !
To the previously unknown
Gunma area racing star...
...Takumi in the Fujiwara
Tofu Shop panda Trueno...
...from some girl
in the gallery !
That's not it...
Oh, then it's from Sayuki !
She's still after you !
No...
They were sent by
Takahashi Ryosuke.
Huh ?
Initial
Next Time:
The Challenge from the Superstar
Don't miss it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org