Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shita kemuri...
...misugita yume no daisyou.
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi.
Accel funde gomakasu.
Yoru ni kowareta mama shisen tsuyoku togarasete.
Dareno kimagure kara sekai sae mo owarisoude.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Obieta me wo shite lost in the night.
Ochiteku yume ni dakareru.
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart.
Jibun sae mo kizu tsukete.
Taoreru kurai ni love me so much.
Subete wo suttee anata wo...
...ai suru koto sae dekitara...
...kitto sunao ni naresou.
Is there a good cure to save Takumi from his lovesickness ?
Today's Friday, so September 15th
is still a week away.
We're lucky that
it's not tomorrow.
By the way, there's a race between the Redsuns and the Myogi Night Kids.
That's it !
We'll drag Takumi out there,
and watch the battle !
He'll be stimulated
and recover !
That's a good idea !
That's it !
Why don't we knock him out and save him from his lovesickness.
Severe Hill Climb
Hey, Dad,
I've been thinking.
What is it ?
I drove on Mt. Usui
the other day.
At first, I thought Usui was totally different from Akina.
But...I don't know
how to say this...
They seemed almost the same after I started driving.
Well done.
``Well done ?''
Akina and Usui are
totally different...
...but you simply drove
in the same manner.
You tried what you do on
Akina in a different place.
Well, take care
of the delivery.
Yeah.
Try what I do on
Akina in other places...
I know what you
meant to say...
...just a little.
I'd better take a
nap when I get home.
Takumi looks totally bored.
Alright, it's the time
to proceed with the plan.
Hey, Takumi !
Takumi !
Hey, big news.
Don't be surprised !
The Redsuns and Night Kids are racing !
And it's tonight !
Wha...?
Don't give me ``wha,''
will you ?!
You're racing against
Takahashi Ryosuke next week...
...so you shouldn't
miss this.
Right ?
Alright, we've decided.
And it'd be a waste of gas
to go in two cars...
...so we'll go in
your Eight-Six ?
My...
I'm so excited !
Aren't you excited ?!
I'll be at the usual place at
seven o'clock tonight...
...so make sure you borrow
the Eight-Six, okay ?!
As I thought,
there're so many people.
Have you seen
Takumi and Itsuki ?
No.~~I guess they
aren't here yet.
I let Itsuki handle it, but I'm worried if they'll make it.
What're you doing, Takumi ?
It's gonna start soon.
Since you didn't want to take the highway, we got lost.
You're so stingy.
What're you talking about ?
You wanted to save gas and
didn't drive your Eight-Five.
Man, I've never heard of a Road Racer who's bad at directions.
It must be
because of a girl.
Okay, I got it.
Hurry, we don't
have much time.
I've been waiting.
The hero always
arrives late.
Myogi's valley is deep.
You'd better be concerned
about your life.
Can it.~~Aren't you
shaking from fear ?
I'll defeat
you so easily.
No one in the Night
Kids can match me.
I hope your overconfidence
doesn't kill you.
We'd better start
before the rain comes.
Right.
The Eight-Six !
It's Akina's Eight-Six !
The Eight-Six ?
Wow, look at all the
people in the galleries...
First, let's
find those two.
I know.~~Since there are
so many people, it's tough.
Where should we
park the car ?
Should we go to the peak ?  There's a big parking lot there.
Okay.~~I'll head for
the peak for now.
So he's come after all.
It excites me whether
I like it or not.
Eight-Six...
...I'll show you how
much I've improved.
It's the Eight-Six.
From Akina ?
Yeah.
So, that's the one.
Hey, Takumi,
I noticed earlier.
Don't you think
they're watching us ?
Dunno...
``Dunno...?''
We really stand out...
...because Akina's
Eight-Six is famous.
Everyone thinks
so highly of you.
I was right about
coming in the Eight-Six.
What're you talking about ?
Alright.
~~~Forward.
Alright, alright.
Okay.
No oncoming traffic.
Starting the countdown !
Five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one.
Go !
What an incredible
rocket start.
Keisuke'll win.
I know it.
Don't lose.  We can't disgrace ourselves by losing on our home course.
Takahashi
It's begun.
Rain...
The FD's greatest advantage
is its manueverability.
Don't forget that, Keisuke.
Hey, Takumi, don't you think Myogi's
passes are similar to Akina's ?
Are they ?
I'd say that they
remind me of Usui.
What ?!
They're nothing like it.
It's no use. His sickness is deeper than the Marianas Trench.
Alright, Takumi,
look carefully.
It's not as narrow as Usui, and this dynamic climbing path is very similar to Akina's.
That's not what I mean.
The rhythm is similar.
``R...rhythm ?''
He's tough.
The FD's fast
in the corners.
I didn't expect anyone to keep up with my R and I on Myogi.
He's started
steering hard.
Is he going to increase the pace to try and outrun me ?
If you do that on the downhill, the tires will definitely lose grip.
This's the midpoint,
and they just went past.
The 32 is ahead,
but the gap is minimal.
I see.
Tell me one thing.
Is Nakazato pulling away from Keisuke at the corner's exit ?
Well, he's slightly slower at the exit, but he's keeping up overall.
His driving is very smooth.
It's very different from
Nakazato's drastic driving.
Okay, I got it.
Thanks.
If you're doing that,
you've improved, Keisuke.
The R32 is ahead, but
there's no gap in between.
They just passed us.
The 32 is ahead, but the
FD is right behind it.
Takeshi seems to
be doing alright.
He's been practicing so hard.
Yeah, he's been totally different since he was defeated by Akina's Eight-Six.
I've considered him my enemy even though we're on the same team, but now...
...when I think about him driving for our pride, my chest aches.
I've never had
a feeling like this.
Here comes the 32.
The FD's right behind it.
Please win, Takeshi.
I'm counting on you.
I can only
hear the sounds.
They're taking so
long to get up here.
What ?
Rain.
This is bad. It's in the middle of an attack at max speed.
The beginning of a rainstorm is the most dangerous.
The dust and sand on the asphalt are stirred up by the rain...
...and the road'll be
extremely slippery.
You can lose
grip very suddenly.
It's started raining.
Damn, the goal
is so close.
The beginning of the
rain is most dangerous.
When you skid, it happens
without any warning.
It's getting heavier.
I hope it won't be canceled.
Say, Itsuki...
...the goal is over there, which means this is the last corner, right ?
That's Myogi's peak, so this short section just before the goal is slightly downhill, isn't it ?
So, the last
part is downhill...
Here they come !
Now it's time to
settle this match !
Impossible !~~You won't be able to turn at that speed !
That idiot's gonna
crash into the cliff !
I can do it.
I have feedback.
My FD's telling me to go.
It's coming this way !
Run !
Goal !
The FD won !
Cool !~~It's so awesome !
Takahashi Keisuke is incredible !
This is the first time...
I've never been excited by watching someone else race before.
I can't stand still after watching something as incredible as that.
You were lucky,
Takahashi Keisuke.
No, it was because
of my skill.
Say what ?
The last corner
was downhill...
...so I knew that the key would
be the front tires' condition.
Didn't you wear down your tires, so the feedback from the front felt sluggish ?
I saved my tires while
I kept pace with you.
It was because of the
difference in our abilities.
Keisuke, that's
just like you !
What should we do
about the downhill ?
We'll have to cancel it
because of this heavy rain.
Yeah...
Then, Keisuke, let me race
against Akina's Eight-Six.
What ?
It's okay since it's not
our home course, right ?
This isn't his home course either,
so the conditions are equal.
Hey !
Senpai...
Who's he ?
I don't know.
Kenta...
You're Fujiwara
Takumi, aren't you ?
I'm Nakamura Kenta
of the Redsuns.
What do you say ?~~Will you accept my challenge to a rain battle ?
Hey, Kenta, without checking
with my brother...
Let's ask the galleries, Keisuke.
Guys, do you want to see a rain battle between me and the Eight-Six ?!
Go for it !
Do it !
T...this is bad.
He can't say no
in this situation.
B...but Takumi has a battle against Takahashi Ryosuke next week.
I'll race you first.
If you lose to me, you don't deserve to race against Ryosuke.
Don't just stand there.
Say something.
I'm confident
driving in the rain.
Don't tell me you're
scared of the rain.
No, the timing's bad.
He's not in
the right mood...
Okay, I'll do it.
W...wait...
No one can
stop them now.
But...
The Eight-Six isn't
only our target.
All Road Racers want to race against the Eight-Six.
You understand that,
don't you ?
That's what I want.
When it comes to the downhill in the rain, we can compare our techniques.
Go get your Eight-Six,
and pull up next to me.
Come with me, Itsuki.
Am I riding with you ?
If I leave you here, I'll have to come back and pick you up.
I don't want to waste my time, so let's go home after we get to the base.
Okay, I'm getting in.
Hold it.
Sorry, Itsuki, but would
you sit in the back ?
In the back ?
Okay.
Is there any
reason for this ?
Well, maybe there is
and maybe there isn't...
What do you mean ?
Aren't you sure yourself ?
How should I hold my
body during drift ?
I'll leave
it up to you.
Up to me ?~~Hey !
It's just a short ride to the base, so hang in there, okay ?
They're not gonna cancel !
There'll be another downhill race !
The Eight-Six...
Akina's Eight-Six is gonna race !
Okay,
no oncoming traffic.
Let's start.
This is totally unexpected.
Yeah, but there was
nothing we could do.
Please watch me, Keisuke.
I like rain.
Before I joined the team, when I practiced drifting alone, I chose rainy days.
I was poor, so I liked driving in the rain because the tires didn't wear out so quickly.
I like your confidence,
but don't underestimate the rain.
I have more experience in
the rain than anybody else.
Don't worry. If it's raining,
I have the advantage.
I'll win, because the
rain is on my side.
Hey, Takumi, you don't
look very nervous.
Are you alright
with this rain battle ?
I don't know.
I can't go as fast in the rain,
so I'll just drive like I normally do.
I don't know if I can
drive fast or not.
I'll try not to push
myself too hard.
If I damage the car,
Dad'll hit me.
I see.
But if he loses, what'll happen to the battle with Takahashi Ryosuke ?
I'll start the countdown.
Five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one.
Go !
You call this normal ?!
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sake bara no youni akaku
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tsuyoku tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Kagayaku mirai e
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
Sake bara no youni akaku
Tsuyoku tsuyoku dakishimete
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Kiseki no hana yo
A rain battle...
Will you be alright, Kenta ?
Yes, I'm confident.
Besides, Keisuke's watching,
so I have to win !
But your opponent is the Eight-Six, and even Keisuke couldn't beat him.
That's why I want to avenge him !
It's for Keisuke !
But it's a route you've
never raced on before.
I'll be alright.~~I'll drive so that I won't disgrace Keisuke !
Wait a minute.~~Don't tell me that Keisuke's your...
Well...
Initial
Next Time:
Downhill Rain Battle
Don't miss it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org