Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information spread out in a matter of second.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love"...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
W...what the hell ?
I don't believe this.
Did I just see the ghost of a Road Racer who died here ?
His first counter-steer was a motion to get the right angle for the left curve.
It was the perfect drift of a driver who knows everything about Akina.
Keisuke, did you
see that Eight-Six ?
Yeah.
My pride is torn up.
My FD, with its mountain setup, was beaten by a 10 year old Eight-Six junker.
What the hell is
that Eight-Six ?
Declaration of Revenge~!~~Howling Turbo
Yes, Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Hey, Takumi !~~Takumi !
How much longer are you gonna sleep ?
Get up !~~You've got a phone call !
It's Itsuki, isn't it ?
I don't know !
Hurry and pick up the phone !
Hello, it's me.
Takumi, over here !
Were you surprised ?
I was.
I thought it
was Itsuki.
I thought it was about time to restore our friendship.
Restore, you said ?
But we weren't in
a fight or anything.
You guys were talking about cars at school yesterday.
Can you drive, Takumi ?
Yeah, I just
got a license.
Then let's go driving
somewhere during summer break.
You drive and
I'll fix lunch.
Fine with me...
...but I only have
a dorky one for work.
I don't mind. It at least has a cassette deck, doesn't it ?
I don't care
what the car is.
I don't mind at all.
You don't ?
It'll be fun.
I'm getting excited.
Why don't we
drive a long way ?
That's right.
The ocean would be nice.
Let's swim together,
since it's summer.
No doubt.
It's the Eight-Six.
I bet the fastest on Akina
is the tofu shop's Eight-Six.
Is this the fastest
machine on the downhill ?
It looks like it's
an ordinary Eight-Six.
An early Apex model,
except for the fog lights.
A car like this can't be faster than the latest machines.
Something must be wrong
with me, searching for it.
Iketani.
Takumi.
What're you doing here ?
Hey, is this your house ?
Yeah.
What were you doing
in front of my house ?
I had something to do,
and I was just passing by.
Anyway, Takumi, you really don't know anything about cars.
You said you didn't know about
the Eight-Six yesterday...
...but the car at your
house is an Eight-Six.
Wait a minute.
It's not an Eight-Six.
It says Trueno
on the back.
You see, a Trueno
is an Eight-Six.
The Levins and Truenos with the chassis type AE86 are called Eight-Six.
Huh ?
An Eight-Six at
Takumi's house ?!
Are you serious, Iketani ?
Yeah, I'm serious.
Damn you, Takumi !
Why'd you keep
it a secret ?!
It couldn't be helped,
because I didn't know.
If it's a Trueno, why
don't you say Trueno ?
You said ``Eight-Six.''
Ordinary people don't call them that.
Why you...
By the way, I have
something to discuss.
Can you borrow the
Eight-Six next Saturday ?
Why ?
It's obvious.
We'll go watch the gathering
of the Speedstars and Redsuns.
Since that incident yesterday,
I'm really into the Road Racer world.
Don't you want to see how the Takahashi brothers, the fastest on Akagi, drive ?
Not really...
Say what ?!
How can you say that ?!
Are you really
my friend ?!
I beg you to drive your
Eight-Six on Saturday.
Hey, guys,
what're you doing ?
You have a customer.
Oh, I'm sorry.
How can I help you ?
Installing brand new tires ?
You've really spoiled yourself.
I've got to cut my time by
installing high grip tires.
I'll also change
the brake pads.
Brakes are important
on the downhill.
Are you going
to run, Iketani ?
I'll run on
the downhill.
I'll tackle the downhill
of Akina like hell.
Don't push yourself too hard.
One mistake'll kill you on the downhill.
I know.
I know, but I
have to push it...
...for the locals' pride.
That Eight-Six didn't
show up today.
He isn't a Road Racer
from this area ?
No.~~He knew everything
about Mt. Akina.
I want to see it again,
and get revenge...
...or I won't be
able to calm down.
Come out,
ghost of Akina.
I don't care
about the Speedstars.
I'm here to face you.
That's just like the drift king,
Tsuchiya Keiichi !~~I can't sit still !
He must be controlling
it using only acceleration.
Takumi, I wish we could
perform a drift like that !
Yeah.
Look at that drift !
It's awesome !
Yeah.
Takumi...
You only say ``yeah, yeah !''
Do you really know what drift is ?!
Yeah, I know
what drift is.
Well then,
explain what it is.
In the curve...
Don't say curve,
it sounds so uncool.
Road Racers
call them corners.
Well, in the corner...
...you steer like this to let the front tires go outward so the car won't face the inside.
Gimme a break, Takumi !
If the front tires go outward,
you're experiencing understeering.
It shows your poor skill,
and it's totally uncool.
You let the rear go
outward when you drift.
You're strange.
You're incredible, Takumi.
Right.
You're the one who
doesn't know, Iketani.
When the car is drifting, it's supposed to be understeered.
It was the advanced answer of those who have mastered the four-wheel drift.
I'm impressed.
Here's a customer.
Let's get to work.
O...okay.
How can I help you ?
Takahashi Keisuke's FD ?
High octane,
fill it up.
Okay.
You're really devoted, sir.
Of course.
I thought I'd
seen that S13.
It's from the Speedstars.
Can I ask
you something ?
You should
know about it.
There's a ghost on
Mt. Akina, isn't there ?
A ghost of an
extremely fast Eight-Six.
Man, does he want
to fly or something ?
Please don't joke
around with me, sir.
I was joking about
the ghost part...
...but it's about a black
and white panda Trueno...
The exterior looks like a normal Eight-Six,
but it's an incredible monster inside.
A local guy should know about such an incredible car.
Well, it's okay.
If it's your secret weapon for Saturday,
I'm looking forward to it.
Tell the driver
of the Eight-Six...
...that I won't let the
same guy defeat me twice.
I lost because I wasn't familiar with the course and got careless.
Thank you.
Takahashi Keisuke lost...?
What does he mean ?
I didn't know any
Eight-Six could do that.
It can't be...
But the one at Takumi's house is also a panda Trueno.
Is what the manager
said true ?
The fastest on the downhill
is still that Eight-Six ?
Okay, that does
it for today.
It's more than usual.
Hey, just don't
spill it, okay ?
I know.
You look as sleepy
as usual, Takumi.
I'm sorry, but my face
is like this naturally.
Don't forget your Eight-Six
on next Saturday, okay ?
I know.~~You're so
persistent, Itsuki.
I have to be persistent or I can't clear my doubts about you.
I wish Saturday would
come early !~~I'm so excited !
Hey, since we hope
to be Road Racers...
...we want to be called the fastest on Akina some day, right ?
I don't really
care either way.
Well, it's probably impossible,
even if you try...
...because you don't have a bit of talent, being scared in the rear seat of Iketani's car.
But I'm different.
Well, it was
a bit scary...
...but I could look at the sharp corners, clenching my teeth.
Iketani must have thought that there would be no hope for Takumi...
...but I have potential !
Takumi ?
Takumi !
Takumi, hey wait !
Even if you're jealous of
my talent, you're too cold.
I'm not...
Say what ?
Are you serious ?
And Rumiko told my boyfriend
about it.  He's so mad.
I saw it.
You like that ?
No.
It's a crime to make their skirts so short without thinking anything.
The school should regulate that.
Lucky.
Takumi, good morning.
M...Mogi.
Oh, I have something
to talk to you about.  Come with me.
Hurry.
W...what the hell ?!
What's going on ?!
What happened ?
Well...
...I have something...
...I want to tell you.
What is it ?
Well...I...
...bought a new bathing suit !
It's super cute !
Is that what you
wanted to tell me ?
Bingo.
Because I was so excited and I wanted to tell somebody about it.
Wanna see it ?
What color do
you think it is ?
You want to see
it soon, don't you ?
Well, I want to, but...
I'll let you see it as much as you want when we go to the ocean.
Until then...
...just...look...
forward...to...it.
What about this Sunday ?
Are you free ?
Yeah, I don't
have to work.
That'll do.
Promise me, okay ?
You can't break promises.
I don't like a person who breaks promises or smokes.
Damn, it's so difficult.
The dull corners now appear to be the scary and tight ones.
Those familiar corners
challenge me so differently.
It's no use.
Even if I push myself to the limit, I can't shorten the time.
I thought if I depressed the accelerator more, I could cut the time, but...
...it's not that easy.
Is this the best
my technique can do ?
There's no way
I can compete with them.
Hello !
Excuse me !
I can hear you.
Wait a moment.
How may I help you ?
Is he the Eight-Six driver who's the fastest on Akina ?
Is he the Road Racer who can beat Takahashi Keisuke ?
What do you want, sir ?
I'll have
a fried tofu.
Thanks.
What am I doing ?
Well, I'm Iketani...
...and I'm with a team
called the Akina Speedstars.
I heard a strange rumor that the fastest on Mt. Akina's downhill...
...is an old guy from a tofu shop, who drives an Eight-Six.
I don't know who said that,
but it's not me.
Please don't pretend
not to know !
Even if I searched
the entire city...
...I won't be able to find another tofu shop man who drives an Eight-Six.
Here.~~140 yen.
O...okay.
Okay, thanks.
Well, I'm in a
complicated situation.
Would you hear me out ?
Don't trouble me.
I'm working now.
You look bored !
No one else is here !
How rude, saying something directly that should've been held back.
I'm sorry,
but I'm desperate.
Actually, a team called the Akagi Redsuns challenged us to a time attack.
There are some highly skilled guys with the Redsuns, and we're no match for them.
I don't want to be
defeated as a local driver !
So, what do you
want me to do ?
Mr. Fujiwara, I want you to teach me how to tackle Akina.
That's impossible.
Just a little is fine.
I'll be satisfied, even if it shortens the time by a tenth of a second.
Please.
I know how you feel, but driving technique is not something you can obtain in a few days.
You have to think over and over how you can make the car run as you like...
...and keep on driving.
When I was actively driving,
I tackled Akina even in my dreams.
Technique isn't something to be taught, you must acquire it yourself.
I'm sorry that I can't
be of help to you.
Mr. Fujiwara, I'll
visit you again.
Think it over and over
and keep on driving...
I'm trying, but
I can't cut my time.
Why ?
Dammit. I can't figure it out, no matter how hard I think.
I can't dodge him !
Please, escape to the inside !
My pride says "You gatta be wild and tough."
*************************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Bunta: Unshou Ishizuka
Itsuki:Mitsuo Iwata
Natsuki:Ayako Kawasumi
Yuichi:Tomomichi Nishimura
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
**********************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Bunta: Unshou Ishizuka
Itsuki:Mitsuo Iwata
Natsuki:Ayako Kawasumi
Yuichi:Tomomichi Nishimura
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
***************************
Keisuke: Koyasu Takehito
Kenji: Tomokazu Seki
~~ Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Yumi Kakazu
Makiko Miyagi
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
*****************************
Keisuke: Koyasu Takehito
Kenji: Tomokazu Seki
~~ Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Yumi Kakazu
Makiko Miyagi
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
***************************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
*****************************************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
***********************************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make a room.
***********************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.02
Additional Timing:
Tizya
Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin my dream.
*************************************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.02
Additional Timing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safe zone.
************************************************
The bell sound in Takumi's Eight-Six indicates he's over 100kmph(60mph approx.)
Tsuchiya Keiichi is an active racer supervising this show.
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
********************************************
The bell sound in Takumi's Eight-Six indicates he's over 100kmph(60mph approx.)
Tsuchiya Keiichi is an active racer supervising this show.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down on the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logics...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
Tsuzuku hatenai michi wo{In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
Okay, today's guest is Fujiwara Bunta, the stubborn old guy from the Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Mr. Bunta, your philosophy says that driving technique can't be taught...
...and must be learned
by oneself ?
You sounded so cool,
and I really liked it.
Well, okay.
Then, could you tell us the highlights of the next episode ?
Wait until you see it.
Well, then look forward to
the next episode of Initial D !
Initial
Next Time:
Downhill Specialist Arrives
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org