Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
INITIAL
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves a lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
He caught me !
What's going on ?
It's driving me crazy !
This is from the straightaway in front of the skating rink !~~They've just passed us !
Keisuke is being pushed !
Akina's Eight-Six
is damned fast !
I've never seen anyone charging on Keisuke's FD so close !
I'm getting
goose bumps.
Incredible entry !
That Eight-Six performed an incredible entry oriented kamikaze drive !
That shitty old man won't call it a win unless I overtake that car.
It can't be helped, because the prize is a full tank of gas.
The attack point is the
five hairpin curves ahead.
End of the Dogfight!
Shit !
What's happening ?
It feels like my FD
is slower than usual.
Did the secondary
turbine stop ?
This is the peak.
Can you hear me ?
Ryosuke ?
They'll pass through
the five hairpins soon.
I want your
live report.
Make it as detailed
as possible.
Okay.
They're just around the corner.
I can hear the squealing sounds.
They'll pass by soon.
Here comes Keisuke's FD, and
the Eight-Six is following !
There's no gap
between them !
That Eight-Six is incredible !
It's performing perfect braking drifts !
Keisuke's turn-in is slower !
He's also good at exiting !
It's so close to the guardrail !
They're entering the second hairpin !
There's no gap at all !
They're even
at the exit !
The FD is moving to the outside,
and the Eight-Six is...
He's not slowing
down for the hairpin ?!
What the hell
is he thinking ?!
The Eight-Six is heading for the hairpin at incredible speed !
Did his brakes go out ?
What the hell was that...?
Keisuke was passed
so easily on the inside !
That's ridiculous !
That doesn't tell us anything !
Explain what happened !
Well...even though
we saw it...
You know how a car can't turn
beyond its tires' grip speed, right ?
But the Eight-Six, even though it was on a disadvantageous inside line...
...turned strangely, just like
it was on a roller coaster.
I don't understand
what happened !
I know what the
Eight-Six did.
It's so silly, but no
one else could do it.
And it can only
happen on Akina.
I've found an
incredible idiot.
I'm looking
forward to this.
The one who will defeat the
downhill specialist of Akina...
...will be me, Nakazato Takeshi of the Myogi Night kids.
This is the finish line, I can hear their engines.  They'll be here soon !
Here they come !
Which one...?!
It's the Eight-Six !
My god,
what happened ?!
Keisuke's FD just showed up, but he's too far behind to close the gap !
The Eight-Six
is way ahead !
Shit !
How could my FD be
defeated by an Eight-Six ?
It's impossible.
A 350 horsepower car was outrun by a crappy Eight-Six ?!
They've crossed the
finish line !
Keisuke lost !
He did it !
Am I still having
a bad dream ?
I was defeated by the
Eight-Six not once but twice ?
That stupid
Takumi won !
Incredible...incredible.
I'm so thrilled.
My head is spinning.
He did it.
Yeah.
Iketani, don't cry,
you idiot.
I'm so impressed.
Let's ask him to teach us things like drift control and line taking.
Put a Speedstars sticker on his car without telling him.
Okay, I'll do that !
I'll leave that
to you then.
We were totally defeated.
We have to admit that.
What about the uphill
time attack, Ryosuke ?
It's meaningless, even
if we win on the uphill.
By tomorrow...
...everyone will know that the Akina Eight-Six defeated the undefeated Redsuns.
We'll have our revenge
with my FC soon.
A full tank of gas...
You promised.
You promised, okay ?
So he won.
I knew he would
before he left.
The right side is where
the Eight-Six passed me.
I can't understand why the Eight-Six turned faster on the inside edge than my FD.
It scares me every
time I recall.
Maybe he really
is a ghost.
Keisuke, tell me
what happened.
Did you notice
anything strange ?
Come to think of it, I heard
a strange scraping sound.
Strange sound ?
I see.
I got it.
I can tell you why
you were defeated.
He used this.
The gutter ?
Yes.
He dropped his inner tires into the gutter on purpose, to withstand the centrifugal force.
That way, it's theoretically possible to obtain cornering force which exceeds tire grip.
It's such a plain, simple,
and silly idea...
...but you just can't do it on the spur of the moment.
He's probably done
it many times.
He must push himself
to the limit on Akina.
Shit !
Well, I like the mountain passes because things like this can happen.
After such a long time, I finally feel like I've found a target that truly excites me.
Let's suspend the
match next week.
We can't step up unless we
record a perfect win on Akina.
I'll defeat
the Eight-Six.
Bunta, are you there ?
It's me.
So hot.
Oh, Yuichi.
Good timing.
I have a local
commerce meeting now.
Why don't you
give me a ride ?
Say what ?~~Are you using me as a taxi driver ?
I heard Takumi
was incredible.
That's all that Iketani and the others can talk about this morning.
He's not really
that great.
The skill level of kids these days isn't very high, is it.
He doesn't even like
driving a car.
Really ?
I can't believe it
since he has such skill.
To him, driving a car means nothing but helping the shop.
He's had to do it since middle school, so he doesn't feel any sense of enjoyment.
I see.
He's uninterested,
or should I say bored.
But I think he felt something after the race on Akina's downhill yesterday.
Come to think of it,
the Eight-Six was gone.
Where is Takumi ?
I'm not sure, but he seemed excited and left home early.
It's cold.
Takumi, you're
good at driving.
Really ?
I usually get
sick in cars...
...so I brought some
medicine with me.
But thanks to your driving,
I didn't feel sick.
This is the first time I've been in a car so long without getting sick.
Do you ride in
cars that often ?
N...not that often...
...like when the whole family takes a trip in my father's car.
Strange girl.
I just drove like I do to
keep the water from spilling.
I felt strange yesterday.
I noticed as I was rapidly closing in on the car ahead of me...
...I was getting excited.
I've never felt that
driving was very fun.
Even today, it's fun to drive with Mogi in the passenger seat.
Cars are pretty
interesting.
Hey, Takumi.
Hey, hey !
You were thinking
about something.
You weren't
paying attention.
You're so mean.
How can you leave such a cute girl alone and go into your own world ?
Sorry.  What were
we talking about ?
I asked you if you
have some girl you like.
Not really.
I do have someone I'm
interested in a little, though.
What about you ?
I have...
...someone I'm interested
in a little, too.
What do you mean ?
Don't copy what I say.
Man, I don't know how many times I was asked the same question.
``Who was in
that Eight-Six ?''
I was asked so
many times, too.
He defeated Takahashi Keisuke,
so he might as well be famous.
I created hype by saying that it was the Speedstars' secret weapon.
I have to get Takumi to join the Speedstars or I'll look bad.
Senpai, leave
that to me !
I'm Takumi's
best friend.
He'll listen to me.
Are you sure, Itsuki ?
Don't worry.
I know his weaknesses, too.
Could you let me join
the Speedstars, too ?
If Takumi does, then
I'll let you in, too.
Right ?
Yeah.
Lucky !
What a great deal !
But what'll you
do without a car ?
Thanks for asking.
I've decided.
Oh, you finally saved
up enough money ?
I'll make my dad a guarantor, and get a loan to buy an Eight-Six !
Takumi has a panda Trueno,
so I'll find a red or black Levin...
And someday, we'll be called the fastest Eight-Six pair on Akina.
But, Itsuki...
...Takumi's Eight-Six
isn't normal.
Right.  It was faster
than the 350 HP FD.
It must be
heavily tuned.
I'd like to take a look
at its engine someday.
I'd like to ride with him when he attacks Akina's downhill at full speed.
How about you ?
Yeah !
I wanna ride, too !
I'll reach an untouched zone
I can't even imagine.
It must be greater than
any roller coaster.
Damn that Takumi !
Wait a minute, Takumi.
Excuse me, but would
you take a picture ?
Sure.
Why're you taking
a picture ?
We came so far.
It's for our souvenir.
Smile, smile.
Ready ?
Sorry, one more picture.
One more picture, please.
That's enough.
It's not.
That white FC...
It's Takahashi Ryosuke.
There goes the Redsuns
number one driver.
Why's he here ?
To avenge his brother.
What else ?
It's right after
yesterday's match.
He must be pretty frustrated because that Eight-Six took all the fame.
An unfamiliar 32, isn't it ?
That black 32 has
a menacing presence.
Who's in it ?
My pride says "You gotta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Guys:
Hajime Hosoi
Shogo Sakamoto
Naoki Imamura
Masato Amano
Jun Suzuki
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Guys:
Hajime Hosoi
Shogo Sakamoto
Naoki Imamura
Masato Amano
Jun Suzuki
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Song Translations:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Song Translations:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make room.
************************
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.02
Additional Timing:
Tizya
`Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin' my dream.
************************
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.02
Additional Timing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safety zone.
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change, even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang, another round, never slow down.
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down to the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logic...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
Damn, that Takumi is a traitor !
You look so angry, Itsuki.
He left his best friend behind,
and went to the beach with Mogi !
You wanted to see Natsuki in her bathing suit, didn't you ?
Damn right !
Takumi must've done things like this and things like that...
...or even everything !
Next time on Initial D,
the signs of a new battle.
Initial
Next Time:
A New Challenger
Don't miss it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org