Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information spread out in a matter of second.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love"...
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
A car with good straightaway
speed is following me.
Why don't
I wait for him ?
An R32 GT-R ?
Let me see how
good it runs.
Fine with me,
that's what I want.
A New Challenger
Is this place alright ?
I'm fine.  My house is
just around the corner.
You said this car is
dorky, but I like it.
It's lively,
small and cute.
What's it called ?
Trueno.
A Trueno...
Let me ride in
the Trueno again.
It was fun today, Takumi.
Bye-bye.
I'll call you again.
Cute, she said.
What do you think ?
I can keep up
with Takahashi Ryosuke.
The GT-R is
unbeatable after all.
No matter how good the driver is,
I guess that's the best a dated FC can do.
I'm Takahashi Ryosuke,
a member of the Redsuns.
I know.
I'm Nakazato Takeshi.
I'm with the team in
Myogi called the Night Kids.
Nakazato Takeshi of
the Night Kids...?
The fastest downhill
Road Racer on Myogi.
I'm honored to be known by a super star like Takahashi Ryosuke.
But the Night Kids'
Nakazato I heard of...
...was driving an S13.
Well, whatever.
And what is a Road Racer
from Myogi doing on Akina ?
Hey, come on.
What about you ?
You're from Akagi, and I know we're here for the same reason.
I came here to see the
Eight-Six I saw yesterday.
A 32 driver is going to
challenge the Eight-Six ?
With a 32 tuned to 380 HP ?
How...?
I can tell by the exhaust sound on the straightaway and power.
But the outcome's
pretty obvious.
The Eight-Six is no match
for the 32 on the uphill...
...and you can't defeat the Eight-Six with your 32 on the downhill.
Say what ?
My 32 can't beat the
Eight-Six on the downhill ?
Don't be offended.~~I'm just telling you my opinion.
You sound pathetic.
You don't have to be so hesitant just because your brother was defeated.
It's only an Eight-Six.
You'll find out
if you race him...
...that only
I can defeat him.
Don't mess with me.  Having said that, I won't back down.
I'll defeat the Eight-Six,
and make you eat your words.
Your confidence
won't last long !
Don't forget about
Nakazato of Myogi !
You'll learn that the rotary is no match for the 32 !
...was driving an S13.
That's right,
I changed at that moment.
Damn, I can't pass him,
no matter how hard I try !
Even if I close in on the corner,
he pulls away on the straightaway.
My technique as a
Road Racer is better !
Damn, I won't lose !
I can't keep up with
a 32 with this car ?
The best of Myogi can't defeat
a 32, which doesn't even drift ?
A car has
its limits.
No matter how good the driver is,
it won't run beyond its capabilities...
...even if it's the Eight-Six.
Good morning.
Yo.
Here, Iketani.
What's that ?
Fried tofu.
We had some left from yesterday,
so Dad told me to give it to you.
I see.
I'll put it
in the fridge.
He's concerned about me.
By the way, Takumi...
Is it true that you've been delivering tofu to the hotel by Akina Lake for five years ?
Yeah.
You're so secretive.
You could've told me.
I couldn't talk about it openly.
I would've gotten in trouble.
T...that's true.
We were only middle school
freshmen five years ago.
So you've been driving
longer than me.
Every day on Akina, whether it's raining or snowing, since middle school.
It was early morning,
so nobody saw me...
That's not what
I'm talking about...
...but weren't you scared
of those corners ?
I was scared
in the beginning...
...but my fear was gone
after six months or so.
As I picked up the speed, the tires would naturally start skidding...
...and it took me another six months until I could skid and stop as I like.
So you mastered the downhill
in only a year ?!
When you do it everyday,
you get used to skidding.
So I try to get as close
as I can to the guardrails.
Ordinary people don't
do such dangerous things !
I never thought
it was dangerous...
...and when I'm in a good mood,
I can get as close as 1 cm.
One centimeter...?!
It's really boring work unless
I find something interesting to do.
I've never thought about improving my driving techniques.
It's tiring, and I just wanna get home as fast as I can...
...so I drive as fast as possible on the way home since I'm not carrying tofu.
Takumi, can I ask
you something ?
How do you drive
when you carry tofu ?
If you drive too rough, you'll damage the tofu, won't you ?
I can't drive that
fast on the way up.
Dad puts water in a paper cup,
and I put it in the cup holder.
If I don't spill the water, I won't damage the tofu, even if I drive fast.
It's pretty difficult.
In the beginning, I spilled
a lot even when I drove slowly.
Makes sense.
Brakes, steering wheel,
gears and the gas pedal...
If I'm too rough with any of those, I spill the water.
Dad told me to rotate
the water in the cup.
Rotate the water
in the cup...?
I think it's got something to
do with surface tension.
The water rotates extremely close to the edge of the cup.
I rotate the water in
every curve when climbing.
It took me a while to
drift without spilling the water.
Drift without spilling it ?!
Can you do that ?
Don't lie to us, Takumi !
You're just joking, right ?!
The most important factor in
driving is shifting the weight.
The drift king, Tsuchiya Keiichi,
said the same thing.
In order not to spill the water in the cup, he had to learn extremely delicate weight shifting.
Especially if it's drift...
No one can do that !
I'm not lying.
Just because you defeated Takahashi Keisuke, don't get overconfident !
As far as I'm concerned...
A customer.
Welcome.
High octane.
Yes, sir.
He's incredible, Bunta.  He'll go beyond being a mountain Road Racer.
Thank you very much.
Takumi, I want to
ask you a favor.
Can you give me a ride,
and drive hard on Akina ?
You're going to use the car
at this time of night ?
I can't, can I.
It's okay, 'cause it's
not very important.
I don't mind.
Are you sure ?
Don't you need the car to
go to a meeting or something ?
You'd better think
about it some more.
What's the matter ?  You sound like you WANT me to have something to do.
It's not that, but...
Then go ahead and use it, but come pick me up at the meeting place.
So you do
have a meeting.
I'm getting
really excited.
It's like riding one of those scream machines in a theme park.
Damn, I'm so envious.
I don't think
it'll be that fun.
I'm ready, Iketani.
Okay, Takumi.
Push it to the limit.
Move away, guys.
It makes a
wonderful sound.
You can never hear
that from a turbo.
Here comes the
first corner.
I'd better pay close attention to see the difference, and steal his technique.
H...hey.
Hey !
Takumi, the brakes !
How...how's he controlling the car in this situation ?!
What's going on ?
Is this really a car ?
Incredible.
It's ringing
at this point ?!
That means he's already
going beyond 100 km/h ?!
The next corner
is coming up !
Hey, the Eight-Six
is coming back.
I wonder why.  It's too soon if he went to the base of the mountain.
He passed out.
Takumi...
...how many corners ?
T...three...?
I witnessed the incident !
On the frightening Mt. Akina downhill
where a scream echoes...
...of Iketani in
the third corner...
...passing out !
I guess he's for real.
Manager, why're you here ?
Well, I was
a little curious.
I guess I'm
out of place.
Please, enjoy.
I've heard of him.
Nakazato of the Night Kids
is unbeatable on Myogi.
I don't trust the skill
of 32 drivers.
Only the car is fast.
Is that so ?
You don't think so, Brother ?
Here comes Keisuke's
hatred of the 32.
But, Ryosuke...
...I don't think it's a good idea for Nakazato to go ahead of us.
If the Night Kids defeat the Eight-Six we couldn't defeat...
...people will start thinking our skills are less than the Night Kids.
That's how a rumor spreads, and I think that's Nakazato's intention.
I don't think
we have to worry.
Nobody in the Night Kids can defeat that Eight-Six.
As long as they race on Akina's downhill, no one can defeat him.
Nobody but my brother
can defeat him.
That Eight-Six is
so good and fast.
I don't get it.
Why can't the latest high powered car defeat the Eight-Six ?
Sometimes, having too much
power is a disadvantage.
The turbo power is a welcome
aid on the straightaway...
...but it disturbs the control of the car when exiting a corner.
It's like a
double-edged sword.
In the case of
the Eight-Six...
...once the line is determined, it can go fast as the driver demands.
In a technical course, where
the straightaways are short...
...an underpowered car can
run at its full potential.
So the turbo power of Keisuke's car worked negatively.
On Akina's downhill...
...the total time for using
my 350 HP maximum was very limited.
As soon as it boosted
to max, I had to brake.
It was really frustrating.
That's the characteristic of the FR, which only uses the rear tires to transmit the power.
Hey, wait.
What about a
4WD like the 32 ?
With ATTESA E-TS system, which provides stable traction during acceleration...
...it can use the full potential of its turbo power, can't it ?
Nakazato might defeat the
Eight-Six with his 32.
Thank you very much !
Welcome !
But I feel strange.
The way I look at
you is different.
What do you mean ?
Why don't you have
another bean jam bun ?
When you eat a bun like that,
you look like your usual self.
You're just a
sleepy headed moron.
Don't call me a moron.
But...
Once you sit in the driver seat of the Eight-Six and go off into the night on Akina...
Bang, squeal and boom !
You're the star Road Racer
of Akina, an admired hero !
Am I ?~~Really ?
I'm embarrassed.
I said not now !
You're only a moron
eating a bean jam bun !
Actually, I feel weird.
How ?
Not just during the race, but also when I gave Iketani a ride yesterday...
I just drove like I normally do, but I don't understand why you guys got so excited.
I've never made
people so excited.
Driving is getting
more interesting.
Hey.
The black 32.
I've seen it
a lot these days.
Damn, he's
tailgating me.
Try not to
let it pass.
Okay.  The power difference is less significant on the downhill.
Even the Eight-Six
defeated the FD.
Small fry...
He passed us
on the outside !
It's almost scary. Its exit
acceleration is incomparable.
As I thought, in reality, an underpowered car can't overtake a car with a bigger engine.
This is an
incredible machine.
After I changed cars,
my rivals became insignificant.
I no longer had any opponent
I could take seriously.
Those showy drift plays
aren't my style.
With grip driving, I can push myself to the limit, and thrill myself.
Otherwise, I can't
be satisfied.
Come on,
Eight-Six of Akina.
I instantaneously sensed that you're good enough to be my opponent.
My pride says "You gatta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make a room.
************************
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.02
Additional Timing:
Tizya
Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin my dream.
************************
Timing
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.02
Additional Timing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safe zone.
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang another round, never slowdown
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down on the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logics...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
Tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
A normal GT-R has 280 HP
ATTESA:
Advanced Total Traction Engineering System
for
E-TS:  Electrical Torque Split
I heard that you were a famous Akina Road Racer, Manager.
Sort of.~~I used to
drive with Bunta.
And Takumi will race against Nakazato of the Night Kids next, won't he ?
Yeah, but he doesn't
like to race.
Then we won't be able
to see the race ?
Wait a moment.~~I have a good idea, so just leave it to me.
Next time on Initial D,
``A Road Racer's Pride.''
Initial
Next Time:
A Road Racer's Pride
Don't miss it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org