Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves a lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
Don't blame me.
The Eight-Six of Akina will simply turn to scraps of metal in a junkyard.
Now I'm pissed.
He did that on purpose.
I won't lose to a lowlife like you, no matter what !
Angry Takumi's Maniacal Drive !
Watch out !
He didn't mind
hitting the guardrail !
And he used the reaction
to initiate his drift !
What's that Eight-Six
driver thinking ?!
No way.
The Eight-Six is
gaining on me.
That's impossible !
Is he trying to
kill himself, or what ?
That Eight-Six driver
has gone nuts.
If an ordinary
driver gets angry...
...he'll keep making mistakes and won't be able to run fast.
But he's different.
His natural driving sense allows him to push the Eight-Six to its limit.
The angrier he gets,
the faster he drives.
The result of this
race is obvious, Shingo.
Shit...
Although I'm pushing
my EG6 to the limit...
How could this
be happening ?
It's strange.
I've never been so afraid of attacking the downhill before.
He's on my tail !
I don't believe this.
The EG6 is the best of its class, but it's being pushed hard by an Eight-Six.
It has nothing to do with being fast or slow, it's fundamentally different.
That Eight-Six
is a monster.
But I'll be fine as long as
I don't let him overtake me.
After I clear the five hairpin curves, the finish is near.
This battle is mine.
I won't let you
take the inside.
Is he going to
hit me this time ?
Dammit.
I thought he was
going to hit me...
...but what was that
cornering just now ?
He stayed inside at full speed,
and passed me so easily.
How could
I be overtaken ?
I don't get it !
Will Takumi be alright ?
I don't think we have
to worry anymore.
We've come this far, so he must've figured out this death match.
He might have pulled
away from that EG6.
If so, that annoying jerk from the Night Kids must be sweating a lot.
Yeah.
He might be regretting
challenging Takumi already.
I dragged him into
this gumtape death match.
If I lose, I'll be the
laughingstock of the team.
I'll keep my reputation by
ending this race with a tie.
The power of my B16A will make our cars run side by side in this short straightaway.
You can't get away.
The end of this battle...
...will be a
double crash !
One's coming.
Which one ?
It's gotta
be the EG6.
The Eight-Six ?!
W...what's that
Eight-Six's problem ?
He almost killed me.
What happened ?
The EG6 isn't coming.
What happened
to Shingo ?
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream, shining bright in the wind...
...you shout with your dream.
Rage your dream.
It almost stops my heartbeat.
I can feel it so strongly.
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang another round, never slow down.
My EG6...
Could that be Takumi ?!
No.
You lost it ?
You're lucky the
damage isn't too severe.
Hey, are you alright ?
Any injuries ?
Get in my car.
I'll take you
to the hospital.
It's quicker than
calling an ambulance.
You don't have
to do that much.
Just make a phone call.
Don't be stubborn.
It hurts, doesn't it ?
When we have an accident, we're supposed to help each other.
We're locals, so we know
an emergency hospital.
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
He's incredible.
Who the hell is that
Eight-Six driver ?
Takumi, Takumi !
Are you awake ?!
Come down here !
What ?
I'm awake,
'cause it's that time.
Just come down, quick !
So, what're those ?
You must've hit
the car somewhere.
There are three scratches that look like the kind made by touching the guardrail.
I don't remember anything.
It must've been you.
I didn't drive it yesterday,
so it was you !
Look at those scratches
on the bumper and fender !
It's true.
How terrible.
Who did that ?
You did !
Ouch.
Why'd you do that ?
What ?
Come to think of it, I barely remember hitting something with the car.
What's wrong with you ?
You're too young
to be senile.
I raced this really disgusting guy yesterday, and he pissed me off in the middle of it.
So I got really mad for some reason, but then I came home and went to bed quickly.
I don't know how it happened, but you aren't very good if you hit something with your car.
If it had been me, I wouldn't have hit anything, no matter what.
So, did you win ?
Yeah.
I see.
Is it alright
to do that, Itsuki ?
The examination didn't
show anything bad...
...so I'll be leaving
the hospital soon.
These flowers
are for you.
I'll arrange them.
Arigato.
I heard all
about it, Takumi.
You won the
gumtape death match.
Yeah.
You're incredible, Takumi !
You can handle
FR killer rules.
You're really a genius.
Itsuki, I wanted to win that battle, no matter what.
Not just because
he pissed me off...
...but also because
I didn't want to lose.
I've never felt
like that before.
You're becoming more
and more like a Road Racer.
No, it's nothing like that.
Okay, once I get out of the hospital, I'll improve my technique.
That way I won't disgrace the name of Akina's Levin/Trueno pair.
What're you guys
talking about ?
Oh, nothing.
By the way,
what about Saori ?
Is she doing fine ?
Is she alright ?
Yeah, she told me
to say hello.
Oh, really ?
Okay, once I'm out of the hospital, let's all go driving together again.
Sure.
Yeah.
It's good to know
that Itsuki's fine.
Yeah.
And his Eight-Five
will be returned soon.
I lied to
him a little.
Saori told me that she was really scared when the accident happened.
She doesn't want to remember that moment, so...
So, even though she knows Itsuki's a nice guy, she wants to leave things behind.
Saori won't
come after all.
Dammit !
Road Racers don't
need a girl !
Hey, what's up ?
I'm gonna take the car to a body shop, but
I wanted to see your aged face before that.
Takumi hit the
car really hard.
But in that race,
it was unavoidable.
That idiot.
But it's a good sign.
You're acting strange.
Your car's fender is dented
and you're still smiling.
His driving
style changed.
He was good, but
he lacked something.
He's trying
to drive fast.
He broke through a wall.
How do you know, Bunta ?
I know because I look
at the Eight-Six every day.
I can see how
he drives so well.
Is that so ?
I'll stop by on the way home, so let's have a drink later, Yuichi.
See ya.
Bye.
A crazy son and
a crazy father.
He hasn't
changed a bit.
I couldn't help
stopping the car.
I don't have any dirty thoughts,
but I can't leave her alone.
Well, I...I don't want you
to think I'm suspicious.
I'm just curious about
what happened to your car.
I don't really
know what happened.
I tried starting it many times,
but the engine won't start.
If you don't mind,
I'll take a look.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
In cases like this, it's
probably an electrical problem.
Let's see...
S13...
Speedstars...?
Can you fix it ?
Yeah.
Man, I've never been so close to a woman other than my mom.
Oh no, my heart's
gonna burst.
She's ultra cute.
Smells nice.
I'm smelling a babe for
the first time in my life.
Oh no, what if
I smell of sweat...?!
Okay, I think
it'll run.
Start the motor.
Alright.
It started !
Great !
Thank you very much.
You really saved me.
It was nothing.
That's not true.
I admire people who
are good with machines.
I'll make it
up to you later.
How can
I contact you ?
It's okay.~~You don't
have to worry about it.
I see.
Damn !
This could be the only chance God will give me in my entire life.
I'm an idiot !
Stupid, moron !
I'm such an idiot !
Ummm, excuse me.
Here.
I'm Sato Mako.
Please call me.
Mune ni nokoru nanigenai kotoba dakega
Only casual words remained in my heart.
Mayoi michi wo nukeru basho shitteita
I knew the place to free me from my delusion.
Anata ni deatta hi kara nanika ga kawarihajimete
Something started to change since the day I met you.
Itsushika koko ni tatteita
I realized that I kept standing here.
That's for your love.
This isn't a dream.
Omoide ni kaeru hodo tsuyoi wake ja nai kedo
It wasn't a memory so strong to recall.
Yorisotta ano koro ni
When we got close...
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
Kagayaku mirai e
...into the bright future.
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Let's make it sure over and over.
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
This passion will be eternal.
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku dakishimete
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
Kiseki no hana yo
The flower of miracles.
You appeared before me so suddenly, like a bright flash of light.
I lost my heart
to your beauty !
Hey, Iketani,
what happened ?
I can't live without you.
Are you a queen or an
angel who fills my heart ?
It's no use.~~He's completely
in his own world.
Next time on Initial D:
``The Angels of Usui Mountain.''
Angel...?!
Oh, my sweet Mako !
Don't miss it !
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org