Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
~~
This story is fiction. The names of people, places and groups are imaginary. Obey traffic rules and drive safely.
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves a lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
What's wrong with
this Eight-Six ?
These normal wheels make
me sick just looking at them.
My eyes are watering !
I've never seen someone
driving an Eight-Five !
A brat deserves
an Eight-Five !
Try hard and don't let
a scooter tailgate you.
I'm pissed.~~I can't
let them get away.
Here we go.
T...Takumi !
Taku...Taku...Taku...
My...my...my Eight-Five...
Please drive gently
with my Eight-Five !
It's alright, Takumi !
T...Takumi...
S...stop, Takumi !
Nice move !
W...what the...?
Hey, a car's
tailgating us.
It must be those
Akina brats.
They'll need ten years of
practice to challenge us.
I see.
I'll outrun it easily.
Takumi, it's alright !
Stop !
Slow down, Takumi !
I don't believe it.
Is this really
my Eight-Five ?
The car behind
us is pretty good.
Could it be...?
I don't know what's goin' on,
but that's the Eight-Five !
That's the Eight-Five we
saw at the top earlier !
It can't be !~~How could an Eight-Five keep up with me ?
You're right !
It's that Eight-Five !
Those brats must've
lied to us !
It must be...
...an Eight-Six !
Okay, go.
What's this ?
It doesn't accelerate,
even on the downhill.
And the tires...
I don't believe this.
They don't have any grip at all.
He's incredibly fast !
It's so slow.
Oh well, I don't have any choice
but to do it that way.
I won't let you
pass, no matter what !
What the...?!
What the hell was that ?!
How I was overtaken ?
That's not
an Eight-Five...
...it must be
an Eight-Six.
It's a highly
tuned Eight-Six.
Or so I thought,
but that rolling...
Could that really
be an Eight-Five ?
We were totally outrun.
That Eight-Five
gave me the creeps.
Could that be...
...a ghost ?!
Is coffee alright ?
Here.
Arigato.
Now I understand
what Iketani meant.
Your downhill
driving is unusual.
Is it ?
I don't think so.
You dummy.
You just don't know it.
I never thought a car
could run like that.
My point of view
has been changed.
It was so shocking.
Was it scary ?
Sorry.
You don't have
to apologize, Takumi.
I'm so happy
I can't sit still.
The performance of a
car isn't the issue.
Good skill can make an
Eight-Five run fast like that.
I really like
this car a lot.
I'll take good care of it, and I'll practice hard starting tomorrow.
I don't mind if
people laugh at me.
I like my
Eight-Five best.
That's right.
Let's ask some girls to go
driving in my Eight-Five.
S...sure.
Don't go without telling
me next time, okay ?
No matter what, Takumi.
I know.
Beach, girls in swimsuits...
Wait for me !
Alright !
My S13.
Finally, it's returned with the
same handsome face as before.
I'm almost
ready to cry.
Itsuki, are you trying
to run me over ?
I'll start driving
hard tonight.
I'll lower the grade of the tires and practice drifting.
I'll join you.
Look at this sticker !
It's alright, isn't it ?
Well...I guess so.
I'm finally a member
of the Speedstars !
Alright, that's it.
And before I forget the feeling
of the downhill drive with Takumi...
Say what ?
You rode with Takumi
in his Eight-Six ?
I did...
...but not in his
Eight-Six though.
What's with that
suspicious grin ?
Tell us everything.
What should I do...?
Do you want to
drink oil, Itsuki ?
Okay, okay !
I let him drive my Eight-Five, and he pushed it hard on Akina's downhill.
It was incredible. I've never
had such an experience before.
My Eight-Five started skidding way before the corner...
...and the reflection on the windshield went by sideways so fast !
It's a godsent skill !
He drifted your Eight-Five ?
It doesn't
even have LSD.
It happened
so quickly.
He passed two cars, driven by jerks in the hairpins on the downhill.
It felt so good !
Do you believe
that story, Manager ?
Even if it's Takumi, it's
just an ordinary Eight-Five.
Usually, it'd be impossible,
since it's an Eight-Five.
You don't have
to say that much.
Even if you don't
believe me, fact is fact.
If he can do that
with an Eight-Five...
...he has much better
adaptability than I thought.
The Eight-Five and Eight-Six share the same body, so maybe the characteristics are similar.
I don't think so.
The suspension of
a normal Eight-Five...
...and Bunta's heavily tuned Eight-Six are like chocolate and shit.
They're totally different.
Shit ?!
So Takumi can push
any car to the limit.
Yeah.
I think he can push any car with an FR layout to its full potential.
They say that you can't use any tricks to drive the Eight-Six.
You have to master the basics in order to push it to the limit.
The Eight-Six is a car
that trains the driver.
That's what Bunta
always says.
The car that just passed by
had a Night Kids sticker.
It had the suspension
of a road racer.
If you pay attention
to how a car bounces...
...it's easy to tell whether the
suspension is modified or not.
Besides, we've seen the Night Kids so often on Akina lately.
I wonder why
they come here.
Well, their leader,
Nakazato, was defeated...
...so I don't think anyone
will ask for a return match.
It serves him right.
After being defeated by the Eight-Six, Takeshi won't be so influential in the team anymore.
What would you
like to have ?
Two coffees.
Okay.
Besides, Shingo, I heard that the driver of the Speedstars' Eight-Six is young.
I don't know about him.
But if I defeat the Eight-Six, then me and Takeshi's positions will be reversed.
I'll be the fastest
of the Night Kids.
Are you going to
do it, Shingo ?
I know you're fast on the downhill,
but your opponent won't be so easy.
I'd be able to equal him by racing normally, but that'd be boring.
I have an interesting idea that will guarantee a 100 percent chance of winning.
Just wait and see...
...and I'll let him experience an
impressive and dangerous downhill.
The downhill specialist should be no one else but me.
The days of the
Eight-Six are over.
I'll push it to the bottom of the valley and send it to the junkyard.
Shoji Shingo of the Night Kids is the fastest downhill driver in the Gunma area.
Where's Ryosuke ?
My brother ?
He's staying in his room,
staring at his computer every day.
I don't know
what's so interesting.
No other Road Racer in Gunma could use a computer to race faster, except my brother.
Hey, Hiroshi, what do you think would happen if Akina's Eight-Six and my brother raced ?
What do I think ?
There's no way Ryosuke
would be defeated.
The Eight-Six's secrets are out in the open because of the last race.
All data was registered systematically in Ryosuke's brain...
...and he must've completed
a winning simulation.
No other Road Racer knows
cars better than my brother.
His technique
is outclassing.
I can't imagine my
brother being defeated.
So ?
But I feel like the Eight-Six
won't be defeated either.
Beautiful high speed drift...
Exquisite braking control...
He's equally exceptional.
As a Road Racer, driving the FR layout, maybe I'm addicted to his driving.
Keisuke...
If they race, one
of them will lose.
I don't want my
brother to be defeated...
...but for some reason, I also don't want to see the Eight-Six defeated.
I feel strange.
I'm sorry.
Did you get wet ?
No.
Pick it up
for a second.
Takumi, why don't we
go somewhere again ?
The mountains, highlands or
the beach would be nice, too.
It's summer break.
We'll share a
lot of memories.
Sure.
I can stay overnight if
it's with you, Takumi.
When will you
have a day off ?
Sunday again...?
The schedule's
not up yet.
Then why don't we go driving
on the next holiday ?
With your car.
Don't go without telling
me next time, Takumi !
Ummm...do you mind if Itsuki comes along, too ?
Itsuki, too ?
Yeah.
If you can arrange a girl for him, it would be great.
He's a nice guy, but he's clumsy about finding a girl.
You're a really
good friend.
I don't mean to
be like this, but...
Okay, I'll talk
to my friends.
You will ?
I'll find a pretty girl
who matches Itsuki.
You look cool !
Maybe I'd better
give it a try.
I'm getting better at using the parking brake to let the rear skid.
Steering timing
is the key.
So you use the parking
brake to start drifting.
But, Iketani, when I was sitting next to Takumi...
...I didn't see him using
the parking brake at all.
Takumi has an advanced technique to initiate the load-shift by only using the foot brake.
We have a long way
to go to achieve that.
We've been happy skidding our cars by stepping on the gas pedal at a corner's exit.
But it's an elementary technique called a ``power slide,'' and it's different from a drift.
In a real drift, like
you see Takumi doing...
...you enter a corner while skidding and minimize the slide at the exit.
That's the fastest manner,
and it looks cool.
I see.
You must've studied a lot.
I had lots of time
until my S13 returned.
I studied by
reading a lot.
I'd like to try
the sidespin.
I'm getting excited !
I've got the hang of it,
so I'll move to the next step.
I'll try the sidespin in a moderate curve instead of a straightway.
Good luck, Iketani !
Watch out for
other cars !
We'll join you later !
It's difficult to
control a car freely.
I want to
be like Takumi.
I want to sit next
to Takumi again.
And it'd be really helpful if I let him drive my car and watch how he drives.
I didn't notice that.
Where did he come from ?
Dammit !
He tapped
my bumper !
Don't screw with me !
You've gone too far !
I won't let you pass me !
Pass me if you can !
Speedstars ?
I made it.
The load shifts forward just before the turn-in...
...so the car loses control easily by being tapped on the rear.
The stability of
FR cars is so poor.
My pride says "You gotta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make room.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
`Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin' my dream.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
************************
LSD = Limited Slip Differential
FR = Front Engine Rear Wheel Drive
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safety zone.
************************
LSD = Limited Slip Differential
FR = Front Engine Rear Wheel Drive
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change, even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang, another round, never slow down.
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down to the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logic...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
Itsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
What do I want
most right now ?
Yes.
Time to be with Takumi.
I want to go dating more often, and share lots of memories.
But even though
it's summer break...
...Takumi is busy working, so we can't see each other very often.
Even if we're dating and I'm close to him, he looks away and doesn't pay attention to me.
Well, this'll take too long.
That makes him mysterious and charming though, don't you think ?
Initial
Next Time:
FR Killing Death Match !
Don't miss it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org