Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Kogoeta machi ni giniro shita kemuri
Silver smoke in a freezing city...
misugita yume no daisyou
...that's the cost of having an unachievable dream.
Kogoeta karada furikirenai omoi
A frozen body and unforgettable desire...
accel funde gomakasu
You deceive yourself by stepping on the accelerator.
Yoru ni kowareta mama shisen tsuyoku togarasete
Although depressed in the night, your eyes are kept sharply open.
Dareno kimagure kara sekai sae mo owarisoude
You feel like someone's careless act could end the world.
"Break in 2 the nite" It's that time.
Obieta me wo shite lost in the night
Lost in the night with frightened eyes...
ochiteku yume ni dakareru
Embraced by a ruined dream.
Kodoku ga kowakute missin' my heart
Scared of loneliness, I'm missing you in my heart.
jibun sae mo kizu tsukete
I almost hurt myself.
Taoreru kurai ni love me so much
Love me so much and knock me out.
subete wo suttee anata wo
If only I can give up everything...
Ai suru koto sae dekitara
...and love you...
kitto sunao ni naresou
...I can be my true self.
Hey, Takumi, you don't
look very nervous.
Are you alright
with this rain battle ?
I don't know.
I can't go as fast in the rain,
so I'll just drive like I normally do.
I don't know if I can
drive fast or not.
I'll try not to
push myself too hard.
If I damage the car,
Dad'll hit me.
I'll start the countdown.
Five...
...four...
...three...
...two...
...one.
Go !
Downhill Rain Battle
The S14 took the
front at the start.
Although it's a non-turbo,
it's got a 2.0 liter engine.
It's not only because
of engine size...
...but he engaged the clutch on
the slippery road very well.
He deserves what he said
about driving in the rain.
No, the Eight-Six was holding
back at the start.
It's like he could catch up anytime, once they get moving.
He took the
front easily.
This is bad.
He'll pull away by using
superior engine power.
The gap is wide.
I guess uphill is too
tough for the Eight-Six.
But it'll be downhill corners continuously from here to the base.
Once they're on the downhill, the unbeatable downhill driver's super technique will shine.
Ishimon Entrance
I don't think he'll
remain behind.
Hello ?
Oh, Brother ?
The Eight-Six and Kenta
in a rain battle ?
Yeah.
That Kenta is so confident
against the Eight-Six...
...but rain isn't
that easy, Brother.
You're right.
When playing at drift
at slower speeds, he's alright...
...but it's totally
different in a battle.
Yeah, it'll be extremely difficult to open the throttle to the limit in the rain.
If it was dry, the grip
of the tires would help...
...but in the rain, a car's behavior will be very severe.
They don't run as you like unless you use the weight shift effectively.
A small mistake will
result in big trouble.
Whether those two know the true terror of driving in the rain yet...
It'll be interesting.
``Those two ?''
You liar.
You're only really interested in HIM, aren't you ?
H...help me !
I don't want
to die yet !
Damn, it's getting heavier.
His opponent is an
Akagi Road Racer.
This isn't their home course, so the conditions are equal.
The problem
is this rain.
I wonder if he drives
well in the rain.
I think he must, because he delivers tofu everyday, doesn't he ?
So many times
in the rain...
That's right !
He must !
If so, his driving technique
will work in the rain.
I won't let you gain on me,
I'll keep pulling away.
My Q's can outrun
turbos when it rains.
He let the rear slide.
That S14 is pretty
good in the rain.
FRs have a very difficult
time in the rain.
Yeah, even if you step on the accelerator, it simply changes the heading of the car.
Here comes
the Eight-Six.
I don't believe it.
How can he drift
like that in this rain ?
What the hell was that ?
His entry gave
me a chill.
I've got goose bumps.
I...is this the driving of a man who was lovesick over a woman just a while ago ?
He said he wouldn't push hard, so is this normal for him ?
I can't see anything because of the rain and darkness. How can he drive ?
It's too dark, and I can't
see where the road is.
Don't make that sound !
This speed is insane !
H...he's not human.
He's a monster.
I'm in the groove.
I'm in my rhythm.
I'm in really good
condition today.
The legend of Akina's unbeatable Eight-Six ends today.
Not Keisuke or Ryosuke...
I'll defeat
the Eight-Six.
What the...?
The Eight-Six is
right behind me...?!
When ?
It can't be.
What happened ?
We've only cleared a few corners since the downhill began.
It's impossible.
How did I get caught so easily on the downhill in the rain ?
No...
...this doesn't
mean I've lost !
They're less than
five centimeters apart !
Look !  The Eight-Six's
about to overtake him !
The Eight-Six's about
to overtake him !
He passed him
so easily.
Unbelievable.
It was worth waiting, even though we got soaked.
Yeah.
I can't keep up !
The gap widens every time
we clear a corner !
I can't enter the corners
at the same speed.
What's the difference
between me and him ?
Isn't the rain supposed
to be my ally ?
Okay, I got it.
A report from the midpoint says that the Eight-Six has passed the S14.
I see.
As I thought, Kenta was
no match for him.
Well, he did
pretty good.
Now we know that the Eight-Six
is fast, even in the rain.
We knew that
before the race.
Weather isn't a factor in
defeating the Eight-Six.
So it's Takahashi
Ryosuke's turn.
Welcome.
~~~~~Welcome.
So it's proven that
Takumi's fast in the rain.
He's getting more
like a Road Racer.
He accepted the challenge
from the S14 himself.
His lovesickness is cured.
I guess our
plan worked.
Hey, Itsuki, you
were damn lucky...
...getting to sit in the Eight-Six's passenger seat during the rain race.
It was really scary !
I almost died !
I wasn't sitting in the passenger seat, though.~~I was in the rear seat.
The rear seat ?
Why ?
Dunno.
Takumi said he didn't have
any particular reason.
Oh, I got it.
There's a reason, and
I think I know why.
Really, Kenji ?
What is it ?
It's...
Because he
gets distracted.
Don't you think so ?
What if someone as noisy as Itsuki was in the passenger seat ?
That's true.
Oh, I see.
Wrong answer.
They're so carefree.
The reason he put him in the rear seat was as an instant setting...
...to increase the weight on the rear axle as much as possible.
Takumi probably knew it by
feeling instead of thinking.
Thank you.
I wonder how much
more he'll grow...
Takumi !
Who's she ?
Could she be...?
Takumi's girlfriend.
I thought so.
~~~~~~~~Say what ?
I didn't have any
reason for coming by...
...but I was wandering
around and ended up here.
I see.
Am I a bother ?
No.
He looks confused.
This is bad.
I don't want to disturb you at work, so I'll go home.
Oh no !~~He finally got well,
but he might get lovesick again !
Do something, Itsuki.
Even if you say that, races just don't happen when you want them !
Anyway, he has the race against Takahashi Ryosuke next week...
...so he has no
time for women.
Okay !
Hey, Takumi !
Let's go driving
on Akina tonight !
It looks dirty.
Is it because of the
battle last night ?
I head north on a morning train at the season's end.
A calm wind blows, and a bird leaves a trail in the sky.
I happen to see a familiar sight while driving by.
I unexpectedly find the town where I used to live.
Memories and the view of the town pass by beyond the window.
Hello ?
What ?
You're who ?
It's me.
It's been a while, Bunta.
Oh, you.
How unusual of you.
Did you get in an accident and are calling from a hospital or something ?
Knock it off.
Anyway, Bunta, a lot of people are talking about your son.
They say he's
pretty good.
What ?
Next Saturday ?
Takahashi Ryosuke ?
Who's that ?
You don't know him ?
He's well known in our world.
I heard that he's the number
one street racer in Gunma.
My son's gonna
race against him ?
Answer me straight.
Who do you think will win ?
I don't know.
I won't know until they race.
Sounds just
like you, Bunta.
I'm tempted to watch your son, whom you taught from the beginning to drift.
Your drift scared the shit out of me, and I still can't shake it off.
That was a
long time ago.
Mr. Tsuchiya,
you're next.
Okay.
Later, Bunta.
You've improved a lot compared to when you started, Itsuki.
Really ?~~Do you
really think so ?
I'm glad to hear
that from you.
I've been practicing
grip driving so often.
Okay, for a special presentation, I'll show you a super technique, the result of long practice.
The fantastic heel and toe !
Something's wrong.
I did it yesterday.
Okay, in the next corner !
One more time, please.
W...wait.
Hold on, Itsuki.
I'm relieved.
I was worried that you
were lovesick again.
Lovesick ?
What do you mean ?
I wasn't lovesick.
But you've been
acting strange.
Like I told you before,
I was thinking.
I'm wondering what'll happen after I win or lose against Takahashi Ryosuke.
Don't you know
what I mean ?
I don't.
Don't play riddle games.
Should there be anything
after that battle ?
It'll be okay if there's
nothing after that.
You drive fast already.
I don't.
What're you talking about ?
You are fast !
You've been winning
one race after another !
Is that it ?
I don't know
how I'd be...
For now, you'd better concentrate on the battle against Takahashi Ryosuke.
You don't have much time.
Takahashi Ryosuke...?
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
Kagayaku mirai e
...into the bright future.
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Let's make it sure over and over.
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
This passion will be eternal.
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku dakishimete
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
Kiseki no hana yo
The flower of miracles.
Ryosuke, you'll finally be able to test your hypothesis  in battle.
I'm looking forward to this opportunity to present my hypothesis.
Could you tell us your
hypothesis  in detail ?
Do you know the formula
E equal M C squared ?
It's Einstein's famous
Theory of Relativity.
First, I apply my
own logic to it.
Take E as the opponent's
average speed.
As long as my average speed exceeds it...
Initial
Next Time:
The White Comet of Akagi !
Don't miss it.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org