Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves a lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break ou
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
Please, Takumi.
It sounds so pathetic that
I can't tell Kenji about it...
...but I thought I needed to explain it to you so you understand.
I don't like it.
I can't forgive her.
Takumi...
Don't think poorly of Mako.
She's a nice girl.
How can you
defend her ?
I don't understand.
You shouldn't
go that far.
I beg you, Takumi.
Please.
Hey, Takumi, you've never seen a mountain pass other than Akina, right ?
How was it ?
I wasn't driving,
so I don't know.
I'll race her.
R...really ?
Thanks.
You've saved me.
I don't know if either of you
will be satisfied, but...
Takumi...
Anyway, I'll go to Usui
with the Eight-Six.
Sudden Death Death Match
Are you sure, Kenji ?
I can't believe Takumi is going to Usui to race against the Sil-Eighty !
Me neither.
He's not the type to go
racing in other places.
I wonder how
Iketani convinced him.
I don't know.
Iketani won't give
me a real answer.
We talked about what'd happen if Takumi drove on an unfamiliar mountain pass.
Yeah.
Well, I can understand
that he wants to see it.
Even so, it's so stupid racing the Sil-Eighty, the fastest on its home ground.
Is Takumi going
to race on Usui ?
Yes, Manager.
And is the
Sil-Eighty that good ?
It's not just good.
It took Usui's narrow
passes so freely...
...and it even used
a feint motion.
Takumi watched the Sil-Eighty with us,
so he should know better.
But Takumi will win.
You're as
airheaded as usual.
Remember the guy at the gas station said that even the local guys can't defeat her ?
Maybe Takumi doesn't care
if he wins or not.
Damn, I'm out.
I'd better take the Eight-Six for a spin, and go buy some more.
What the hell ?
My Eight-Six turned
into an Eight-Five ?!
I borrowed the car.
I left you a substitute.
Your dad must be
really surprised by now...
...because his Eight-Six
turned into my Eight-Five !
Iketani, I want to
ask you something.
What is it ?
Whose side are you on
for today's battle ?
Whose side...
I just set up
this battle...
Do you mean that ?
What about Takumi ?
Aren't you causing your friend trouble so you can look cool in front of Mako ?
I'm not doing that.
Yes, you are.
Let me ask you, then.
Do you think Takumi has the
slightest chance of winning ?
Well, Iketani ?
Give me a straight answer !
That's...
There's no way
he can win.
He only knows Akina's
mountain passes.
He's never driven Usui's passes,
and it's such a difficult course.
He has wonderful technique...
...but sometimes technique doesn't mean a lot in racing.
There's familiarity with
the course, for example.
Without practice, it won't be a fair race, even for Takumi.
You know that.
W...well...
Of course, any man is more or less powerless with the one he loves.
For my last memory
of this summer...
...would you let me race against Akina's Eight-Six on Usui's mountain pass ?
But don't let your friend down by losing yourself to a woman.
Haven't you forgotten that Takumi and his Eight-Six saved us at an important moment ?
Akina's Eight-Six
is our pride.
If you don't
cancel this battle...
...our friendship
is over.
Kenji, I understand.
Sorry. I should've talked
about this with you earlier.
I've been thinking
about this for a while.
I don't understand why you're going to quit racing.
We were obsessed when we started
racing two years ago.
Our goal was to be
the best in this area.
It's still fun today.
Or isn't it ?
I don't know how
to say this...
...but I don't feel the tension these days like I used to.
I don't know why.
I thought,
``It's time.''
I think it's
time to quit.
Is it ?
I really don't
understand very well.
I want a boyfriend...
I want to find
my love, like you.
You don't have to quit
racing to find a guy.
I do.
I don't think you can
understand how I feel.
You have someone you
like, don't you ?
Honestly speaking,
I had a guy I admired.
I didn't know.
My leading question worked.
You never told me about it.
Of course you
didn't know.
He doesn't live nearby.
I was dreaming of him
from a distance.
What's wrong with you ?
You're almost like a romance novel character who's extremely modest.
You're twenty already.
It doesn't matter.
I was happy just
dreaming about him.
``Dreaming...?'
You should look
at reality.
Sorry...
I want to see what we've accomplished in the last two years in my last race.
To put a period
to it, right ?
Sounds thoughtful of you.
He's good enough
to be our opponent ?
Yes.
Let me tell you this.
If we race on Usui's mountain passes, we can't lose no matter who the opponent is.
Or I won't be satisfied.
I know.
We have to win.
Even if it's against
Akina's Eight-Six.
Yes, definitely.
So, why don't we cancel the race, since you're not personally interested ?
Iketani and I'll talk to them, so you can turn around at the next exit.
Do as he says.
Sorry about this, Takumi.
Forgive him, Takumi.
Kenji, I'm not going
to turn around.
Takumi.
I want to race,
so I'm going.
It's my own wish, and I'm
not going to turn around.
Takumi...
But, Takumi, you know how good Mako is, you saw her with us.
There're too many
disadvantages for you.
Even though it's you, you
won't be able to win.
I know.
I'm not worried
about the result.
Don't say such things so casually.
Akina's Eight-Six is famous now, and you should protect your reputation.
I don't like it.
I've been winning because I'm familiar with the course.
But I don't like the fact that the fame is greater than my skill.
I'd feel good if
such fame went away.
H...hey.
Why...
I'm going.
I want to push as hard as I can on a mountain pass I've never driven.
Sorry about my
harsh words, Iketani.
There's nothing to say after
hearing that from Takumi.
Right.
He's so weird.
He's different from us.
I don't know if he's great
or simply airheaded.
I don't get it.
Tires are okay.
Tires with this much wear
will grab the road best.
No need to change
the suspension settings.
I think the current
setting is the best.
If you say so,
it should be.
I think you know this, but when it comes to a duel, you should avoid overusing drift.
And the key is to decide at each corner whether to skid or to grip.
Especially on Usui, where there are many consecutive corners.
I'm with you, so you should trust your technique and push hard.
No one can defeat you.
I'll prove that,
so leave it to me.
The two of us
drive as one.
I'm getting excited, Sayuki.
Tonight, my tension
is so high.
I'm looking
forward to it.
I'm excited to see how the battle'll go and what kind of driver we're going to race against.
Hey, Takumi, how're
you going to race ?
If you have
a plan, tell me.
I don't have one.
How can you
say that ?
Can't you
do something ?
I don't want
to see you lose.
How about this ?
Usui is narrow and there
are no straightaways.
Yeah.
So get the jump on her
and take the lead.
What do you mean ?
Then, keep blocking so that you can't be passed, and you'll be able to win.
That's too cowardly.
How can I do that ?
But, if they get ahead of you,
they'll pull away, and it'll be over.
You're right.
Any good ideas ?
Both are just cars
with four tires.
Are you reeeeeeeeeeally the
driver of the Eight-Six ?!
I don't believe this.
How old are you ?
I'm eighteen.
Eighteen ?
A high school kid ?
Give me a break.
You're only twenty,
so you're young, too.
And they're women.
We can't lose to
a younger kid, Mako.
Well, let's get
down to business.
These are the
race rules.
It's not fair to start
side by side here...
...because the one who's in front of the other has an advantage.
We don't want to argue
for a jumpstart or such.
My idea won't work.
So, how do we do it ?
Let one chase the other.
Get it ?
It's run and catch.
If the frontrunner runs away from the chaser, the front wins.
If not, switch positions and try again until the game is settled.
It's a sudden death
death match.
How's that ?
Fine.
We're locals, so we'll let you choose your position for the first run.
Choose front or rear.
Well...
Wait a minute.
Come over here, Takumi.
With this rule, you should take the front for the first heat.
Yeah, there'll be a second heat,
so you'll have a chance to practice.
Even if you lose in the second heat, you won't look too bad.
I know he'll take the
front for the first heat.
We'll win the second heat.
Don't worry.
Thanks for being concerned about me and giving me advice.
But I don't like it.
What're you talking
about, Takumi ?
I'll take the rear
for the first heat.
Say what ?!
Think it over, Takumi.
Okay ?
This is my battle, isn't it ?
Let me decide.
B...but...
I'll take the rear.
Rear...
Is he taking us lightly,
or is he just plain stupid ?
Okay, I'll leave
him way behind.
Who the hell is that ?
I'm busy.
This is the
Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Hello, is that you, Bunta ?
Oh, it's you.
I'm busy.
I'm worried about something.
It's about Takumi...
Are you ready ?
Let's start.
...went to Usui to race ?
I see.
``I see ?''
Is that all you can say ?
Don't you worry
about him ?
Nope.
He's my son, you know.
We'll start slowly,
so relax and follow us.
As soon as we clear the first corner, we'll drive with all our power.
That's the sign of the
start of the race.
Is that all ?
Nothing else ?
That's all.
I'm busy, so don't call me
about such minor things.
H...hey, Bunta...
Takumi, I was stupid.
I realize it now.
I knew it all along.
Even though you don't like it, you're doing this to save face for me, aren't you ?
I really regret this.
You're the pride of
all Akina's Road Racers.
I've done something
I can't make up for.
I don't want to see you
lose because of my stupidity.
Takumi won't lose !
But in reality,
it'll be difficult.
It's my fault.
Iketani...
Senpai...
...I chose the rear because
I have an idea.
What ?
I don't know if I can win, but I'm not thinking  about losing.
Takumi, do you have a plan ?
It's not really a plan.
It's just
a simple idea.
What is it, Takumi ?
Hey, tell us.
No matter how fast they are,
their car can't fly or anything.
Both are just cars
with four wheels.
Four...?
So, if their car can take a corner at a particular speed, I think I can do it, too.
That's what
I'm thinking.
I see.
It makes sense.
That's impossible.
We're going.
Let's go, Mako.
Let's finish this battle
on the first try.
Okay, Sayuki.
I'll show you the
best race ever.
Both cars blasted
off at full throttle.
Takumi's first visitor race
has finally begun.
But this battle's conditions are so tough, even for Takumi.
Don't worry.
Takumi will
definitely win !
Ai ni tsukarehate samayotte ta koro
Being tired of love, I wandered around...
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Yokubou dake ni kararete miushinatteita
...I lost myself to carnal desire.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Kimagure na unmei wa mujaki na hitomi ni miserate yuku
Innocent eyes slowly charm my unpredictable fate.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku kimo wo daite
Strongly, strongly I hold you tight.
Tatta hitotsu kono omoi wo shinjitu da to ieru
I can tell that only this feeling is true.
Yorokobi wo kanadeyou
Let's play the melody of pleasure...
Kagayaku mirai e
...into the bright future.
Ah Kazoekirenai hodo tashikameaou
Let's make it sure over and over.
Jounetu yo eien e todoke
This passion will be eternal.
Sake bara no youni akaku
Bloom red like a rose.
Tsuyoiu tsuyoku dakishimete
Strongly, strongly I hold you.
Tatoe nani wo ushinattemo kono ude wo hanasanai
Even if I lose everything, I won't let your arm go.
Utsukushiku Karen ni sake
Bloom beautifully and gracefully.
Kiseki no hana yo
The flower of miracles.
Mako, we can't lose
on our home course.
We're Road Racers.
Ummm, Sayuki.~~What will you do after Mako quits road racing ?
I'll keep on racing.
Sayuki...
So you won't retire, then.
Well, I'll race for a man.
Any cute guy...?
Any cute guy ?
Good-bye, Sayuki.
Next time on Initial D:
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org