Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves a lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
}We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
Hiroi sekai ni obieteru
You're afraid of a big world.
Hajimatta bakari no
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
Kitto kagayaku
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
Why...
I'm frustrated to death.
I want to go to
Mt. Akina so much.
I don't know if I like
to drive that much or not.
But I've been driving alone for five years, whether it was snowing or raining.
I've driven Akina
more than anyone.
Well, that's what this is all about, so let me use the car, Dad.
You'd better hurry, Takumi.
It's almost time.
There !
There he is !
No.
They saw me.
I can't even run away !
I'll be killed.
What're you doing, Itsuki,
sitting in the middle of the road ?
T...T...T...
You're in my way.
I'm gonna run over you.
Takumi, you came !
Yeah.
Sorry I'm late, Itsuki.
Takumi...
Road Racers have to accept
challenges, don't they ?
Takumi...
Stop it !
Hey...
Battle to the Limit !
He's young.
He must've gotten
his license recently.
How could a kid like him
have such techniques ?
I thought he'd
be older than me.
So that's the GT-R.
It's far better than good.
It's totally overwhelming.
It's got a drive train that combines the advantages of both FR and 4WD.
I'm Nakazato of
the Night Kids.
What's your name ?
Fujiwara Takumi.
I'll remember your name.
Let's get started.
Severe understeering is better during acceleration if the driver is good, you say ?
If the characteristics
have changed...
...don't you think he'll get
confused when he attacks hard ?
You should've told
him about that.
It wouldn't help,
even if I told him.
He's not smart enough to change his driving habits by thinking about them.
Say what ?
Then he'll...
It's okay.
Don't worry.
He's not smart...
...but his physical
responses are good.
It's too late if you respond to thinking based on feelings in the seat.
Your hands and feet have to respond unconsciously to control the drift, right ?
You don't have to worry.
His sense of accelerating the car while skidding is exceptional.
Even if the suspension settings are a little different, it won't bother him.
He'll easily find the best way and fully control the car.
The Eight-Six is the kind of car that can train the driver.
This is the finish line.
No other cars are around.
Anytime is okay.
Iketani, start when
you're ready.
Alright.
Let's start
the countdown !
Ten seconds till start !
I'm counting
on you, Takumi !
Keisuke...
...I'll let you observe this
battle from the VIP seat.
Hurry, it's about to start.
Five seconds !
Four !
Three !
Two !
One !
Go !
The 32 has the lead.
But Takumi isn't
too far behind.
Here they come.
Put on your seatbelt.
It's the FC.
Takahashi Ryosuke
rocket-started his car.
He's gonna
follow them.
My god, it's gonna be a super
battle between the three ?!
It's gonna be the match to
determine the fastest in Gunma !
That GT-R driver
isn't flooring it.
Is he waiting for me ?
It wouldn't be fair to get a lead on the straightaway.
I want a battle.
The real start is
the corner's entrance.
Nakazato is going easy on the pedal, and waiting for the Eight-Six.
I hope he won't regret this easygoing attitude during the second half of the race.
There they are.
This is the first corner !
Three cars are coming in back to back !
Incredible.~~It's just
like Bunta said.
What the hell ?
Is this a joke ?
He won't be able to follow me with that overly active ``crab walk.''
Watching him up close,
his drift is almost an art form.
Four wheel drift at full throttle with minimum counter steering...
Do you know
how great that is ?
He can control his Eight-Six like his arms and legs in a critical situation.
I can't control my
FC like he does.
I'm so impressed.
But Nakazato is
slowly pulling away.
Will he be able to
win this battle ?
This is it.
This is the feeling.
This high tension
of boiling blood...
This is a battle.
I'll push myself
to the limit.
How much longer can
you keep up with me ?
It's different...
The car's running
slightly different.
The car doesn't lose stability...
...and I can depress
the gas pedal early.
Dad must've done something
while I was working...
...because it wasn't like
this earlier this morning.
I see. That's why
he wasn't home.
I don't know why,
but I like it.
The car doesn't skid too much,
so I can step on it without worrying.
Incredible.
Unbelievable drift.
This is the first time I've seen someone who can let their car skid on a straightaway.
It's unusual. You can't do that unless the car maintains its speed.
What was that ?
That's not the kind of
drift we're used to !
Awesome !~~Once you've seen it,
you won't forget it !
Incredible !
The Eight-Six is still
keeping up with the 32 !
Takumi seems to be able to keep up with the 32.
I...incredible !
He can match Nakazato of Myogi and the superstar, Takahashi Ryosuke.
He's too good to
be my best friend !
He's so cool !
Speaking of Takahashi Ryosuke,
his FC isn't part of the battle.
He's just a third person.
Yeah, Nakazato
is the opponent.
I know he's at a
disadvantage racing the 32...
...but since it's Takumi,
he'll win, right ?
Yeah, he will !
That's right !
He's pulling away.
Nakazato's good enough
to match his big mouth.
He's balancing the load well,
and coping with understeering.
It's a driving technique to make use of the power of the GT-R.
It looks boring, but he doesn't drive wastefully, giving no overtaking opportunities.
Hey, Brother, how can
you be so laid-back ?
If he wins,
we'll be disgraced.
The battle
isn't over yet.
In the first half, the straightaways are relatively long, and the slopes are gentle.
There are many disadvantageous
factors for the Eight-Six.
From here, the slopes
will be steeper.
The downhill specialist
will show his true skill.
The 32 is good at these
low speed hairpin curves.
If I make use of the powerful brakes and slow down as I should...
The load shifts to the
front on the downhill...
...so it doesn't exhibit
understeering on acceleration.
And the acceleration in the lower gears is better than any other car.
The strongest car on the circuit is also the fastest on the public street !
The emblem on the rear is from the R of the unbeatable legend.
Can you keep
up with my R ?
Hey, Iketani.
What ?
I've been
thinking lately.
Is Takumi an unusual Road Racer
who's only fast on Akina's downhill ?
I wonder how he'd drive
on other downhills.
Haven't you thought
about that ?
Yeah, I'm very
curious about that.
But for now, this
battle is important.
Don't be defeated, Takumi.
Takumi...
Incredible.
My eyes can't focus.
Now he's
getting serious.
He's started grabbing the
gutter with the inner tires.
That's it.~~That's the
technique I lost to.
I never thought I'd
be able to see it again.
My brother's
stopped talking.
He can't relax.
I've ridden with him many times,
but I've never seen him drive like this.
He's serious.
He's closing in !
The Eight-Six
is catching up !
Impossible !
Fine then.
Now that you have done so well, my prejudice against a ten-year-old car is completely gone.
It's a wonderful machine with first class fighting capability.
I won't hold back !
I'm so glad he's
making this so exciting !
I haven't been so excited since
I switched to this car !
He can't catch up with the 32
at the exit of a hairpin corner.
Even if the Eight-Six gains on the 32 at the entrance, the gap will widen.
Nakazato's got guts, pushing so hard on the downhill with a heavy 32.
What ?!
The Eight-Six is gaining on
the 32 in a high-speed corner !
How can he four wheel drift so close to the guardrail going faster than 100 km/h ?!
It's got nothing to do
with the car's performance.
His brain lacks
a few lugnuts.
If he makes a
mistake, he'll die.
I can see the secret
of his fast driving.
Since the Eight-Six
is underpowered...
...if the car loses speed, it loses time picking speed back up.
So he doesn't slow
down wastefully.
Now I understand why he managed to stay right on my butt like a ghost.
I can't pull away.
The time he stays on
my tail has gotten longer.
Dammit !
He's tough !
The distance to the guardrail is about 20 to 30 cm for Nakazato.
That's about right for most Road Racers,
no matter how good they are.
But the bumper of his Eight-Six almost rubs the guardrails...
...and it passes the shortest distance through the corners.
He's in a
class by himself !
How can he perform such
precise drift control ?!
I've been steering hard,
keeping the ABS on.
So the load to the front tires
is greater than I expected.
It's getting tough.
The five hairpins
are ahead...
What ?
The place where you were overtaken will be the key point.
I didn't expect the battle between
the 32 and the Eight-Six to be this close.
It's indeed a battle
to the limit.
Who will win ?
This is from the five hairpins !
I can hear the squealing !
My pride says "You gotta be wild and tough."
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
Ryosuke: Takehito Koyasu
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Nakazato: Nobuyuki Hiyama
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
************************
Guys:
Takehito Koyasu
Tomokazu Seki
Nobuyuki Hiyama
Wataru Takagi
Hajime Hosoi
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
************************
Translation:
Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations:
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make room.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
`Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin' my dream.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.0
Additional Editing:
Tizya
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
************************
ABS = Anti-lock Brake System
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safety zone.
************************
ABS = Anti-lock Brake System
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change, even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang, another round, never slow down.
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down to the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logic...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
Ryosuke, most of the people said that the 32 was superior.
The length of a
normal R32 is 4640mm.
Width is 1720mm,
weight 14...
In other words ?
In other words, the length of a normal R32 is 4640mm.~~Width is 1720mm...
In other words, on
the downhill, Takumi is...
In other words, the length of a normal R32 is 4640mm.~~Width...
Never mind !
Next time on Initial D:
``Dangerous Five Hairpins.''
Don't miss it !
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org