Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
INITIAL
Information byousoku de tsutawaru jidai
Information, spreads in a matter of seconds.
Demo choice no shikata ga wakaranai
...but we don't know how to choose it.
Money can't buy my love nante...
Those who say, "Money can't buy my love..."
...nonki na yatsu ni lariat san kai
...deserves a lariat three times.
Manual douri ni tada dakiai
We make love according to the manuals.
Ai ga nai koto ni ki ga tsukanai
We don't notice the lack of love.
Chissoku suru mae ni sakebouze Ho!!!
Before we suffocate, let's yell. Ho !!!
In the midnight dream.
Iki sae tsukenai nemurenai machi
No place to relax in the sleepless city.
Suki mo misezu ni waraiatte
We smile without dropping our guard.
Uso sae safety honto ga empty
It's safe to lie and the truth is empty.
Abunai kurai ni wanna shut and break out
I desperately wanna shut and break out.
Now, we gotta start.~~Let's get moving.
Let's move into the brand new world.
Let's dive into the brand new trip.
You're afraid of a big world.
It's just begun.
Now we go full speed and funky beat.
You'll surely shine.
Around the world.
Trip to the world.
Yo! Here we go unknown world he to
Yo ! Here we go to an unknown world.
Umareta bakkari no tabibito
You're a newborn traveler.
Narenai ashidori mo mata aikyou
Unstable footsteps are fun to watch.
Kimeru took dake bashitto
Get things done right, only when needed.
So many people in this world...
...toki ni chuusyou toka mo nai wake ja nai kedo
...sometimes, you'll receive slanders.
Tsumannai took wa warp shitekou
Let's warp uninteresting things...
Suji dake wa toosite ikiteru
...and lead at least a rational life.
That's our law.
As usual...
Ultimate Tofu Guy Drift
1,300,000 yen~($13,000)
for a 1991 model.
As I thought,
the S13 is expensive.
It's the Eight-Six after all.
It's more realistic.
The car has to be F/R,
right, Takumi ?
Takumi ?
Hey, are you listening ?
I am, Itsuki.
So, how much is
that Eight-Six thing ?
Well, there's one
for 300,000~($3000).
It needs the
tag though.
And how much do you
have saved so far ?
A little
over 50,000~($500).
Long way to go.
Where can I find a
good job for quick money ?
Even if I work full time this summer at the station we're at...
...I can only earn
120,000~($1200) at most.
I wonder if I can
find a better paying job.
You guys have jobs ?
Mogi ?
What, is it so surprising
for me to talk to you ?
Not really.
120,000 for full time
during the summer ?
How long do you
work a day ?
From the morning
until the night.
You work that hard, and you only earn 120,000 a month ?
That's a ballpark figure.
Pay's really low
for high school students.
I didn't know.
I've never had a job.
Work hard, okay ?
Let's go out together
when finals are over, okay ?
Yeah !
She just said
``go out together,'' didn't she ?
Yeah.
With Mogi ?
Cool, cool !
Takumi, why didn't
you tell me ?
You should've told
me that you knew her.
It's been almost a year
since I last talked to her.
We were in the same club...
...so we used to talk often,
until last summer.
What're you talking about ?
It doesn't matter anymore.
Mogi Natsuki, huh ?
What a nice turn
in the story.
My eyes can't help
following her. She's so cute.
Takumi ?!
Hey, Takumi !
You look out of it !
We've gotta hurry !
We have a grammar test !
H...hey !
Say, why don't we buy
an Eight-Six together ?
If we combine our pay,
we can pay the loan.
I don't want to.
Why do you want
a car so badly ?
Your family has one,
don't they ?
It's no good.
My dad's car is automatic
and front wheel drive.
And the engine is diesel.
It sucks.
It's not even a car.
If it runs on four tires,
it's a car.
You don't know anything.
If it's not enjoyable on the mountain passes, I don't call it a car.
What do you do on
the mountain passes ?
It's so obvious.
Tackle the corners.
The corners ?
Is it fun
doing that ?
Of course.
You're a man, and you don't want to tackle the corners on the mountain passes ?
I'm tired of that
kind of thing.
What do you mean ?
We just got our
licenses last month.
You're pretty.
You look best
in your uniform.
Do I ?
Thank you, Papa.
Papa, my schoolmate
has a job.
Even if he works throughout the summer, he'll only earn 120,000 or so.
Well, that's
about right.
I guess it's hard
to earn money.
I receive 300,000~($3000) a month by only seeing you three times.
Is it alright
to get that much ?
It's alright,
because you're worth it.
Is it ?
I don't know.
Thank you very much.
~~~~~~~Thank you very much.
Hey, Takumi, think about
the Eight-Six, okay ?
Forget about
the Eight-Six.
You guys have good taste,
looking at an Eight-Six.
Right, right, right ?
You think so,
too, Iketani ?
Yeah, the Eight-Six
is a good car.
See ?
Well, to tell the truth, I don't know anything about the Eight-Six.
Who makes it ?
Are you serious, Takumi ?
Wanna drink some high octane ?
It's pitiful for someone working at a gas station not to know about the Eight-Six.
Well, I guess it
can't be helped.
When you guys were in 3rd or 4th grade,
the 92 was already available.
There's an old car we use
for work, at my place.
Don't compare
it with that !
Even if it's old,
the Eight-Six is different !
If I bought an Eight-Six,
could I join your team ?
I've been dreaming of joining the Akina Speedstars.
Sure.
By the way, it's Saturday, so people will be gathering on Mt. Akina tonight.
You wanna come along ?
Can we ?
But we don't
have a car.
I'll give
you a ride.
In your S13 ?
I will, I will !
I'll definitely go !
You're going, right, Takumi ?~~We don't
get a chance like this very often !
Yahoo, I'll join the Speedstars !
I didn't say I was going.
We're leaving !
Alright, and I'll pick you up at the bus station at 8:00pm !
Okay !
You're really into it.~~Which mountain pass are you going to ?
Manager, Mt. Akina is the
only place to drive around here.
Our team is proud of being
the fastest on Mt. Akina.
There are many guys who proclaim themselves the fastest on Mt. Akina.
When I was
actively driving...
...there was a guy everyone knew
was the fastest on Mt. Akina.
And he's still
driving on Mt. Akina.
Even now ?
I know most of the people driving on Mt. Akina,
but I don't know anyone that old.
He doesn't drive
at the same time you do.
He's an old guy,
who runs a tofu shop.
He delivers tofu to the hotel by Akina Lake around 4:00am.
His speed on the downhill
is well worth watching.
He has to drive in rain and snow, because it's his job.
If it's Akina, he knows everything,
even the stains on the asphalt.
I bet the fastest
on Mt. Akina...
...is the Eight-Six
from a tofu shop.
The Eight-Six from
a tofu shop ?
Are you going out, Takumi ?
Yeah, I'm supposed to
meet with Itsuki.
I don't mind you
staying out late...
...but I'll beat you until you wake up in the morning.
I know. You don't
have to tell me.
Well, I'm leaving.
Shut up, Takumi !
You'll disturb Iketani !
Even if you say so,
what's scary is scary !
It can't be helped.
Everyone's scared when
riding with a Road Racer.
Next, it's a hairpin
curve in 2nd gear.
Shut up, Takumi !
Alright, I'll push a
little harder tonight.
Okay, let's go
full tilt.
Are you alright, Takumi ?
I didn't expect
you to be so scared...
...so I pushed hard without
worrying about you.
You're such a wimp !
You're so uncool !
You must be one of those people who screams on a roller coaster !
I've never thought a
roller coaster was scary.
It's not like that.
Itsuki, you wouldn't
understand this fear...
...even if I explained
it to you.
I've never seen
them before.
Are they heading for
Mt. Akina this early ?
Something might be
happening at the peak.
Never seen them before.
Redsuns...?
Are they the Redsuns,
the fastest on Akagi ?
We're the members of the Akagi Redsuns Team.
I hate to ask this
so abruptly, but...
...if you know any team or driver who's the fastest on this mountain, let us know.
Is he serious ?
It should be us.
We're the Akina
Speedstars Team...
...and we consider
ourselves the fastest here.
That makes it easy.
Would you like to hold a ``gathering'' with the Akagi Redsuns on this mountain ?
Wow, it's gonna
be a cool scene !
What do you say ?
It's boring, always driving
against people you know.
It's exciting to drive
with other teams.
You can make new friends,
and exchange information.
It'll help improve both
of our skill levels.
We'll drive along for a while,
then pick one from each team...
...and race uphill and
downhill at the end.
We're not concerned about winning or losing, just friendship between teams.
How does it sound ?
If that's what it is, we don't have any reason to decline.
Nope.
How does next Saturday
at 10:00pm sound ?
Okay, fine.
Then we'll drive as much
as we can today.
This is awesome,
so awesome, Takumi !
We don't have to hold back !
Let's get going !
Okay !
Iketani...
Let me see how the Takahashi brothers, the fastest on Akagi, drive.
Takahashi brothers...?
Do you mean they're the super famous Takahashi brothers...
...the ones who were
covered in the magazine ?
Yeah, people call them the
Takahashi brothers of the rotary engine.
Iketani, what about us ?
Sorry, but I drive alone
when I drive seriously.
Wait here,
I'll pick you up later.
I feel left out !
Why are we the only ones
who don't have a car ?
Hey, Itsuki...
...is it so fun to
be a Road Racer ?
Why do they get so excited
about such a thing ?
I'm the one
who has to wonder.
Hearing the sounds of cars
being pushed to the limit...
...don't you get
excited, Takumi ?
Excited...
Yes, Fujiwara Tofu Shop.
Oh, it's you, Yuichi.
What's with the call
in the middle of the night ?
``It's you''
you said ?
It's been a while,
and you sound so cold.
I passed you coming
back from your delivery.
I flashed my lights,
but you ignored me.
No, that wasn't me.
It had to be, because the car was your Eight-Six.
Well, actually...
It was probably my car,
but I wasn't driving.
My son, Takumi, is delivering
tofu to the hotel now.
S...say what ?!
S...since when ?
Five years ago.
``Five years ago...?''
When he was only 7th grade ?
\C5(Note:  Japan's legal driving age is 18.)
Dammit,
I can't keep up.
They're fast.
I'm pushing myself to the limit, and I can't catch any of the Redsuns.
What do you think, Brother ?
They're pathetic.
Even our second stringers
could beat them.
We don't have to send
our best next week.
I'll pass on it.
If you won't,
then I'll pass, too.
No, you should drive.
Leave a course record that the local guys can never beat.
Otherwise, the name of the Akagi Redsuns won't become legend.
For starters, we'll rewrite every course record in this prefecture.
Soon, we'll do the same in Saitama, Kanagawa, Tokyo, and Chiba.
We'll be legendary Road Racers, leaving the fastest records in the Kanto area, then retire.
That's the Akagi Redsuns'
``Fastest in Kanto Project.''
Incredible.  They're
fundamentally different.
It's so shocking to be outrun
by outsiders on our home ground.
They've spent a lot of money on their suspension, and they've got power, too.
It's impossible to compete
with the Redsuns.
But the local people
can't run away !
Right.  Since we said
``yes,'' we have to !
But you can't beat
them with just guts.
Well, that's...
But...
It's getting late, so let's find a place to talk about this tomorrow.
Road Racers
hate defeat.
So when it comes to racing,
we tend to become overly stubborn.
Nothing could be worse than being defeated by outsiders on our home ground.
It's like the code
of the Road Racer.
Hey, where's Ryosuke ?
He went home
a long time ago.
We're the only
ones still here.
It'll be dawn soon.
Let's go home.
They can't keep up with
me if I drive seriously ?
They aren't so good.
There's somebody.
It's not from our team.
Is it an MR2 or a 180 ?
Fine.~~You won't be in my mirror after two more corners.
An Eight-Six ?!
No fucking way !
My FD can't outrun
an obsolete Eight-Six ?
Am I having a
bad dream or what ?
Shit !
I'm number two
in the Akagi Redsuns !
He doesn't know
what's ahead ?
After this slow right-hander, there's a tight left corner.
If he doesn't slow down, he'll end up at the bottom of the ravine.
As I thought.
He's going too fast.
He doesn't have enough room
to recover and slow down.
W...what the hell...?
Inertia drift ?!
My pride says "You gotta be wild and tough."
*************************************************
Takumi: Shinichiro Miki
Bunta: Unshou Ishizuka
Itsuki: Mitsuo Iwata
Natsuki: Ayako Kawasumi
Yuichi: Tomomichi Nishimura
Iketani: Kazuki Yao
Papa: Tohru Furusawa
Sou tanin wo kaizai shinai
I don't let others meddle in.
******************************
Ryosuke: Koyasu Takehito
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
~~ Hajime Hosoi
Kenji Nojima
Jun Suzuki
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Never stop tomaritakunai
Never stop. I don't want to stop...
************************************
Ryosuke: Koyasu Takehito
Keisuke: Tomokazu Seki
Kenji: Wataru Takagi
~~ Hajime Hosoi
Kenji Nojima
Jun Suzuki
Nobuyuki Tanaka
Gisei ni natta ai ga cry shitemo
...even if I sacrifice my crying lover.
***************************************
Translation: Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations: Hiroaki Fukuda
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Peak mezashite sweep the winding street.
Head for the peak, and sweep the winding street.
*****************************************************
Translation: Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations: Hiroaki Fukuda
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Beep beep! Keikoku on wa so cheap
Beep, beep! The warning sounds so cheap.
***********************************************
Translation: Hiroaki Fukuda
Song Translations: Hiroaki Fukuda
Editing:
Lillian
Hiroaki Fukuda
Todd Perkins
Barbara
Dave
Mouse
Sheep wa michi wo akero
The sheep should make room.
*********************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.02
Additional Timing:
Tizya
`Cos I'm never gonna stop streakin' my dream.
***************************************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.02
Additional Timing:
Tizya
Easy na motibation
Your motivation is easy.
***************************
Timing:
Todd Perkins
A
Central Anime
Production
Version 1.02
Additional Timing:
Tizya
Subete wa simulation
Everything is simulated.
Nigete mitatte doko demo safety zone
Even if you want to break out, you'll end up in a safety zone.
Nanika wo te ni irete nanika wo wasureteku
You obtain something while you lose something else.
**********************************************************
Eight-Six: 1983 Model
FD:  1991 Model
Papa = Older men sometimes pay
~~~~~~~~~young girls to be with them.
The girl usually refers to the man as "Papa."
Sekai ga kowaretemo kawaranai
It won't change, even if the world is destroyed.
Beasty shout dareno te ni sae oenai
Beasty shout. No one can handle it.
Hageshii yume jikan sae mo ima koeteku
The raging dream goes beyond time now.
Rage your dream yami wo harisaite iku
Rage your dream to break through the darkness.
Like a stream to the peak.
Sekai juu no kogoekitta yoru wo keshiteku
It will eliminate the frozen night.
Rage your dream michi wo hiraiteku
Rage your dream to explore the road.
Di-ding dang, another round, never slow down.
Comma zero ichi byou de Knock down
Knock down in comma zero one second.
Yoin nokoshi kietekou to the next town
You head for the next town, leaving trails.
Hokori mau haisha chi ni hau
Dust rises and the loser falls down to the ground.
Rikutsu dake no nogaki tachi
The puffery, full of logic...
Jama kusai kara shikato shiteikou
...is bothering, so let's ignore it.
Streaker satteiku street no mukou
The streaker disappears into the street.
Something they would know.
Rage your dream.
tsuzuku hatenai michi wo
In the never-ending street...
Ai mo kako mo furimukazu
...without looking back at your love or your past...
Yukeru anata kagayaiteiru
...you keep on going, so you shine.
Rage your dream.
Ima wo ikiteiru
You live in the present.
Drift fans and Eight-Six owners,
sorry for the long wait !
Initial D has finally started !
How'd you like Takumi's Eight-Six chasing around that super high performance...
...350HP FD, 1.6 liter, non-turbo,
using his super drift technique ?
It was totally
awesome, wasn't it ?
Initial D is full of distinctive essences that those who know cars well can truly enjoy.
Watch a hot race in
the next episode, too !
Initial
Next Time:
Declaration of Revenge !~~Howling Turbo
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org